You Jamie card me, okay, then a card
Okay, come on more than you more than I'll do one if you want more
Oh, let's get the moon. Wow the moon. There's Alice with the Cheshire cat the Cheshire cat this cat full of illusion
Okay, Jamie wants the card to
Okay, there's the moon.
Okay, so it's supposed to be revealed.
Just like the treasure cats or treasure cats,
you know, in their smile,
like not things are everything they've seen.
There's like illusion going on,
but things will be revealed.
You have to wait, wait until the morning,
things will be clear.
This is all, it's all illusion at night, right?
One more, let me, Jamie wants one.
Jamie, it's a car, okay, Jamie wants a car.
Jamie you got this four of flowers, okay four
Four is so it's all right open right to it's the four flowers is an exciting
Celebratory card suggesting you'll have the cause to throw a fun tea party of your own very soon
This is your family reunion housewarming party birthday celebration
Or another milestone in your life. Enjoy the exciting time with friends and loved ones. Hope you like that
Jamie looks like time to celebrate looks like time to find out your hair down
How's everyone doing today
Thank you for being here like the chats moving fast. I think algorithms already improving
Another drink here and another I guess it's like a heart. I see
I'm gonna go to subway in a little bit
Thank you so much for the
Donator
Mommy dinner tonight. Thank you so much
I hope everyone's doing good
Welcome in everyone thanks for coming in I'll put the invite up come on up and say hi. You want to say hi
Some more drawings tonight
Oh, good night. I didn't do it. I didn't take a hit of DMT today. I
Need to I need to be more. Thank you. He-man. You're awesome. He-man. Thank you so much
Hey guys join the membership
That's a lot of fun
I'm gonna do some members only streams too
Hey, thank you guys
Love you guys
But Jamie's holding it down
Yeah, so it's been pretty crazy
Oh, I don't think I was a real Freemason
It's like Freemasons don't I never seen like the like a red
Sass or other than he's a he's a Grand Wizard or what do you Grand Master or something? I don't know
I'll believe him
And someone's are saying stuff about racial what the fuck
Subway
She gets subway
They walk over there I can walk over
Much about two percent. Okay, I'm gonna walk over
Hey, pull up my phone is up. Oh Pony
Hey, baby, there it is
Hi guys
Up nice
Hey time
Only one mod. Let's go crazy. Nice one. Nice
Word
Yeah, it's a nice word. Thank you time. You're nice
Time's a good dog. We saw time's picture
I'll do good. Thank you for coming time. Thank you for coming everyone. I'm not gonna stop guys
Guys as long as we're not
Are we up free?
Are you able to breathe? Are we able to wake up? Are we able to?
Just do something for ourselves
You know make a good life for ourselves
Better obstacles the matter
negativity
Always the way out
Some weird people charisma who's weird not time. I'm not weird. There are some weird people out there, you know
we want to
Be compassionate people
A lot of people have had different upbringings different experiences
different role models different
different things different values and
Hey, we can always like learn from each other
It's a big world a lot of different people all kinds of people
Are we doing tonight, let me see I'm interested
Hopefully the phone's charging a little bit, but it's like 10-15% of look over a subway
Should have my friend coming back something to clean the house
Good heart. Hey this guy needs a little bit of help. Yeah
I think there's really good people out there,
people with big hearts, people that are willing to share,
people willing to love people, forgive,
be a positive influence in the world.
There's a lot of like, nasty little
mean groups and subplots and schemes and so.
Let people breathe, let people live, let people do their thing.
How's everyone doing in the chat?
Come on, where's everybody?
Come on up.
I like that guy, Michael Lionheart.
Pretty cool.
So I'm gonna check what anybody can happen tonight
or pretty quiet evening.
Isn't it a quiet evening?
It's been nice, nothing really exciting.
You know, Bita came this morning, we had Christine
You know a bunch of you are banished with big pipes. I don't know if you guys know Mr. Big Pops
He's just trying to try to use them like voodoo or something on me kind of cast some spells on me
You know, I'm sure it wasn't good
I banned him he said he said I hexed you 666
So I think he's kind of delusional
specific
Shit order guys. I'm hungry
Yeah, what a dick
And then they cast a guy well everyone's just trying to hex me he's magic on me. I mean if you have any power you only need to use
sigils or magic or any easiness signal
Lobster guys? What's this? Lobster? Lobster grill sheet? That sounds so good. Lobster rolls? Oh my
god, that sounds so good. Where's Joker been? I don't know, Joker kind of turned on me.
I don't think Joker likes me anymore. That's where I'll go for hours.
Let's see offers and jokers. I haven't seen Joker Joker just like kind of said oh side. He's like your site
You know your you kind of expand me talky free talky sway go chicken sandwich
Talkies chicken sandwich. Okay, it's for you
19 value may have coffee to
But yeah, yes, please enter a but yeah, you like that yes enter the but like how do you feel? How do you feel?
Has it to have a butt in your butt? Oh my god. They have oh my god. They have a coffee brownie twist milkshake
almost chocolate
cheese talk
Man it's Wendy's so good
Wendy's if I okay so I can get two chicken sandwiches. Where's the chicken?
Spicy chicken sandwich
What's the sandwich the whole sandwich is called?
The talkies flago. Where's the talkies flago?
Hi, I think that is
When is when he's complicated?
Brutal lounge
7-Eleven
El Amigo I
Said if I love I know time he told the whole story
He said he said two hours a woman paged him with the butt plug. It got way too disgusting for me to handle
Hi Ilya, Ilya is my, he's one of my sweethearts.
Ilya, what are they doing?
Ilya, they're harassing me.
You help me?
People are harassing me.
She's a big pepsi, I put a curse on me.
Okay.
That's a weird start.
That was a weird start, I know.
Yeah, this is a big pepsi, I was like, you know.
So let's take something and mr. Beat Pups, but yeah, I'm not gonna judge him
Banshee grilled cheese
Caramelized onions to make a ripe avocado between oh my god
Sounds good
Pan shadow bacon burger, she probably chicken mushroom mark Mac attack macaroni and cheese grilled cheese
Guys let's fucking do it
But we're kind of for a sourdough. Okay. Let's do 20 bucks. Okay 20 bucks
Okay, that's worth it. It's worth it. Let's fucking live guys. Let's fucking live for them. Let's live for the moment
Let's go
Macarons. Oh, I mean so it macarons. She's groceries. Yeah, it's coming some the way
Hey, dude, come on up everyone come up. Is it Lincoln Lincoln? Oh, I need to open the link
For my phone dies, huh YouTube?
Jada you're doing are you doing bad things to me?
What are your intentions here? Oh
There we go timing time you're gay. It's okay if I'm gay. I don't mind gay people
I put the things in the fridge. I put them in the fridge. Okay, I think I'm way ahead of you way ahead
Money guys, hey, Jamie's Cowboys. Yeah, look J-Dog look
Awesome people
Yeah, you know time's telling you like guys come up here. Let's talk on the panel
I love you guys. I love you guys so much
Hey Rudy
The future they're gonna have problem with that. I don't know why did I get it's like yeah, are you living your shoes?
Hey, hey, oh, he's meowing good. Hey Rudy you're feeling better. He's meowing good
Hi
Me out and not strong
Really you're good
Everyone live your truth, you know, but you know what?
We can always change for the better. You know, it's like it's not your truth
They don't let other people define your truth for you. You you look you decide who you are you change for the better
Your past doesn't define you, right?
Yeah, are you kidding? Are you sleeping on that on your porch swing?
Don't judge you see that was on this poor swing. It's okay
Yeah, I'm starving guys in this camera. Oh, it's so good
Thank you for my donate or night. You got me dinner. Thank you so much. I
Have created a bit from subway as like as like oh wow macaroni and she
macaroni and she's on sour
Ruby rooster that was a strong meow. Yeah, he's wow. Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're learning truth
Yeah, all right, where are you talking? Yeah, we're talking shit about me J dog after here
Everyone's like all of a sudden
Well, I hear yeah, who's that? Are you fix? I mean, yeah
Hey, Dougie Doug, I'm back. You know, I didn't like that here. Hey Dougie Doug has a membership. That's awesome
Remember it's Dougie Doug. Thank you Dougie Doug. I'm glad, so good.
Do you get, I think, do you win a membership? Dougie Doug's an awesome guy. Thank you so much.
You never did. I just saw that one clip, J-Dog, where you were like telling, talking to the AMC.
Yeah, it's awesome. I love having
great people with this tag, great members.
I love you guys. I really do. I'm having a good dinner tonight. Why don't you catch up on that sounds fun?
I think they're still preparing it
My order is on oh the courier is heading to the store play one minutes
Well, that is a real Doug D. Oh, that's that's so you're there Dougie Doug Doug D is a different person. Yeah
Awesome Doug why no
You don't need some members today, and I think ten yesterday I
Think another five today
Thank you guys so much. That's awesome
We're growing it just helps the channel. Thank you so much 60 people
Guys, I hope you're having fun on my show
Time is a gentleman around town maybe
Time you're the you're the good guy
Come on up. J-Daw, come on up.
What do you want me to do?
I'm going to speak a blunt.
I still have this little vape left.
I'll try this.
It's almost empty. It has a little bit left.
Forget a hint.
So forget a hint.
Had a hit it was a hit with almost out
Hey everyone in chat guys, I'm gonna eat this macaroni and cheese in front of you
Hey, hey, hey, what's the eye? Oh, what's that?
Miss Lola
Hi, baby Ferrari
time
Yeah, the hot dogs doggy dog. Yeah, it's kitty kitty. Hey, Lenore. Hey, Lenore
You want to come over here guys? Have you seen Lenore? Dougie Doug? You love Lenore. You love her
Lenore, come say hi
Yeah
This Lenore
Guys a little bit. She's a little bit fussy lately here. This is Lenore
Say hi hi Nor is a sweetheart. You're a sweetheart a cat nor be the camera
It's my Kevin
Miss Lenore my little black hat
There's Lenore Jamie. See she's fine Jamie was like, where's Lenore Lenore's things in the temperamental
Have a key this is like the path. Oh, I'm sorry
Yeah, that is that's Lola right there. Lola loads over there. Hey Lola
If you want to say hi
Yeah, another girl. Hey, we're my boy
Hey, what's up, bro? How you doing? Oh good. How are you just chilling man?
Are you mad at me?
No, why would I be mad at you? I don't ever want to be mad at me these days. Everyone that yells at me
No, bro, we love psyche. We love psyche. We love what psyches?
Awakens Carol. We love you. Oh, thank you. Hey, who wants to hide you?
Look at your face. You make a face. You say hi kiss kiss kiss. Yeah, you kiss yeah, I'm the kitty
Squeakers yeah, oh
You're kidding me. Yeah, I'm sorry baby Ferrari. Yeah, it's always horrible lose a pet
Well, so that's your favorite one ever. That's Lola and then there's tricks back there. There's Lenore. They're all around me right now
Oh, yeah, I was gonna tell you man. Um
Time is really a homosexual man. So I know he might be interested, you know
I see him all the time and I think time should come on panel and finally just you know come out the closet and just
Reveal his true love for you psyche and I think everybody will just be very happy if you just get that
Time is this trip time you're in love with me. This is you
And the only way for him to confess right he needs to just come on the panel and just admit it
Yeah
Let's do it
Little are you watching?
There you go. Well, you see data. Oh, look, you know, this is over there. Oh
Actually, hi, hi
Yeah, I like that you know things this is something to live up. You know, are you you're lying?
No, I'm not lying time is really a homosexual. Tell them to come up
Time come black RG. Come on. What could you really go?
You make see Mexican K KX Mexican. Hey, I'm with them in Kentucky
Time is homosexual if time loves the wings he loves it. I
know
If you're mocking you time, I don't know. You're mocking time
You're mocking me. No, we have we have a guest tonight. Let's welcome our new guest
Hi
How are you? I'm good. I'm at work. You're
Yeah
well
I'm doing pretty good today. I had a nice, I had a nice spiritual bath today and it took a lot of negative energy away
So I don't know much energy negative energy is around us and on us until
It gets removed and it's like a huge weight off my shoulders and it's like a huge
one site I
Have a
Myself back so home. I'm walking my lifestyle by acting like he's an insult to lie. Oh, yeah
You're making fun of gay people J dog. You're J dog summer. You're J dog, right? Yes. I don't do dog
Here
Have a summer it was like my girl cat with the white on her face, too
Yes, they're gorgeous cats
It is so hot here. It is 11 o'clock at night, and it feels like a hundred degrees. Oh
We're under that heat wave that's going through the Midwest and it's just it's miserable. We are
Yep, believe it or not Kentucky because like all the mountains and stuff we have around us
We're kind of down in the valley a little bit. So that makes it 10 times humidity. I mean the humidity is just
Well, it's kind of like just like a bowl, huh? Yeah. Oh
The heat just sits there and it's
It's bad
But allergies are bad that people would breathe in, you know, if you have breathing issues
It's hard to but it only lasts for a couple weeks
But it's it's a refer a little bit and then that it'll break and it'll you know be hot
But it won't be like I can't breathe type hot like right now. It's like stuffy as fuck
So but you know
Happens every year. It seems a little bit hotter this year
I've said that before like I've had a couple of protests and I've done a couple of like I was a pride parade the other day
And I mean it's just I walk all over the city and it's so hot dude
Like I go home and I have to take like three or four showers a day. It's so fucking hot. I can't do it
Out of those homeless people do it like I feel bad for them like
Yeah, we don't have a shelter, no food, no, you know, water.
I'm sorry. Yeah well we try to keep them with as much water especially and food
and then we do you know we give out things that'll help with their shelter to keep shade and stuff
like tents or even tarps and different things like that that'll help you know but it's still it's
still rough you know we we have enough teams in our city that we're you know we're always there's
always some people on the street helping but even with that it's like the weather we have to deal
We find people dead because of heat strokes and shit.
You guys give them like tents like these, right?
Yep.
Well, they'll be the pop-up tents with the tarps, not necessarily that big.
No.
No, this is a makeshift one. This is just like for a patio.
Well, now I was gonna okay. Yeah, I was gonna say they do make some stuff
Don't make makeshift stuff like that with all the tarps and stuff like back in the
Like especially in the woods when we go back into some of those
I'll tell you what some of them guys can fix up some real shit like it's it's I'm like damn dude. That's the opus fuck
Have you seen somebody they drag an extension cord from some kind of property?
Or some kind of public access to where they got it rigged
They had electricity and they got a hot stove and they got well their radio and TV and I'm like what and they got Wi-Fi
I'm like, how the hell do you have all this and we had one guy
Him and his people on their camp. They even had like, you know the stoves that you put the wood in and has the long
Piping that the smoke comes out of it like they made one of those like it was it was it was there's I mean, you know
You think about a lot of people that are homeless is that they're veterans and and different things like that
So they have certain skills that you know, I mean, there's a lot of portrait. There's a lot of veterans on the street
It's almost like it's almost like prisoners because a lot of prisoners are like
Extremely talented in some way, especially when they're in prison, their brilliance can come out because finally they're isolated, they have nothing to do, they have no drug distractions, women distractions, and they can focus their creativity.
I've seen prisoners make these very intricately designed doll houses.
Cakes out of Oreo cookies and kind of stuff. What do you think?
Sometimes I think I think everyone's brilliant, especially but especially sometimes people would because of their psychopaths and
criminals
Let's say criminals are smart as fuck. I mean some criminals work, but I mean I think it's just human nature
And I think there's a lot of people and you know
I'm speaking from your experience have just gone through a lot of crazy dumb different shit and
You know you think that well, I would never be able to do that
I would never be able to do that but by human nature like you're you know
I mean, I'm sure there's gonna be some people that'll just like and will it off because that's just the way the world works
But most people will be able to no matter what circumstances they're in you know, at least
figure something out
Well, you know, it's like, you know, even you know, even Donald Trump, I think Donald Trump
filed bankruptcy, right?
Even he's in the right and filed back. He's in the negative, but you know, he was able to
Use what he had use the connections get some loans buy some more real estate, you know
You know he would get back to billionaire so we can like have it all lose it all we can get it back
Hey, Jenny Jen. Thank you for coming
Your new member, thank you so much
What's up Jenny?
Thanks for becoming a member Holler
They are macaroni and cheese grilled macaroni and grilled cheese sandwich. It's macaroni and grilled cheese
You're welcome. Thank you. Thank you so much. Welcome to the membership
I'm so happy to have you here. I'll have a little baner. I think I'm directly in this office. I'm gonna get me a cold milkshake
So fucking hot. I love a good milk. I love a good milkshake. I do love a good milkshake or a malt
My dad used to make these malts and the mill malt. Yeah
oh yeah so guys you know the song it's a crew crew crew some man you know that
no yeah yeah it's been a banana rama okay yeah so what's up to the night
It's hot!
Tuesday night.
I played on Tuesday night, so...
Well...
And you're with the cats, you know, so summer like I have a friend of his girl. They have Shawna. She's like
She's like my mom over my friends. They're this I can't hang out, but she's becoming over
She keeps our vacuum cleaner and a bunch of the cleaning products tonight. She's gone right now
But she's helping me clean my house. You know, she put my kitchen floor
Really well. I'm getting back on track
But yeah, sometimes it's good to have people that are like, hey, let me help you out.
And so we get the tent tour.
Yeah, there's no piss bottles here.
Get out to the pissing bottles, either.
Yeah, I'm going to pee bottles.
Summer mr. Big I you know I kick mr. Big perhaps of the show summer
He's weird
Yeah, he was just being so weird and then he said you know what he said after he came off the show
He said he hexed he hexed me and that um in 666 and he just wanted to chill and I'm so jelly
Well, that's pretty but I just want to say thank you Jenny because that yeah
Yeah, that big box dude is odd. Oh my god, and he was like hitting on page and pages
like you want to sing the page and he played a song he played songs for
literally for literally hours he's playing the same song and then he was
being remember how I used to be like inappropriate with guys sometimes no I'm
gonna do that again because this is because it's appropriate inappropriate
with me and now I feel violated and so I understand people feel it's what we're
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, thank you. Yeah. Oh, yeah, there we go. Well, I love having a show. I love I love my show. Yeah. Thank you. Thank you, J dog. Oh, the other one. Yeah. But okay, I got a two for I got a two for summer. Do you like it?
Hi, I'm not into armpits
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, Jen. Yeah. Oh, no, no, it's okay. Thank you. Thank you
Yeah. Oh, well, oh, ladies got a thrill.
Trevor's still here. You got a thrill, too.
Yeah, J-Doc, do you want a card?
Do I what?
Do you want a card tonight?
Do I want a car?
Yeah, a card.
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
OK, so J-Doc, oh, oh, oh, OK, OK.
What is this?
Hold on.
Can you see it?
The mystery the mystery. Okay, one
mystery
So, oh, there's a Cheshire cat. You see the cat smiling
There's something something you've been told of us or something some kind of mystery you are
Pursuing I'm thinking like this is who we do. Okay, so this is a mystery
But the mystery is also the high priestess the traditional decks
And your women are mysteries to it says the mystery represents
wisdom
Intuition and subconscious the card like the Cheshire cat
Carries the message that things aren't always what they seem
The mystery advises you not to take anything at face value, dig deeper, use your intuition
to discover what's really going on below the surface.
Take time to consider situations or new perspectives.
You may discover that the challenges you're perceiving aren't even truly there at all.
Hi.
Do you like that one?
That was a good one.
What oh, oh, what's this?
This is the what it says one of spears. Oh, this is the aces. I think the ace of spears. So okay
So it's like the ace of swords something's being handed to you to help you. It's like a
Okay, you're just kind of boom ace of spears I spears
It says
Asus Spears represents new ideas and clarity you had a breakthrough and are feeling inspired
to brainstorm plans for the next great adventure.
This is a great time for stargazing.
So there you go.
That was a good one.
Yeah.
I think we should stargaze tonight.
I think that's what that says.
We should.
We're going to look at the sky and we're going to trip out on it.
Yep.
Hey.
Okay, guys.
Hey, black RG.
You want to come up on the panel?
Summer, are you there?
Yeah, I'm here.
Do you want a card, Summer?
Or a few cards?
What did you say?
Do you want a few cards?
Yeah.
I'll take a couple cards.
Okay.
Summer the free your first car is judgment. Okay
It's in a stick the the white rabbit here blowing the blowing the trumpet calling judgment, you know
but
This is things that that
You know something's been going on and it's about to be be ending and just gonna be called things are just as a
Following judgment. So I think they are gonna be made fair. So it says
with all the white rabbit
Loze's trumpet to announce the arrival of the Queen of Hearts, the tarot card judgment
announces the arrival of an important realization.
Judgment marks the time to make amends for past blunders or wrongdoings and forgive yourself.
Everyone makes mistakes, that's the simple nature of it.
Whether you've hurt someone's feelings, made a poor judgment call, found yourself late
for a very important date, judgment encourages you to make amends and forgive yourself.
you've come so far along your journey and grown so much along the way it's time to leave regrets and
guilt in the past and move forward okay so i don't know if there's any judgments or guilt but
time to move forward oh look you got this oh hold on you got this queen of spears and so look
there's that you know i'd never seen the scene in the movie i don't know if it's there but the queen
of spears queen of swords and there's like the queen of hearts on the on the throne
Doing the judgment and then Alice grows and she's like no he's hands up against the bully. That's what it is. Yeah, exactly and
And that's what a lot of quit the Queen of Swords do is like, you know, they are able to
To use that sort of truth, you know cut the negative people out Queen of Swords. Let's see
So we got the Queen of Swords says
The Queen of Swords has a strong sense of fairness and willing to fight for what feels what she feels is right
Like Alice at her trial the Queen of Spears is direct and level headed doesn't tolerate nonsense
This tarot card is a reminder to stay confident even in the face of adversity
Stand up for yourself when necessary
There you go. I have one more for you
Okay, you got the eight of the eight of cups. Okay. Hold on one second. Is this the right person? I think
Hold on one second
It's me
Hi, I see you. So I'll let you do your tarot reading love it eight of eight of cups
So this is a pregnancy kind of kind of emotional strength you have because eight is the traditional traditional
strength card
eight of cups is like you
You're really strong and even in your motions and so this is eight
Says you've recently achieved a goal you put a lot of energy into but aren't finding it fulfilling as you expected it to be
Time for introspection if you're if you're unsatisfied you reflect on what maybe
Self-reflection may help you discover what will make you truly happy and content
So I think you've achieved a lot what you want to but there's still something else you're like looking to achieve
So keep going, go through your, if you have other dreams to achieve, go through your dreams, you know?
Yep, I think we should all be wanting to level up every day.
Yep.
But just make sure, everyone make sure you're thankful for what you have, because we have so much, there's so much potential we have in ourselves.
Thanks.
So we can do, yeah.
I agree.
100%.
What's up, Penn State?
Hi, Penn State.
What's up, Summer?
How you doing?
I'm doing well, but more importantly, how's my homie psych doing?
To me. Yeah, you motherfucker. Me. Okay. Okay. What are we talking about exactly my fish taco friend?
Yeah, I miss your fish taco. You're the only nigga that likes fish tacos more than me
Maybe but are you in a tent? Oh this nigga disappeared
Are you in a tip right here? Yeah, right here. This is my patio tent right here. I'll show you why you look like Riddick
You know
Don't make all me a video game character
No, it's a tent right here
Yeah, I'll show you. I'll give you a full tour of the build a bum shelter on your house
Let's see this bedroom. That's not my bedroom. Oh, it's his living space now
No, it's not a living space. It's just a spot just to just chill just to just fucking fuck around and just look at exercise bike
Up in this bitch look at you. Okay. Okay
You build a bum shelter outside of your house with
Yeah, we'll go outside. We'll check this shit out. Oh hell no. Yeah, he was a Riddick
Is this an Airbnb as well remember be careful. No, it's not an Airbnb. You know what happened last time
Well, we won't make that mistake again
Yeah, you'll be surprised. You know, maybe I already did
Let's check it out for more
So what's y'all been over here talking about?
Oh, it's you know, it's just bit. Oh, we're having to see my my I think though the drawer dash person's here
Macaroni and cheese sandwich coming up. Thanks, but it's enough to you know, it's been like you know a little bit quieter my chat
You know, I love people are mad at me or you know, I've just been too much a fuck up lately
But why don't people be mad at you? How you been so I don't know
I mean you do my best, but you know
You know
trying to
Yeah, beat is mad at me. Yeah, why's beat a man. He's always mad and drunk. He don't look up mad. Yeah
Yeah, I
Don't know. Hey loser loser. He never said he think he misses through Matt. Yeah
If I move away from a phone
Yeah, also the back where she's at it's almost here. I think it's plent the guy's pulling up a little bit
I think it's ketchup on it would be good
Have you and Jay dog got fish tacos yet?
Yeah, I'm biting me. He's like he says he thinks he's
What you talking about?
Nigga he's not trying to fuck you. He just wants to go. Yeah, you guys are friends. He said
You're gonna go with us this age. You know if I lived in California, I would definitely get fish tacos
It's like we're gonna have a threesome. No
Okay, there you go. There you go. He made the proposal
Here with me. I'll be it. I'll be at this stage his butt and then he'll be
With the GHP no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I don't get down there with some
I just doing gay things to both you another
He used to pay people in prison to great people
No, I didn't but I got paid. What'd you do? You got paid? You're yeah, you're involved. Yeah, you're involved
It's a creep in prison. Tell me that I got paid
Yeah, you're just anything horrible like that. Are you why are you so evil?
He says he sells a dog is a gay pimp. You're you're
Here here here I'll tell you guys
Summer he was a CEO in prison and what he would do is take payment and let other men rape other men in
prison as a CEO
Oh, you're a whole bit
I have no idea how he lives in a patty. It's it
Yeah, that's not true
Okay
No, I'm so evil. No, I'm so evil. No
I joked around about that but never that happened.
There's like no, your father will come back around and this is going to happen to you or somebody who has no proof.
There's no proof that that happened, there's no proof.
Who the fuck joked about it? Who the fuck joked about shit like that? That's where it is, fuck!
Exactly.
That's lame, they're starting to shit you just don't joke about and that would be one of them.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Well, it happened. That's what happened.
Jay dog. Yeah, Jay dog. Why why don't you think about these people and like have sympathy or
One of like, I don't know. This is weird
And that's they're like, you know, they did it like murder
No, I never murder nobody. I never get I you but
Murderer he's just a
Advocate for great
No, I'm not an advocate. No, there you go putting jackets on me. No, I'm putting jackets on you
This came out your mouth. You told us I was a CEO and I would let home
I would let the people get grapes for money and I'll do this and do that was that that was right there
That was a motherfucking
Well, what is what is my boy Jim say a machination wasn't no machination. Yes, it was look at summer. Yeah
Stank face. Yeah
J-doll like
Something like that dude like pro like and the universe on the way
I don't give a fuck what it was. I don't give a fuck. That is one thing like come on, dude, really
No, I regret it. Don't get me wrong. I'm not
joking
No, I didn't I didn't joke about me doing anything to know what I didn't do nothing
That's predator shit. You're bragging and joking or whatever about setting up somebody getting great and you a ceo
That's why nobody fucks with you motherfuckers cuz I'm fucking right
This nigga from California. He even from the Midwest. He ain't from like Ohio, Kentucky
Fucking California
Different in Kelly
Yeah
And the joke about that like that
It's not sure don't worry, it's not sure
I don't know. I don't know.
There's no chicken or nothing.
No, this is back. We're in
grills. It's all carbs,
psyche. It's all vegan.
Actually, you're skinny as hell.
You need carbs. Eat that shit.
No, I will eat that.
Yeah, I'm gonna catch up to you.
Eat it, psyche.
I will.
Hey, guys, who likes Rocky
I'm rock your picture show anyone see that movie
No, I'm just
Yeah, J-Doc's a monster
Yeah, J-Doc
What are you thinking J-Doc? Why'd you do that? I regret it. No, is that Texas toast?
It's sourdough. Oh hell. That's even worse. Why do you people do this sourdough? That's a Cali
Because sourdough is the best
What fucks are monsters?
You don't fuck with it
Why not
Does white house be having milkshakes
Yeah, they got strawberry vanilla and chocolate
But you got something to make it extra blended
Yes, you niggas over in California don't even got white
No, we don't got white captain we got five guys
even worse. Yeah. Yeah. We
at that burger. We got in and
out. We got in and out down
We just opened two in and out.
I just got out. It's like a
Holler in the hollers, baby
Yeah, you got to get a wimpy burgers out there. That's a good shit. They fried the bread the best guy
What a triple cheese burger is about what an extra large fry. Well, no a chili cheese fry fuck all that
Chewy cheese
Chewy cheese fries, that's what it'd be what made you pick those sunglasses
Why are you hitting on my glass or stage? Why is it a boy's in a jargum? Where are you Hawaii or something?
Fuck here 842
I'm over here in Michigan
Okay
It's all the same time, but I'm very familiar with Kentucky. I heard you say you were from there earlier
Yeah, so I did what I do all my work. That's what on Wednesday
So I go live I always drive around the city instant because that's what we do
A lot of people don't realize that they'd be like, oh, that's just Kentucky. I'm like, listen
And Michigan and all that get in trouble and they come down to here
So yeah, I think you have to change like it's it's actually sad right now the way you know
I've got a wiener snitchell down there
What they got the hot dog
a wiener's ritual?
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
You have hot dogs.
Did I love the wieners?
Yeah, no, they're hot dogs.
They got the best hot dogs.
The best chili cheese dogs ever.
Yeah.
Right here, shout out to Wieners Knicksles in California.
I don't know if there's anyone else.
Hey, how big do you like your wieners?
No, we're gonna get we're gonna get a motherfucking if we're gonna get a hot dog. We're gonna definitely get an
All-beef Chicago dog
That's what we're gonna get with some chili cheese
Have you guys ever been to Chicago I grew up in Chicago, right?
And so there's a place that you can go in Chicago
It's over on the south side and the ladies will cuss you the fuck out like they will climb on your ass
They will roast you from head to toe, but that's like their thing. That's what they do and like their favorite
Is it the dicks place?
It might be I can't my fucking brain with my memories this I have a TV
They put like a hat on you and shit roast the fuck out you yep
And it's in like a little it almost looks like you know like the metal trailers that people like kind of round like and the 50s or
Whatever they have that, but it's a yellow one. There's not a trailer. It's like, you know a truck or whatever
Yeah, and then there were what used to be a restaurant
I forget the name of it too, but they would cloud your ass when you go on there, too
That's it was I love that place
Or shit, yeah, that's Dix it was fun. Yeah, the one where they were classrooms and they talked shit about you
I think that's the rest of your top up. Hey, the rest
I'm a very straight man
No
No, I think it was trash
And their
Roasting wasn't that good. I didn't like the hat because it looked like a KKK Klan mask
I
Didn't like white girls in there, and I did fuck her which is cool
Yeah, you got something out of it I guess
Yeah, it was alright
The hot dogs window, it's a bunch of odor black ladies that do it.
The one that I'm talking about where they like, they're funny,
they're from the south side.
There's just some OG black chicks that like they just, they go crazy.
The worst crowd is just like, it was funny.
Good loader, that's a machination, show proof.
That's a lie.
What did I?
where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where do I where
Yeah, that's weird like I don't know. I don't want somebody would joke about something like that
You know, like I've said some foul shit. I might talk about somebody dead parents or you know to say some stupid shit
But like I ain't great talk about no shit like that
No, nothing like a violation
Nothing that if I was in jail and I said out loud, I get beat the fuck up or violated
Yeah, watch yourself
But these little fake motherfuckers on YouTube, they don't really give a fuck they just say everything they've never been in trouble
They've never actually been in a real world. They are like a goryphobic never went through shit
Bunch of weirdos
Yeah, yeah
You was popping off at one of my homies summer and I didn't appreciate it
My boy DSE
It was like two days ago, you probably didn't even realize it it was like he was arguing with that fucking oh
I'm gonna set it on psychies
The panel Rewinder Alex
Oh, yeah. Well, I mean, I don't remember it and he probably I was part of the soccer since so
Oh, yeah, you were you were you were you didn't you didn't like go too hard, but I was like damn
She's defending this motherfucker. I honestly I'm so happy Alex is I don't know if he's gone or what's going on with him
But goddamn
He's banned
Just turn his mic down psyche. It'd be okay, but no
Every single time and it's sex and you know like I've had I've known Alex for a very very long time
But it just also a point like I got tired to making excuses and I got tired of him every time like I have your back
24-7 and you're like the most toxic person on the fuck alive, but I still had his back
And I just he always threw me under the bus. I'm just like dude. I could fuck with you
But I ain't got to fuck with you
Like I'm just over you know what I mean
Yeah, no, he's the absolute worst he ruins panels
Horribly, it's like it's so crazy like I never seen anything like it
It's too loud though, that's the thing he's he does that he yeah, I know
Like my wife it might be loud, but I try not to interrupt as much and Alex. He's just like
And then he makes psyche paranoid he's like they're trying to get you psyche they're trying to get you
They're gonna get you psyche. I know these discord people. They're gonna get you
It's like bro. Get your skit so paranoid ass out of here dog. What the fuck you talking about fam?
No, I get it because niggas gonna be out here trying to bomb psyche. I get it. Trust me psyche. I yeah, yeah, I
Get it. No, not everybody is a fucking op and Alex is trying to make you into like a
Dibra, yeah, he just wants to run the channel and be a little yag
Yeah
It's like I've known for a long time and and when Alex is cool Alex is cool as fuck man
He's really cool fuck, but I think he's making excuses
But I'm not gonna have I'm just not gonna continue to be thrown on the bus like I'm an asshole
It's not I can hold my own but at the same time. It's just like you fuck. You know what I mean?
so
TPP a gulander. What's TPP?
That's where yeah, we we we were from there
All of us are from over there. I got banned
But this was like last year. I would pop up randomly drunk as shit. I don't know anybody over there
I would just panel surf and they would always be streaming
Yeah, yeah, I was probably I've I've probably talked some shit to you
I've never spoke to you before I know that for a fact
I can't even remember anybody over there
No Christine was over there
Yep. Yeah, Christina's room over there. Yeah, all of us were over there one point in time
But the thing is it's like Eli his egos so fucking stupid and when he's you know, when you call him on his bullshit
He'll start blocking you or you know, if he if he feels like you're getting too much attention than he is
He'll block you and they'll be like, oh, no, this is people podcast
This is freedom of speech line ass bitch ass motherfucker. Every chance I get I wrote it ass. I can't stand that motherfucker
Shout out my homie freesad
Freestyle, what the fuck you be doing to Kate? Why does Kate hate you and baby Ferrari? I wouldn't ask summer for her fucking snapchat
I'm not a weirdo that tries to get shit from YouTube people motherfucker. I don't have a
Ferrari stalks me
Followed me into a bar and told them that he's hacking their Wi-Fi. Oh
shit
He he stalked me while I was doing IRL and followed me everywhere I went
But yeah, I'm not invasive. I don't try to get you to pussy as people try to do
I'm not a I'm not a I'm fine in the real world. I'm fine with where I'm at
Well, that's good. It's thirsty motherfucker the horse. Oh, you have no idea girl. This shit is crazy
Motherfucker. Oh, yeah. Yeah, you're a woman. So yeah, you definitely got an idea and you got pink hair and shit. Yeah
Well
Your hair is naturally pink
Didn't you have pink hair? I did I had red hair actually, but I took it dark for a little bit
Exiles here exiles, what's up?
Oh, it's pop what you doing over here sage. I know you come over here
I
Always come to psychies I come to psychies when psychies live and I'm feeling
Was a little bit I got to know you a little bit, so you're pretty cool Joe Joe you're talking some shit Joe
You want you mean a spank spanky?
Ferrari I'm bigger than you nigga. What the fuck you mean my little buddy Ferrari such your ass up
My buddy, you know my buddy like you're like 511 boy. I'm bigger than you. I'm not your little buddy
Motherfucker if anything, I'm your big buddy
This is a hillbilly. You're my you're my little buddy. You're my little buddy for sake. I'm taller than you
You know, I'm much bigger than you. I'm six three. I'm six three and
220 pounds
Can't do Monchou. Thank you. You have a membership here. Welcome. Thank you for coming and hi
Actually, I might be to 20 this week. I've been eating well
Yeah, can I see a nude photo?
Exile
Psychic
I'm a married man. He's married. I want to say
Are you married? Okay. Yep. Do you guys want my new photo? Nope. No, I think you're my speed my American flag speedo
I very much believe in
I believe in emotional cheating I would not have mostly cheat on my wife
Okay, okay, but during the mail the speed of it was fucking comedy
You was here for that hell. No, no, no, no, no, he hopped on a random panel. He was like, hey
There's good
Fourth of July came early this year. It was a goddamn American flag speed up
Which this shit was fuck he had a smile on his face and shit. I was like, oh, what the fuck's he about to do
Yeah, thank you fucking hilarious and I feel like people just don't really see it because all the bullshit that happens on his panel
But this thing is comedy
Thank you easy easy about me the speedos and so it's all it's all you know all the things go to easy
Easy cameras on
Order me that's you know
Thank you easy
Hey, Sage is
Married to a number of Becky of in the boots with fur clones at any given time Becky in the boots for who's that?
Your wife is that your wife?
No, I'm not white. Say no that your wife saves your man. No, my wife is not white. Is your girlfriend in Becky?
No
Becky I just
Don't tell me talk. What do you mean guy? What do you mean bet? I like I enjoy white women. Have you ever been with a man?
No, no, not one. Actually, it's a stupid ass question. Nevermind. I don't I don't want to hear a joke
You haven't got to answer that psyche
Okay, but no, I've not been with a man
Don't plan to be with a man. I don't play
The thing I like it might happen it might happen man
I like pussy. I like titties. I like soft skin. I like ass. I like long hair
No hair on the body. I like my women. Yeah, I like titties ass. I like to feel a pussy
It's amazing
like
fucking skinless or hairless faces
Skinless? Hold on, how do you say it? Have you met Flirty Diamond?
Bro, yes, I've seen her girthy ass. I'm good.
So you're interested? You like to be like a date? No, no.
A little bit too bulky. They said she built like a linebacker, bro.
Yeah, she's a pretty hefty. I would send her
to attack a woman. I'm like, Flirty, I need you to be an enforcer.
This bitch owes me money. Go get her.
and yeah, Ferti would probably hit a woman because she thinks she's a or he thinks she's a woman or whatever the fuck the
Flirty got lying back her shoulders. She's not yeah, she could wear a suit
As I do want to get you you would date today pretty diamond I can hook you up
The flirty diamond can fill out a suit without shoulder pads.
He's a fucking bitch.
My wife is absolutely gorgeous.
I think I talked to your wife on the panel.
Ironically enough.
You're a dark-scanned lady.
Yeah, but she was like, I'm actually married.
And I was like, who's this like, Zalblen?
I was like, that nigga's a white racist.
She was like, no way.
You wasted no.
This is back when I didn't really know you back when he was with T fuck. I'd yeah, this was wow. It's probably like
Finder I was one of the motherfucking trolling truth finder and what fuck said we couldn't find his docs
We had his docs in 12 minutes first time. Yeah, they ever got docs
Yeah
who's dying
He's talking that wrong shit. We just got this dude named came
How how you say a name?
Coretta, however, fuck you say his name and motherfuckers sit there and try to deny
It's his not Docs when his middle name is came well fuck it
He clicked on the wrong link
Oh hell yeah. All right y'all. I'm about to go
Jump off nice talking to y'all deuces
Psycho say this is I have a crush on you. I have a crush on you
You don't even know what I actually you do know what I look like. You're great. You're great, right?
Are you this is great?
Yeah, that works. Okay, great. Come come nice talking to you psyche. Good night. Good night. Summer you guys have a fantastic night
And yeah, keep the content rolling deuces. Yeah, I am
Bye
How are you guys doing? We have summer and exiled one up here. How are you guys doing doing?
I just got through fucking with a live
But my drama was that I started in a shit show being transferred over to another show to the
Chroma community
So yeah
Good we go
Here you go guys come on up. It's a hi to summer and exile one of myself
It's a friendly chat
It's that we're 29 people in the chat by the way pretty good. Come on guys come say hi
I still have a have a
Macaroon she sandwiched that green sandwich really good, but I had to catch up. I need to catch up
Hey, you're over here. I'm trying to say hi
Tricks for me saying hi to everybody. He wants that you're there. Okay. Oh
Bye bye summer. I
That's mr. Tricks by by summer. Thank you for coming
Don't know much. You have a busy night. I want to stay busy. Yeah summer is busy
You know, so who's in high school gulander
You know
How she manages it well, you know, it's like
She's a power, you know women are very powerful they can get things done
Well, yeah, she's definitely got to be very organized for sure
Okay, I like it. We're I have one more big hit of
This will be the last one or my criminal come over and I'll be for a while longer, but
The guy they got you guys
So how many strength did you have to do today psyche? I'm not many. I don't think I have poor bummed at all
Maybe like attempted
But pretty good
I'm doing okay, like
You know for all the
Damage people tried to do
Hey, nothing too bad. It's
come back with her madness.
Yeah, I know. I'm saying it.
I haven't seen her since this
morning, but, um, you know, she
was really, uh, pretty kind and,
uh, you know, you never know
It's not a Christine fan, I guess, but oh, yeah, she's definitely a roller coaster ride. That's for sure
This is funny, you know, it's like, you know, it's all there's all sorts of people here
You don't know it with anything about
I'm liking the cast of characters though
What you got in there
Sativa Indica
It was like I'm probably mixed hallelujah. Yeah, I hit like folks. Yeah. Yeah, I mean
Crystal, you know, it's she's funny. You know, it's like, you know, and I have a good cast of characters
I do I have like my own whack pack
but
You know, I'm gonna be a little bit kinder about it because I'm probably I probably I should probably be in black pack, too
I'm just I'm just as bad as anybody else. Not bad or bad. That is good. Better good
But you know, like I like the eccentric eccentric people in the world. You make the world go around
for an exiled one. Yeah
You know eccentric people or let's go down in your neck of the woods
I don't know, but you know, you know, it's an eccentric people.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Besides me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's like the porn thing is you know be kind of people usually they don't deserve it be kind
Because you know all these communities to gather
Well, I'm gonna say cast them out of the garden. Well, would I even work, you know?
Yeah. Yeah, it works
This is the years in our community
It works, but there's all but there's always gonna be more bad apples coming in right is that we're gonna do you want
Oh, you know, you don't want them all to be gone when the entertainment's gone
Maybe discovery of people and their personalities that that's part of the fun of this shit, right?
It is but you know also
You know
Human beings are a lot of things you can be a lot of things about a lot of people
But it didn't go to the core of the human the core of the person
Are they someone that wants to hurt people someone wants to help people someone that's
Vendictive someone that's malicious or someone that's as a kind
Forgiving soul, you know people can also change people can also change for the better
Is it true in other certain people that you know statistically depending on their psychological issues they don't change
Well, you know, it doesn't get harder to change as you get older if you have these ingrained patterns
but if there if you have a desire to change you can you have it if you have a
Vision of being a better person you can get to that I believe
You know what the outside circumstances if we you know, if we maintain our love for ourselves if we maintain a healthy conscience
You know telling us what right? It's a little Jiminy cricket little cricket. What's right and wrong?
Angel the devil in your shoulders
Always giving you advice
Has everyone doing you see I just finish all
I'm a firm believer that some people have empty shells
That they're just empty shells. I'm a firm believer in that
Not many of them out there, but there is some
Yeah, I mean there's some because I mean they're called kind of walk-ins like people that have
Totally abandoned their body. They totally abandoned their morality to totally banning and then like an angel comes in and like takes over in the
For the body the rest of life. Maybe maybe the angel will have to do us some shit because
Why that fucking other angel that was inhabiting the body really fucked up and
But you know what?
We're doing it we're doing we got it figured out, you know
People that are violent people that are doing things actual crimes actual physical assault actual
You know larceny ceiling burglary these people are getting punished
They're learning a lesson and
Maybe they'll want to do it again
Hopefully hopefully they like a lesson
Yeah, well criminal justice is a very uh
It's pretty harsh, you know the jails aren't bringing I've been to a jail for a few days
No, but it is a good lesson. Yeah, and I said I'd never work back there again. I won't you know
See how would you go to jail for disorderly conduct or something stupid like that?
It was the possession charge and the possession charge nowadays will would be
Maybe
It would be there would you they wouldn't even book me that me by my last possession offense
I was arrested for like putting put in custody for six hours or maybe three hours out
But I did my community service
Sent on your way
Yeah, well no, no, you they took me to the
detox
Not the detox, but I
Could do community service. I was like I'll take the jail time
This is probably said three days in jail. Let me spend four. It was adjourned. It was a it was a journey
But I was like I never go back here again, but it was fun. I finally I had my first boyfriend. I had
Yeah, I had a great shower with everybody. I'm kidding. I'm kidding, but I'm not kidding.
You met him in jail?
My first boyfriend? Oh, actually, no. There's a guy in the jail that was very...
He was you know, he's a peckerwood, you know peckerwoods. I was very skinny. Everyone's everyone's very nice
I also was everyone's very nice. I didn't have sex in Jeff. I just
That's very nice people. You know Jamie's cowboys and chat exile. You know, Jamie's cowboys. Yeah, Jamie's cowboys
He was cowboys down here. Hi. Oh good night
She's a cowboys fan
Hellbilly hellbilly good night and loser. Good night. Hey everybody come on in
I don't know
Hey, Jamie
I mean today
These people make these AI photos of the guy. I wish I look if I look like this. I'd be so happy
There's one here. Oh
Some good-looking I am
All the outfits
Oh, that's my basketball. I was in basketball
And that great guy the kind of hand though that that kind of it that there's the hair
Yeah, I think they I did awesome on that
Yeah, it's pretty good
So you got my hair down. Oh good night loser
Let oh, I look the tuxedo. How much did you pay for the zombie bomb that you got?
Oh, I've had nothing because um easy um easy um purchase it for me sponsored that bomb
So thank you easy. Here's the zombie ball
Yeah, he's a nice guy, you know, he catches a lot of shit for what he did to Eli
Yeah, you know what it's like I hear
Piece of shit that acts like he's a gangster. So if he's gonna add gangster
He might as well get a taste of the gangster life, I guess
I just, I don't know if he's listening, but I have people saying, oh, easy to this, easy to that, he did it or didn't do it, you know, I believe in forgiveness, redemption, and judgment.
Oh, he did it. I got the film of him doing it.
Oh, he did. I know, okay.
Well, he did it and, you know, easy. I'm sure it was self-defense. I'm sure he thought there was another option. But he did it.
Well, I mean, I would see it as you know, it was easy knows how I feel about it that it was a pussy move to bring a knife out in the fist fight.
And you know, I mean, depending on what the state of New York thinks about it, it could very well be a defense case. I don't know.
That depends on his defense attorney and the prosecuting attorney how that turns out.
Yeah, well
You know, I got I got easy's back you had my back in you know, I'm never gonna tell you see
I said, you know, I'll judge you by a part not by the action that he made
He's a good dude
He just made a stupid stupid fucking decision
well, I
Can everyone relate to that have we ever made it like a stupid mistake?
I wish we could take back.
Yeah, but never in a fucking camera.
Never on camera.
On camera too.
That's the thing about streamers.
They're cameras on.
A lot of streamers are like,
they show everything.
Benny Blanco hit his mom.
Back in my day, you had to turn
that camera off or you was
bitch.
We were catching that somewhere
where you didn't have a camera.
Even a camera now is that you know you can't believe what you see because
Images can be manipulated
There can be other agendas there could be it's just like so easy to like
If you if someone's targeted, it's so easy to like produce a million fake things about that
I mean it's like and people will just believe them that you distributed it persons helpless to it. So
No, so son waver you can't throw me in jail type shit
Shit, I fight a motherfuckin in but you know as far as these motherfuckers going out there and just filming it
Shit, stay and pick up a case on your ass in some places and neither one of y'all got a choice in this shit
So I ain't fucking around
I enjoyed my freedom
Yeah
We have freedom here and it's like but we also have privacy and so you know if art
So far freedoms are a truth upon
You know
That's a whole other case that can be made. You know, it's like
We should have freedom we should have
Very transparent dude, you know what I'm saying? I don't care about privacy at all, but
You know other than when I'm in my nudity with shit here. I mean
As far as you know, like we're talking about easy as far as his right to a fair trial
I feel like he deserves that
Yeah, and that and whatever the trial is if you sound guilty he'll serve time and then
We'll come out time served
Are we supposed to be
He'll be able to survive in there. He just got it. He got to work on his you know, how can I say man your reasons of being too hyper?
Just hyper I'll just put that I don't think you and I don't think you I don't think you'll go to prison
I don't think you go to prison. I think it's a big misunderstanding or a self-defense or something. I
See his heart and he's fine
But we know what happens
That's New York a lot of people die by stabbing in New York
They might have a zero tolerance see on that I said we don't know the laws like he know them laws
Yeah, easy like you know the laws. I mean, yeah, I'm the same way, you know
Like I like him, you know, lots of me broken long ago get caught but
Why break them anyway
We like to test the judicial system
So as is macaroni and to say I heard of macaroni and cheese grilled cheese macaroni and cheese
I'm going to go on cheese. What it's not going to grill to you sound
I'll do it. I'll do it. Hold on. Oh, it's kind of
It's a macaroni
I asked you it looks pretty fire. What do they do they deep fried it? I was a deep fry
It's just some sourdough bread grilled. That's some sourdough bread. It's like not too
Too badly grilled
Hey ninja with the pencil. What's that? That's good
Yeah, it's the A-Side one, you want to come up on the panel, I'll have it in a few bites.
Since it was a Penn State it seems Cowboys hold it down.
Minions don't hit panels too often, but he might hit it.
I like the dude, that dude's pretty fucking chill, man.
He gets out the algorithm of his little community, he's fine.
Charisma, I don't know the story. I don't know the story. I don't know if I want to know
What story is that?
But easy it says we she went to see went to someone's private home
Pull weapons and self-defense. I'm not sure. I just don't know. I
Don't think he unalived anybody. I don't think anybody's
Eli still alive
We know he's a good guy. Yeah, that's back
Hey everybody has everybody doing tonight, I don't know
And I thought that ignorant ass motherfucker refused treatment at the first hospital because he was still acting stupid when he arrived there
I'll stab the fuck up
Wow
Hey, you know, Jamie's holding it down the chat. Thank you, Jamie
Everybody here with 17 people in the chat. Why is everyone so quiet? Everyone's always so quiet
Guys, we got a bill of this channel. We got yeah, probably 15 memberships
New memberships in the past couple of days
Thank you guys so much. There's Jamie
Your new Cowboys photo Jamie the new Cowboys Jamie loves the Cowboys
now I agree I agree with her though I mean like self-defense it's just gonna be
a hard argument to it are you a self-defense when the other person
didn't have a weapon yeah that's totally easy
Well, I mean, there's like, you know, there's states where you, you know
If you if you see someone on your property, you can shoot
I really don't think New York will be one of those with all the stabbing with New York has because it destroyed gun laws
Yeah
And yeah, some states, you know, you're not even allowed to
Defend your property some states you can shoot on site. I mean the Texas you could they have like
But in some states, you know, if you've had a case with a intruder, he filled up the person's roof and broke his back or something like that and sued the homeowner.
And he was robbing the house, you know.
There was a farmer that shot an intruder in, I think Nebraska and the motherfucker got outside the front doorway of his house and he sued the owner.
Yep.
Yeah.
Oh, we have a guest.
Hold on.
Who's this Alexander McQueen don't want to know me don't want to know me. That's only one
of all the way you'll think this is somebody else that you popped out what would I do to psyche if I pull his ass over
you're like me Alex you don't like me anymore you think I'm a spoiled brat and like
yes yes I think you're spoiled brat and you gotta clean the crib I hate you
I know I'm cleaning it Alex people are helping me
well I heard you had a vacuum and some senorita coming but I still don't see no vacuuming going on
but that's not why I came up my man
I came up because what the fuck you guys talking about easy for
And I wanna like no, no, I'm talking eggs out. Oh, okay
What trial
What that shit is done, it's under the rug it's bye bye that shit is
No one what he told him a trial my man
No one press charges. There is no trial.
Oh, okay. Well, shit. That's what's up. I didn't know.
That's what's up.
Okay, so everybody stop.
Yeah.
The kid was drunk one night and had a fight
and did some retarded shit for two seconds.
Shut up. Everyone shut the fuck up.
But they you guys we love easy and work
How we ever gonna move on when you talk about some past me
Let me guess what you've done extra on your life
Let's let me hear your life story. So I'm sure you did probably worse than easy
That have done things that we can even found them
Так, а вы что-то пока обыщем бьёдень, так что не думаете?
I was saying he was a good dude, and he deserves a second chance and he deserves a fair chance
Yeah, we all got that already months ago
Assumption that he was still fucking pressing charges against easy. I didn't know he dropped
You think he like cares about that shit. Don't you see him?
The lives just got deleted. He's opening up a new studio. You think he has
Press charges the night it happened
Do you never remember he said I'm not pressing charges tonight. It happened. Do you never remember Eli leaving the hospital on his own accord?
Like I'm out. Do you remember him ripping the IV's out of his arms and saying I'm out of here?
And I'm not pressing charges so everyone what the fuck?
That shit is crazy stop talking about that bull. Hey, it's a sometimes picks up charges jackass
It's been a year later. I guess the state has bigger things to do
Alex you don't like me anymore
No, none until you put gel in the hair
they'd have been a kid he said to all
vacuum, see vacuuming
and
well as tricks me out so much tonight
But then I stumbled upon and I'm like he's laughing and then I heard you guys told him I did shit
And that should just made my blood boil, bro
All right, it's dropped next subject man
I gotta go I gotta go have a great night guys. Bye
Jesus
Alice has never said I got it. Oh, he said I got to go with that awesome. He usually never says I got to go
Alice is usually
We're down to hang next time to make sure complaints to the complaint department that will be found in the discord
Sir, it's good. You know me in discord. I'll see the message, but I might not reply
But that's how the complaint department works
Play department is a play of our it's like a box
You know box it with a slot you put it in the box. There's a candle burning it burns all the complaint
They're not red because it can't take any more complaints about my show
Yeah, every once in a while one slips through the box and that's it
Well
Hopefully things will work out. Let's see. How's everyone doing tonight? Come on. What's up money for 20 in one?
Come on the panel come chat
I'm seeing it. I don't know. Maybe maybe you have a friend might come over help me clean some a little bit
But otherwise I'm hanging out a couple more hard lemonade, but I think two is enough
I like my cruelty sandwich and doing readings. What's up, Jamie? What's up? It's a beyond
Exiles
Charisma so exiled so what exiled so you've been like what it what is exile exile means you've been kicked out of somewhere or what?
No, it's my game in community
Just look it up is it's called exile game. It's a game in community
It's out of the game is it is a certain game is a game in community. Okay, so you're a gamer
Used to be
Stop doing this shit a few years back turn this shit into a troll account
Are you trolling me?
No fuck no
No, you wouldn't do that. No, you you got others to come on your show that I like to show
You and honesty, right?
Well, who else Alice come back. Oh
Sometimes it just depends on the person's personality temper mood
Yeah
What's up?
You know, I think
I think as long as people are
You know, there's no harm to their people
There's loving intentions. No, so I didn't know doxing
Miss wanting to doxing
Now I'm here for the emotional reactions
Yeah
You're gonna see I think you're just happy to see the XL ones here. I'm happy
I'm gonna draw XL ones. I have a pen. Okay, I'm gonna draw you. Okay
All right, I'm just gonna draw you. I'm gonna draw you. What kind of recording to your picture. Let me see
Okay, let me see
Okay, I'm doing pretty good so far, okay, okay
Okay.
Excel.
Oh, let me see, X.
Okay, I'm doing special for you.
X.
Yeah, this will help you with your artwork. My buddy did this for me with my avatar. My buddy Daria
Okay, well, I don't think I did that well
Is it good
The I like it. Yeah. Yeah
I don't know
Letter, but I didn't even know you had the one with the glass hole. This is cool. I
Even know it was gonna be that I was drawing it
To that and I know time for you my friend Daria six at a world did that one for me
Like that Jamie. Yeah, that was cool because it was like you didn't tell me that it was I or I was like I just
Yeah, I was like I was like it needs a face
You know you should be wearing it in the face in there, but I was like just cuz I see the letter I was like
There's a portrait, but
That's why I should run the dark glasses on the yeah, you like Daria. I love I love the fit of Daria
I was a fan of Daria. I'm an 80s baby. So Daria was like, you know, they're probably my teens
She did his avatar for me. She in our
Yeah, cool
La la la la, this is my
Okay
Lesson diarrhea, but yeah
So
I was exiled. Everyone come up 24-20. Just try tonight. Come on.
This is my stuff time to get out
You're standing on my face that way how it goes. Oh
No, I'm neck. You're standing on my neck
I don't know it. I was like, yeah, I got a lot of channels that follow so I'm probably about to bounce to another one
I think dude
If I say I say offer somebody a free reading to come up. You might get somebody to come up
Okay. Hey, everyone who ever comes up next is a free reading
Up
He loved me all along
Alice come back
Don't you know you got a hold of me. I
Was found and I just can't live without you
Okay, let's see
Money for 20 you wanted drawing of yourself, huh?
I can't really see him that well, but I can
Improvise some of your sprints here many for 20
Many 420 are you there? I
Drew you I don't know if it's a good one
Maybe 420
To zero look okay
Off and my on
Mr. Money for 20
So it's going crazy guys I have more coffee that is cold
Cold coffee and more beers. I'll drink some coffee. I try to save
It's oh so quiet man, I remember I had like 50 people in the chat everyone's like oh well
Everybody's going back and forth people come on the panel. I know what's going on the panel
What's the chat? No one's even chatting. There's a little eight. Oh here now. It's a people. Okay
Want want want my girl runs right when they say I'm just a big failure
That's good, where's everyone going? Everyone's leaving me?
Told the band to be.
Hello? Anybody out there? Anybody here? Hello guys. Say hi to me.
I'm just kidding.
Hi, y'all. Good to see you.
And it's a fun
Anybody
I'm gonna talk about anything or any questions. Hey, I psyche I psyche hour
They ask me anything
Call me anything
Oh excuse me. I've seen someone here.
Hi, Sponky. Sponky's cool as hell.
hi guys i think it's good in life to have a positive outlook you love me thank you
i think but i think you should everyone should have a positive outlook where
i mean there's so many things in the future that can be scary how's my day going it's pretty good
it's been nice i had a nice um cleansing bath a friend coming over helping me get everything
Clean and organized. It's like, you know, yeah
And even people sometimes people that even think don't like you
Actually do like you and I want to help and like, you know
Sometimes some people have a a little bit of a it sounds
Yeah, oh my gosh. I got a macaroni and she grilled she sandwich and shuffle the cars
This is stop to see what comes up. Yeah, yeah
So you say stop? Yeah
But it might be a delay because I might see you and but whenever it's but whatever supposed to happen will happen
Okay, yeah, I'm shot. She'll put in the car. Do you tell me when to say stop?
There were cars on top
We're on top
Yeah, it was a grilled cheese sandwich place. It's like a macaroni and grilled cheese sandwich
as
Stop. Oh
You got the mystery
Dancing to the mystery
Okay, so this is like a high priestess card
This is the high priestess. It's the Cheshire cat Cheshire cat has Cheshire cat knows everything right Cheshire cat
Knows everything and that's why he's smiling because he has all these all those knowledge. We can't really
Share everything like it is. Yes
riddle and stuff like that, but it's a high priestess card normally, right? It says,
the mystery represents wisdom, intuition, and the subconscious. The card, like the Cheshire Cat,
carries the message that things aren't always as they seem.
The mystery advises you not to take anything at face value.
Dig deeper, use your intuition to discover
what's really going on under the surface.
Take time to consider situations from new perspectives.
You may discover that the challenges you're perceiving
aren't really there at all.
One for you?
Okay, so your taco show?
Okay, I'm shuffling, just tell me,
say stop when you want me to stop, okay.
Taco she'll just type stop get cars for everyone tonight
I'm sorry. I haven't been doing it. You know, I shouldn't be promoting my carburetines more, but
Okay, oh stop. Oh, okay
This is okay
Say okay
So this is the pair. It's sweedledy tweedledum
It's the pair is similar state. It's also the lover's card. Okay?
so a perfect match with somebody
like you have a perfect twin or some kind of
You see
Lovers car so it says the lovers, you know the pay of the pair
Tweet-a-dee, Tweet-a-dum are harmonious and completely in sync with each other.
The pair represents partnership, friendship, or collaboration.
It is effortless, united, and congruous as the bond between Tweet-a-dee and Tweet-a-dum.
The pair represents a harmonious union.
The tarot card also carries an element of choice.
Even the best friendships and partnerships take work to maintain.
Will you choose to nurture the connections you value the most?
Are any adjustments needed in these relationships?
Check in with yourself and communicate what's on your mind openly.
There we go guys.
How was that?
I hope you liked that.
Yeah, I like that lover's card. It's like, you know, usually it's the divine union sometimes
There's somebody in the background
Try me trying to interfere so
But if it's meant to be that that one's a really good lovers card think I thank you, I it is beautiful
Thank you so much for having a reading
Yeah, guys, I have a really a few decks of fairy books
Here to hang out
Don't be said
Yeah, that's been too big but this big I was banned from the show
But you know what I ban Alex and I had Alex back. He was nice. He'd be here. I'm so I like him
You know, I don't know if he apologized me. Do you apologize? No
People are leaving oh gosh
Let's see. Who can I draw? Let's see if y'all want to card or
Didn't money for 20
Glander
Hey Glander knows. Yeah, somebody yeah
Goulana I just have these lovely ladies coming over. You need to apologize. You can draw a card. Yeah, of course
Spunky here you go this one up
Night of hedgehogs
Did I get this for you before I?
Almost remember did I get this for you? Yeah, I got this again
This is like so let's just interpret it like it is let's look at the car, okay?
He's all like a little gondola
You keep getting this yeah, just night it says not a pinnacle's not a pinnacle's there to chill
He's there to he sees bringing his overnight bag
He's here. He's not a pinnacle's comes. He's there for a little bit. You know, he's he's uh, he's coming for a stay
Isn't yeah, that is so weird
All the cards, you know
So I don't know
Are you getting a rep or reptilian?
He might as you're getting a reptilian. I don't know, but he might have that
You may have some reptilian qualities, but like he's coming for his stay. This is a guy. He's he comes with some gifts. He
He's out on business. He's out here working on business and some of the time it comes back with a lot of cool stuff
You got you got some swords. Hey Joe, and come on. Okay. I'll get some more cards for you
Spokes for you for you a punk punky because
This is awesome. First, uh, what else we got for punky? Oh
Nine of T cups
Okay, nine. Okay, nine is the hermit
They kind of like some kind of like recharging
I don't think you're doing it on your own, but Nine of Cups is also some somebody you got you got all this happiness
You you're like guarding it. You're sitting there guarding it
You're like no one's gonna know it's gonna serve my happiness. It says the Nine of Cups is a positive sign of successful outcome
Luck is on your side. Your wish has been granted things are finally going your way
Stay in the present moment to fully enjoy the ease and comfort of this wonderful time
You're gonna go to hermit. Yep. It's kind of it's kind of like, you know
Didn't didn't tie that into the hermit on this on this in this book, but I see that it says
You know stay in the present moment enjoy the ease and cover the wonderful time. So I
say
Yeah, it's been some time doing self-care
Okay, oh night of flowers another night
Never got these guys before look at okay, so is that home? Who's a guy a burdo that burdo right there? You know this night of flowers, okay?
There's some flowers
They have this like auditory or
Vocal talents night of flowers that flowers is gonna be the ones
Yeah, oh yeah, watch out for this guy watch out for this guy
That's I don't know who this is
The Knight of Flowers represents a fiery, passionate,
and temperamental person.
One moment, he's sociable and enjoyable.
Next moment, he may be dumping rainwater on your head
and chasing you out of his garden.
Take inspiration from the action-oriented nature.
Knight of Flowers is decided to actively pursue your interests
and put meaningful momentum behind your goals.
Yep.
So you have to you mean you have to decide what that means for you is it it's when you know or is it you know
Didn't need to be action-oriented
Get out there and get some stuff done, but
It's about Justin yeah, okay, cool
Sounds like it. Let's see what here's a word of advice here. Let's do a advice card. You're so cool. Oh three heads out collaborate
This is a collaborate
this is like also somebody has been like seeing your work and it's like oh like look
let's let's uh let's go let's go check her oh yeah hold on so uh three pinnacles this is like
collaboration someone wants to work with you someone wants to work with you so it might be you
and you and your boyfriend and somebody else is wanting to come in and say hey we have a good
Hello
You me
Yes
Hi, thanks for coming tonight. How are you?
Oh good. How are you? This is my first time
It's your first time. I've seen I've seen you on beat his show the before
How are you?
I'm good. How'd you find the show?
Someone mentioned your channel
And then I tried to hang.
Yeah, that's better.
Gunda.
Welcome, Smaki.
You, too.
You know, you don't have to do what you want to do.
Wow.
Yumi, where are you?
What country?
Oh, she, I think she muted.
She muted.
you see Yumi cat you see the Yumi cats hey I've seen Yumi on betas I think she's from
hey you Yumi where are you from Indonesia Indonesia yes Indonesia okay so you're
you're so you're in Indonesia you're just talking you're talking to your family
Sorry, I talked to my students. I'm still working it's okay
Yeah, do you mean you did you like tarot cards?
Pardon tarot cards tarot
Yeah, you mean you're reading
Yeah, I know about about it
Okay, you know you know Alice in Wonderland
Okay, okay, you me tell me when to stop okay say stop okay
Stop
Okay, so you got the seven of tea cups, okay?
So, seven of tea cups, what this means is that you have a lot of things that you might
want and you have a lot of options presented in front of you and it looks so confusing.
You're like, what do I really want?
Because there's many options available to you right now and this track is gifted aside
You're welcome, it's it.
The good about I'll tell you I'm gonna read you from the book
It says seven of teacups asked you to take inspiration from Alice and dream
Allow your imagination to wander daydreaming can be a powerful act of
Manifestation and form the framework for your future goals and actions tap into your intuition
Let your mind wander who knows what wonderful adventures your dreams will take
you on. Thank you. Thank you. Yes. So just like, just dream, you know, it's, it's like what, and
decide what, you know, whatever you want, you know, you can achieve it. This is the,
this is a world with all these options and all these possibilities, and so many, whatever you're
interested in, there's something to represent it. Yeah, I have a...
I'm responsible with my students right now, and I'm sorry if some of them want to see
while we're talking.
Oh, it's okay.
Concentrate on your class, or I think you're teaching your class with students.
Yeah.
Awesome.
We have Yumi from Indonesia.
Stop and buy.
Anyone who will come up on the panel, everyone's welcome.
You know, there's no nobody's band right now. Everybody's everybody's cool
What makes you can I ask you some one? Yeah
What makes you like to do a do a like a reading that card those cards
Writing the cards. Yeah. Well, it's just because I found tarot to be very good way to
Discover more about people, help them learn some things about themselves, to learn about yourself, there's beautiful symbolism, it's very interesting, and I think it's very accurate, and you know, even if you just take it for entertainment or you take it very seriously for advice about your life, I think you're going to find some things that will help you and you'll find
synchronous synchronicities or I don't you'll just find you'll get the right
message at the right time because it always messages coming is there many
kind of kind of pattern cultures just
Many kinds. Yeah. Well, there's many designs of decks, you know, there's different styles
But there's a basic layout of the deck and there's also different kinds of cards
They're kind of like Oracle cards or different style decks, but the the the main tarot has like usually 78 cards at 22
22 of the major cards and then
Like 55 of the
You can also use playing cards to do readings and
Some students like to play, you know, you know, you know, you know cards
You know cars have a Pokemon like Pokemon
No, you know cars like
Oh, yeah, I know you know it's a game who knows the game. I just yeah
Like that's the big thing this year is Uno
Yeah, so you mean do you know how to do the reverse uno? I
Don't know how to play the uno with some time
I see some students playing in the in the park around the university. Yeah, I work in the university
Hi. Yeah. Oh, hi. Hi. Yeah, it's me
Hi, well, thank you for coming on camera
Hi, CB. Yeah, we're with Yumi. Well, also, you know, my little brother, he taught English
and Korea, and I've been to Thailand and China, but I've never been to Indonesia.
I, you know, I'd love to maybe visit there someday. Yeah, we saw Yumi. I don't think I've
ever seen Yumi come up at she. Thank you, Yumi. That was very nice. Hey, Dingo.
Have a nice conversation and you read the cards for me. That was cool. Yeah
You're welcome. It's pleasure to have you here. Are you subscribed make sure you subscribe and like, you know, oh, you know
You're welcome any time
We have a thing that is in the chat. We have Jamie's cowboy. You know, Jamie's got your people in my chat
Yeah, yeah, someone mentioned your name those
Awakens is live and then okay
And then I like thinking around and there's the ones here yet.
So I try to thank you for letting me out.
Oh, no problem.
Thank you for being here.
It's a pleasure.
You're really cool.
It's awesome to have people from around the world.
Guys, do you know how big the world is?
And we have people from the other side of the world
hanging out.
I mean, it's an American guy in Los Angeles.
Let's see.
Dingle CB thing that is anyone come up. I'm James Cowboys awesome. You're are you so teaching class right now?
Cool what what what grade do you teach?
Or I guess I have different different grade system, so it isn't small world after all Dingle, you know, we're all
All around the world. That's you from before me
Okay, thank you. Thank you so much. Thank you later. Thank you. Have a good day. Thank you. Bye. Oh
How nice what a sweet or sweet lady?
All around the world that she's crumbled for me
I know I love I love you
Everyone
So what are we gonna do guys? How are we doing? You forgot about the song? I know well I had Sugar Ray
When it's over that when it's over
That's the time I'll fall in love again
Every morning there's a headlight ball me on the corner of my car. Oh, I know
Who's quitting cold?
Once again, I predicted that my broken, open heart opened and you ripped it out.
Something so deceiving got me there believing, turn me around again.
I
Mean a great night guys
Probably I don't know if their friends are coming back, you know
So I was gonna try to do my sandwich making that is oh it's more of it. Oh
It's a little bit vinegary.
So, what are we gonna do?
Where do we go from here?
Excuse me. Mm-hmm. Some cheese sauce and dip in there.
Maybe I like the vinegary ketchup, but it's good
Mickey park
Doesn't even matter because you know because we all die, you know no matter what horrible
But we'd have horrible thoughts about the future, but
As long as we're still alive we can change our fate
So when we pass away, we're not one not necessarily here
Maybe we escaped here. Maybe we
Maybe it wasn't at a bad time, but I
Believe in reincarnation. I believe the soul goes on. I believe your consciousness continues thinking about the one human body
Has like a billion
Raised nuclear energy like where does these powerful powerhouses of energy limit this energy?
You can do amazing things. We haven't even figured out what we can do
We're gonna do general yeah
Is it are people here you can do some hoodoo tarot
What the guys want to learn a few cards from the hoodoo
Who does a great deck interesting this is for everybody here
These cars have keys all over them too we are power Dingle
You know what you know, we're more powerful
Even more power when we work together when we they can vibe together when we can
Help people out
What's this ooh six of six?
This is like, you know, it's easy to see this victory six of wands as I got victory coming out of something successfully
There was a test you had some kind of tests that you pass pass successfully
On the white horse
There's people around you and I celebrate and there's something that there's something that went right for right for you recently
Some kind of test that you pass
It says, the plant is called a goat through.
It says, the image, Nat Love, 1854 to 1921,
was one of the greatest cowboys of all time.
Cowboys, right?
He was seen riding into town as a people cheer.
According to Lowe's autobiography, he was badly wounded when he was taken captive by
Pima Indians who eventually nursed him back to his health using herbs.
The Pimas adopted him as member of the tribe.
He escaped captivity on a horse he named Yellow Dog Chief.
The symbol on Yellow Dog Chief depicted here is called the Iamori and represents the Puma
And so it says there's been a positive victory being promoted, overcoming a hardship, receiving
compliments, good news, recognition, having high self-esteem, becoming a VIP,
feeling encouraged, being sought out for your expertise, and being a recognized hero.
One thing I want to have a look on is, see there's that, I think it's that, that right there.
Emotory tribe
Bible said thought was real I think
Thought was done is real
Yeah, well, there's a saying thoughts become things and
The thing about that does there are cool cards. These are called a hoodoo easy
Easy sponsored the cards for me. So thank you easy
But there's a saying thoughts become things and people say what does that mean?
Doesn't mean everything you think will come true
Means you can take things that are thoughts
Turn them into ideas bring them into the world the thoughts can become you bring them to the physical
That's that's what it means thoughts become things. It's a few more you guys are having fun. I
Love you and tarot
Okay manifest things yes
But you think about every invention that's been here or every idea, right?
Everything that's on this world that was first a thought it was first thought so it was like a
Thought came and then the ability to
Manifest okay, so what's this one?
Here's the chariot. So this is called railroad hill
Railroad hill you can see this
There's a train. So this is something called railroad hill. It's a chariot card
So in this book they have it as a railroad, okay
Temperance okay the rail real one
Yeah, what time friends?
Just says her string railroad, okay, so it says the chariot your manifest a billion dollars do it
It's okay. So here's the Psalm it says Psalm 108 it says with God with God we shall do
Radiantly is he will tread down the foes
Valiantly with God we shall do valiantly in this you should try the most
This is mental health problems. What's up 18? What's wrong with you? We're having fun
Who needs help? Who? Who? What are you talking about?
Mr. T? Is that you? So it says the photo the plant is Maka. Maybe we're Maka. Oh
a team
What's a joke yeah, it was a joke okay, so it says the image railroad bill is waving at the people cheering for him at a distance
So it's another victory. So we got the last one is a victory. This is another victory railroad. Okay, so it's a railroad bill
born, we don't know when he was born, but to 1896 was his laborer with no clear
past as his name, place of birth, and many other details about his life or man in
mystery. What we do know is that the authorities claimed he was a man named
Morris Slater. We know the hell he put them through. It all started in 1894.
While Bill was employed as a turpentine worker bluffs brings Florida and after an altercation
he exchanged gunshots with the deputy.
The cause of the row has been lost to time but it was from then on that he became an
outlaw.
Bill committed train robberies and engaged in fatal gun flights with lawmen and bounty
hunters who traveled from all over the country to collect the substantial bounty on his head.
Naturally, the daily reports of a Negro desperado gunning down white men sold a lot of newspapers
and didn't take long before a folk hero akin to Robin who was born.
According to members of the Black communities at the time, Bill said he used his spiritual
powers as a congerment to avoid capture by transforming himself into a fox to throw dogs
off his trail.
He became a personification of the clever trickster who appears in both indigenous American
and African folklore so much of his legend continued to grow well into the 20th century.
There are many songs about Railroad Bill by artists such as Riley Pat Puckett,
Vera Ward Hall, Gid Turner, Gid Tanner, Thomas Dorsey, Will Bennett, Jack Elliott, Bill Williams,
Joan Baez, and others. In 1981, Bill was resurrected and cheered by the working class once again when
the musical play Railroad Bill was produced by NYC's Labor Theater, one that was founded specifically
Meaning, when robo-bill turns up, you're being encouraged to increase your efforts to ensure
victory.
It's a reminder of the characteristics that are required to win confidence, determination,
discipline, persistence, and assertiveness.
Now is the time to adopt and take no prisoners' attitude toward anybody or anything that attempts
to get in your way.
then this car is warning that you might toughen up or risk the loss of what you worked so hard for.
So if you receive railroad build during your reading, consider the following.
If you don't plan to win the game, then why are you playing?
Success is the best revenge. Get rid of any people or situation that are distracting you from your
mission. Now, only self-confidence and strength. A strong will to survive will get you through this.
It's my way or the highway. What competition know thyself to prepare those of
It's called self-esteem for a reason stop waiting for others to cheer you on
Says the dominant domination happens. I'm allergic to humble pie. So if you have it
What is the victorious outcome you seek where there's a will there's a way? Yeah, it's an ego thing. I ain't sorry
You can do it, but will you?
So you know what it's saying
There's gonna be people that tell you you can't do it people that tell you hey
There's no hope. You know, just
Your hopeless despair you might as well just end it all now
People that actually will be sick enough to try to tell you that
You know what?
What was the 99.999999% of what they're telling you is just bullshit
Trying to knock you off your square trying to get you off in your
in your mind
Thinking about it and fearing it and not living your life now because you're worried about some event that may or
It probably will not happen in the future, right?
It's just it's like what what are they psychic no
But what they can do is they can put ideas in your head and you can do self-fulfilling negative prophecies
So we're gonna you're gonna do is make sure you know what you really want
You know, you're safe protected no matter what will happen
Here you'll be protected and
You'll find a way to survive who your survivors. How's everyone in chat doing anyone?
Come on the panel talk. I don't have the link pin. Do I leave pinch?
Well, my phone's almost gone.
See if I can, I'm not depressed.
No, I'm a very lucky person.
I've lived a very happy life.
My life right now is,
it's a dream, it's just a dream.
I don't know if we're better, if we get harder,
but...
Having a good time just live my life
Let's let's do a little fun
See something for fun, and I love you guys. Good luck guys little fun
Congratulations, Tony Peterson MSC
New member of psyches angels recruit is a recruit
Just a little
Something to give back to you guys if you'd like to come on a member of psyches angels. There we go. Hey Justin Boyle
It really does help it really if you appreciate it. I will give you extra cards
Yeah, I think that is as a member. Yeah
So, Justin Boyle, you come up on the panel,
we had some cool people on tonight.
You're always welcome.
JB, Justin and I have the same initials.
So cool dudes.
Also the same initials on the high priestess card.
This is BJ, but it's JB.
Hi, Justin.
I hope you're doing good, dude
If you want a reading tonight, I got a reading for you anybody else want a reading
I'm gonna do a lot more readings now, you know
Don't ever feel shy to ask, you know, I always got a couple cards and you can do a couple cards pretty fast
You want a more detailed reading or private reading you can contact me on discord or Instagram
We're asking in the chat
Everything's good. Everything's good. Just chillin
Sheeters
Well, sheeters is an interesting show, but
Why don't you want to show with more fun?
Now that I've had my show my show had just as much fighting as Jerry Springer
They said readers thing. I've never seen as much fighting on any show. My show is like gonna go in the record books for like
Some of the fucking fights Wow, I mean there's a lot of things that on my show, but
cheaters
There's enough cheaters out there
How about you have a show called faithful, right? You could add Jerry's Springer music to you. Yeah
Copyright struck by Jerry's bringer though, you know
Guys look I got cigarettes tonight
I had a pair I don't have a pack of cigarettes for like for like almost a year
Long time they don't sell switchers anymore switches are gone from the stores now
What the fuck I want to see I want to see someone I know I want to see someone I know come on
We're ran got it I don't know
What the hell guys let's do it
I got a few people don't need 10 memberships today. I just will get back
Yeah, yes, we got it hold on where you got it
Guitar J
Okay, I don't I mean I need to see somebody I know
Guitar J. I don't know who that is
What's the one I know?
You know what you want to match me, you know, I have to of course
You're really exciting to get up all these people don't even remember shit tonight, but there we go
Congratulations guys get some people in here
Each are eight, okay, you know I don't know these people either
How about have an even $20 someone someone can someone someone match me someone just match me
I'll do it
If you match me so cool, it's so cool
20 bucks, whatever
It's a membership extravaganza guys, it's my way of giving back
Good people who did who got it?
Big
RIC oh Christine. Thank you. Christine's awesome. Thank you so much
sweetheart
J-fam big are
CC I
Hope they come in here soon. You like it when there's no fighting. Thank you guys
Thank you Christine sweetheart
Yay guys, that's cool. Get some members some new members. I think we now we've got 20 new members in a couple days
Wow guys
Really really awesome. It's sweet of you guys. You're sleeping. I wake you up. It's deed
Christine there's a song with Susan the band. She's a song called Christine Christine Adam macaroni and she's grilled cheese sandwich
Thank you so much
That's exciting
Exciting guys just anyone want to reading I got doing readings. I don't think my friends are coming back tonight. It's gonna be later
So I still have some energy. I'm just I haven't started my third. I chugged that coffee. I'll probably
Probably have one more one more drink tonight
Pretty good
Pretty good day though
Oh
You're coming up for a reading. Okay, Justin come on up
Okay, my deck for you
Cool guys
Yeah, I'm very I'm very blessed very lucky
Very humble that you know, it's an awesome people you guys hang out with me
No, you got you guys you it's a good bad the ugly
But if you appreciate you love you
Hello, hey psych. How are you doing, buddy? Good. How are you doing? Good, man?
Hi, hi
You still your volume
I'll come up for a reading. Hey, I'm a really excited man. Yeah, cuz I've I never had a reading before
Yeah, okay. I'll do a nice
I'll pull five cards for you. So the first couple cars may be like your
You're a more recent
Pass up to the present the middle card like the present the last two cars
Maybe like in your future or just things to look out for or maybe advice for the future. Okay, okay
So okay, so this is a villain's deck and so
Okay, so this is like okay
So we have this aid of swords and so this can kind of feel like maybe trapped in your head about something cuz it's like, you know
I think this is a lying king. He feels all surrounded. He feels like
But actually, you know, this is mostly, you know, it's mostly the source and so it's mostly to do with the
mental it's mostly it's mostly your own thoughts that are that are
That are your bound, you know, the your
Obstacles or boundaries
Instead of like, you know, you really being trapped you might just feel like that in your head. So it says eight of swords
says
It says it is sort of in the case you're feeling restricted or trapped though. You're hopeless of them
They may hopeless in the moment know you have the power to get yourself out of this
Look around you'll find that you actually have more options than you think you do
Okay, so that might have you might have felt like that in the past. You might have you might have come through that
Okay, oh here. We have the judgment card. Okay, so recently you may come through my judgment. This is the queen of hearth
You know, she was a you know, her judgment was always off with your head
You know, but maybe there's another kind of judgment you've recently been through or you've had to make
judgment here says is
armored with
Royal or
Announced as royal fanfare Queen of Hearts serves as a decisive judge who delivers her verdicts off with her head
with authority judgment represents
cause and effect consequences and
And though the Queen of Hearts may not be familiar with this concept, forgiveness.
So when judgment is drawn into terror reading, indicates you're nearing the end of a long
important journey, while this could refer to a conclusion of a big project, like building
a house or obtaining a dream job, it usually refers to a more personal inner journey.
Take some time to reflect on the steps that led you to where you are now
Appreciate the lessons you've learned along the way and make pieces in the steps you've taken
I might have gotten that first funky earlier too. I don't think the same card. Oh, that's a
That's a judgment. And so also, you know use your best judgment, but remember that forgiveness part is
Important, okay. Okay, so we also have this four of swords and this looks like scar
four of swords so another
something to do
With the with the communication or your thoughts, okay, so the four swords says
It says you fought a hard battle now
It's time for a much needed rest and relaxation
Put your put up your feet and prepare yourself you need to need to recharge in order to prepare for the adventures ahead
So maybe something
There's something big coming up that you need to make sure you're
Rested recharge ready for and prepared. Okay. Oh, we have this
Okay, eight of wands. Okay, so whatever this is there's something coming. There's some news coming really quickly about it
There's gonna be some fast communication
expect some kind of
News I think it's going to be about this this four swords this prepare for or it's like prepare for battle and
Everything's gonna happen really fast everything can happen really fast
Finally this I think this is like really good. Give me the bite. Okay hermit. This means like, you know, make sure you spend enough time
Recharging and doing self love self self reflection
And getting enough me time, take some time to withdraw from the world maybe and just be by yourself or, you know, at least withdraw from the rest of the world.
So, I'll do one more car. I have a feeling one more car for clarification, the whole theme of the reading.
Okay, king of wands. This is about you're coming into your power. You're really mastering your
Emotions you may have had like volatile emotions
and
Like gotten angry or and stuff like that, but it's like the king is like you've come into like being able to master them really
It says the king of wands represents a focus determined
Creative leader
To far was the potential potential for of a diamond in the rough like him the king of wands
Powerful visionary though his methods are unconventional
His commitment to them
Inspires loyalty the card is signed trust your vision even if others don't understand it yet
Okay
Awesome, man
Hope you like that. Yeah, appreciate that. Yeah, there are some that
They're yeah, they're like really spot-on especially like the your first two like what's going on in my life right now like like yeah
That was really accurate. So yeah, I appreciate it, man. Oh
No problem anytime pleasure to know you and spunky you're
Be awesome. Thank you for checking out the show and
Always being great and shadowing panel. Thank you so much. Oh, yeah, thank you. You're welcome. You know Alex
No, it doesn't I never thought that it's fucking ass on my life psyche. Did you back you?
I had I care about hygiene. Yeah. Yeah. Another thing I want to ask you is why did I see you not out on panel the other day?
your eyes were
Chris crossed they were going to the back of your head and then you just nodded out
And that's not tiredness
So don't fucking lie to me, bro. What do you mean?
What do you mean?
It's okay. It's okay. Well, what what are you saying?
I'm not saying anything. I'm just asking. I saw you fall asleep the other day on the panel and your eyes were in the back
of your head
You look like I don't know
Passed away
so it is it is it pills is it pills are you injecting in the toes between the toes
because that was drugs bro and no fucking lie to me i i i've been up for a week straight
i've been doing gmc i've been doing gmc my friend the dmc what the hell is that
dmc is like is like a crazy um psychedelic like it's just like fucking
Okay, it's crazy. It's a good a bed like my good. Oh, it's stronger. It's like stronger. It's like oh my god
I'm not the other thing
Yeah, I mean it's like
That I have pot to have a smoking pot. I've been yeah, yeah, and plus no sleep or yeah, so what that was DMT
Yes, and you like yeah, it's super isn't a relationship in you. I mean it's a it's like you have her ayahuasca or like
Yeah, yeah, that's like natural um acid
Yeah, I mean, yeah
It comes from a tree bark you can extract from the tree bark
But my friend has it I used to make it but I'd like it like it's a little bit from making it
It was kind of waste my friend has a DMT pen and it's like so strong and it's like oh my god
Wait, so one of those great pens has DMT in it. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Now. I'm getting it. Holy shit
Yeah, you know, let's just fuck you up and knock you out
Yeah, your eyes were crisscrossed. I thought you were gonna die. Honestly. I'm like, oh my god
I'm fine. I'm like walking and he just fell asleep and then I saw you like take the covers. I'm like, all right. He's okay. He's okay
But you know that you were scary, man
Well, you see you see Ilya came back on the show
Mr. Big Pies first
Mr. Big Pies put a curse on me
I've already counteracted it. I had a I took a
Uncrossing spiritual bath. Oh, of course what dad that is the harmonica dude for a person. Yeah, you bugger. Yeah, yeah
You believe in that bullshit?
No, but it only works if you believe in it site. I don't believe in the first the first
I was like first he kept putting up this his profile picture as this like
Okay, like some kind of like it was a green. Yeah, I mean bullshit got the green shit
Yeah, and I thought it was just like I thought that was his like computer logo, but then it's like
but then he always had it up but then he said his camera worked and then someone said over that green thing is part of the hex
It's a yeah, it's a chaos magic
sigil
That's like city with his avatar, right? It's another demon. Yeah, same bullshit, bro. It's just retarded people
They have no power over you, bro
Yeah, that's just
Just laugh on them. Just laugh
I know
You know it's funny because before I even so I just like got uncomfortable when I saw this
He was I saw he's using a sigil and then because he was like putting it
He always had it up and so I
Hit him out and then he and he went into the back and he types. He starts every fuck you. He's like your hex
You know, I'm a he's like a little wizard. I'm a powerful magician and stuff like that. And then I had then Ilya came on the show
Yeah, Ilya came on
Yeah
And then Ilya came on and Ilya was wearing a kilt and with no underwear
Oh, no, no, I saw that last the night
That's the day that you passed out on whatever DMP and then he took off his wig. I
Was bugging I'm like oh my god. I everyone knew it was a wig, but he took it off and it was seven Christine
and he's just, you know, Oblamov, just being a good Oblamov, showing a little side,
I don't know, Christine was going crazy, like, that's not a, like, eye candy, I don't know,
but he, he's cool, but he's so funny, I don't know who that fuck that guy is or where he is,
but he's far knee.
Oblamov, man, God bless your Russian ass.
I like him better without the wig, by the way.
but I was wondering if he knew the panel was on because he took off the wig and was like, I was like, what am I wearing this?
It's because I okay, so
He's been on my show three times.
I was his third time on the show.
The first two times, the first time he was on my show,
he mooned the show, and I had to end the stream.
The second time he was on the show,
he said, can I be the first guy on YouTube
to pee in a bucket on a live stream?
And I was like, no, don't pee.
I said, don't do it on my live stream.
I said, if you had to pee, just pee off camera.
And then I was like looking at my phone.
I heard like peeing and he was like sitting there. Yeah, I remember that. Yeah. Yeah
And he showed his penis and I had to like in the stream and
Delete it. So that was like both times he poor mom. So third time
I don't he was testing you're like a loyalty these people people crazy
You know what people get piss like because the the rules you have right?
No point. What what are they? No doxing
No nudity
No, um, talk no slander
Every word everybody's mouth up here is slander. So that rule gets wiped out
It's not being like enforced and then
Noody the only new reappears you in a G string and when your balls pop out or do you get bomb on?
I said
You were behind the stars
So I think people get pissed and now you got these freak Mormons
They're like Christians like that and now and even last night I went on beat us. Did you see that one?
Yeah, I was
How was that? Okay? She stuffed her fucking brawls on her real tits like, you know, I was doing me
and I said, you know, I just heard psyche read half the Bible.
Some this, some that, but he skips over the part where it says,
yeah, you should not lie with man.
Oh
Yeah, you know, that's what I'm here for just to stir the case see what feathers fall out
But man when the motherfuckers reading the Bible about the song this and then he's turning around it
So I want to cock in my mouth
As much as I love you something's not adding up
You cannot say you're reading Psalms and then be like I want to fucking dick in my asshole in the cock in my face
It just doesn't coincide
So that's where I go
Jesus Jesus Jesus was a power bottom. Did you know that? Oh Jesus? I'm sure he was
Was he
Okay, because he had a diaper on big the Romans just put the diaper to the side
Yes
So you tell me that the disciples were actually a bunch of gay guys
under a tree
breaking bread
Just having an orgy and we know nothing about this. They raised that from the Bible
Yes, no, I'm getting man
Yeah, no, I'm getting
So Peter
and Joseph and Jacob they're all cock suck
Bro, but at least go on and suck some cock
Yeah, you know my chat you're after my chat now, you know, you're back much up. You're so rude to me
Yeah, I
Don't know I'm having a panel. I said I said your band. Why do I keep having you back?
Why am I in love with you?
You marry me the question of the age marry you
Do you have a fucking life insurance policy? Maybe
No, nothing found your grand
Well, I had a bitch with a fucking million dollar policy and she made the beneficiary and I kicked a bitch to the curb
The fool can't buy me bitch
Oh
Dangerous, what's up see me? It's like where are you from see me? Oh, that's you see you me. Hey, you me
University night kitty. Oh, yeah, that's Rudy. I have a few kitties here. Good job removing all the wrenches
You're welcome. Yeah. Oh, yeah from day one, bro. Yeah. Well, you know, he's cowboys. I was one
Yeah, yeah
No one just for nobody
Your knees at least three that you trust with your fucking life
Even one I would go to tool man. You got a narrow down
Yeah, well, no, I have a traveling gypsy that I'm on to
That's the best move you've done bro black our G knows it yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, nobody can cry
Shut up. Just you hear that fun
That blue shit like points is everyone's mind
It is a power trip. Everyone just falls into this power trip from out
Yeah, I mean also, you know, it's also I really needed the bonds just to be like they're just like looking out
You know, there's just people that
Channels need money to protect you. Yeah
Therefore not to sit there and fight each other and like have power trips
It's a business your channels of business
mods or your assistants protecting your business
Yep
You understand they like your trump and the monitor the secret service. Are you gonna give everyone a fucking gun in the protect?
the selective
Yeah, nobody gets a right people channels. I mean, I'm offering a service on my channel
I am uh, you know, do you energy I do energy exchange with that? You know, it's like this
I am I'm pretty intuitive. I also have other other ways to support the channel, you know Alex
I think I just did like I think I did like how many I think I did like four or five memberships
I donated and I think it's beautiful and then
Christine donated a membership
and uh, this and Dougie Doug Dougie Dougie or Doug Dougie summer is live right now
Why aren't you there or why aren't they here?
Instead of like being separate everyone should be coinciding. That's what always throws me off
Like why is everyone that his family open up multiple panels at the same time?
Like everyone should be together
Jen, I don't know how you, uh, how you personally membership, but when you click the dollar sign or the, or you go to that member,
membership, membership gifting, and then you have an option there and
very much appreciate it. You know, we're building that community and it's gonna, you know, that
makes me, uh,
even more motivated to
do, do great shows and you know, I have been on every day. It was a good one. Yeah.
Alex is very commanding. Yeah, I was a little little bulldog. I'll sit back again. Yeah, I
Know I can't help it. They mr. Mr. Big Piper says it doesn't charm me out. Alex kind of like
I was kind of this week. I don't know if you guys have seen this but
You guys want to see?
Can you put a video up for old time's sake?
That's a pro for life. Alex
What are you gonna do to me if I you pull me over?
I've been speeding on the freeway. What are you going to do to me?
I'm going to say, sir, license registration. I'm going to pretend it's bad. I'm going to
say step out of the car, and I'm going to throw you in the bushes. In the bushes. I'm
going to fuck the shit out of you. In the bushes.
Okay, oh my god, I'm gonna end up in the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you and then that's it my man
I'm gonna make hot coal and just fall my way
Yeah
Part two
In the trees on the side of the highway
Fucking just give it to you and then that's it my man
I'm gonna get in my top car and just go my way unless you want to go to jail
I can just can't cuff you ticket to jail. I can fuck you on the side of the highway
It's up to you my man. Okay. Thank you guys everyone Alice be controversial
But Alice, he's a sweet guy. He's a sweet guy.
I'm very sweet. My sweetheart.
I'm a lollipop. You're gonna lick me like a lollipop.
How many licks does it take to get to the middle of a tootsie, pop?
Alex, can I try can I can I lick your choo-choo pop Alex? Oh, yeah, baby. Oh my god. Okay. I love I got I love this guy
This good this good. He's my he's my he's my cutie, but he's my he's my cutie, but he gets in that
He's a police uniform he handcuffed me to the bed and he f's the f out of me
So, oh, so romantic. It's nice. It's so sweet
That's that's what I love that looks like easy kissing you
God you want to read you today?
Yeah, okay easy. Yeah, I mean, yeah, it looks like him a little bit
29 people in chat. Wow. That's building up tonight. Wow
Guys, I mean, I've been doing saging today. I took a checker special about you're not feeling tonight. Not even hope they come in peace
I'm feeling peace
Hopefully I'm willing. Oh, I think I'm gonna draw a picture of you tonight Alex. Let me see. Oh
Is it gonna be a demon again?
No, you are a demon so it's like I
Am
Try not to like
Okay, he's not doing it. It's that's fine. Okay, so I'm gonna draw Alex. Let me see
You seen that movie or say so
with the Denzel Washington with the demon would just touch people and will pass through people by touch
That was that was Denzel Washington, right? Yeah, and John Goodman
Remember that? Yeah
It's on my side. Yes, it is
Movie was great
Yeah, that was a cold fallen bite with Denzel Washington, right
Fallen yes
by touch
boom boom boom we were just
the little girls of this part
that was amazing
and it started with the guy on death row
man I just got goosebumps
thinking that shit
I see
okay
of the
the
Okay, let me see it. Let me see
I'm it's on my side. Yes, it is
It's actually not by the way, that's a lie time. It's not on your side. That shit doesn't give a fuck about you
Flames around you
You're spending too much time on it. I'm getting scared now, bro. Okay ready. I'm running three. Thank you
Ah, it's better than the first one
Now now I'm half a demon
Well, the first one was cool beaming. This is half demon. So we're working up the ladder
Maybe the next picture will be a normal
Hold on
But I was dead on your body like it
Hello, oh, where'd he go?
Oh gosh, I love you guys
Let's be able to talk to people
I'm gonna draw that Alex
Everyone like this dream. Yeah
Flirty come on before it comes out. I'll draw picture 30. Oh
I don't know one
Hey, Prairie, what are you doing?
I'll draw you for the if you want. This is my page drawing
I think I kind of fixed it a little bit
Hi guys
Paige
Oh he's back
Oh shit that was funny
Yo I was trying to zoom in on the picture
To get like an in close
step look of it
Cause it's better than the first one
Yeah well this one this one
That's like the first one that was the prototype
Yeah that's the first one
Exactly now do them put them both together if you can side-by-side and we'll see how how far I've come
I'm only happy man now
Yeah
You see Alice
Sage and page page was supposed to open a store called sage and page
Coaxing and yours is yours wiener, too. Oh, I see that. Oh, wow. There's a wiener. Yeah. Yeah
It's normal size Alex
It doesn't represent the real thing at all though, you got a triple that we know a couple more a couple more at least
Couple a couple of senses. Yeah, come on. You gotta edit that puppy
the
i don't understand why brazil i mean i guess brazil but why not canada what if like it's a goose
or you can't you're in canada you fly down south in the winter so i just thought it south america
and i want brazil or would you rather chili have you heard been to santiago chili no i would
just uh you're right we'll just stick to brazil okay yeah speaking of brazil what's up with that
It's what do you mean? It's a t-shirt bra if you can't like I normally I don't I wear just never mind
That's in your business. First of all, and it's where we're
appropriate and it's just never mind
It was she had a hot tank top psyche really tight
She'll come out. I'll see you here on page
Maybe I don't know Emma
You need some hobbies. We need to find you some hobbies.
Oh, so help me out with the hobby finding. What do you suggest?
So I can take my site.
and
back in your fucking house
get a bottle of Windex, baby
spray the windows
alright, clean up
Alex, Alex
I'll never be cleaning
Alex, if 5 seconds to apologize
or I'm kicking you out
3, 2, 1, later
Motherfucker.
I mean you just say sorry.
I said yes was a call page.
It's honestly okay. I don't care if he doesn't say sorry.
I just don't want him to stay in the first place, right?
Yeah.
Alex, you have five minutes time out.
And the next time you do it, it'll be a 25 minute time out.
And it'll be a 25 hour time out.
And you know how long psychs minutes are.
They're really long because you forget.
How's that go, too?
All right, Alex left, Alex left.
Well, I've just been, I've been doing readings tonight.
I've been, you know, it's been really good though.
You know, it's having a fun day.
Like, I've been doing more of what I wanted to do
with the channel, which is like, have readings,
have good people come in.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, even forgiving Alex, you know,
it's like, it just shows me, I can be so mad at somebody
and then like, I still forgive them, you know, I don't know.
well we discussed that in your in the like we did readings for each other like this morning
wasn't it this afternoon yeah and it definitely said a lot of that so it's good that it's coming
to fruition yeah and it's like also you know it's like you know guys it's like a lot of the world
is like you know generated from our mind it's like it's almost like
We have so much power over our future by thinking positively and not thinking all these horrible scenarios
because that will just paralyze us what we want to do is just
Live in the moment
Do what makes us happy and then it's like at least if something horrible happens
We'll have done what we want to do up to the moment that we can't do anymore
So he left the dog out for the day. I was like, oh, you're welcome, Jamie's. You're welcome.
How did you do it?
Oh, I didn't say hi to anybody in the chat. And I felt like,
no, I feel like what Alex called me, I can call myself.
Oh, no.
Hello, Jamie Gotti. Yon. We have Yime. Dingle. See. That's it.
What do you mean, perfect?
Oh, thing. That's right.
Oh, that sucks.
And 30 and 30. What's up? 30. Hey everybody in chat. Oh
God
Hey stories, you know every notice when you watch the movie and it's like I never know
I never care if like a hundred people are really gunned down or horrible things happen
But then it's like the dog the dog dies the movie devastated. You know, it's like
But it's like the worst thing that happened in the movies.
Oh, I know, it's so sad.
Dogs are so loving too, they're so loving, trusting,
and loyal, and nice to meet you too, Jenny.
You're awesome.
Thank you so much.
Pleasure meeting you, pleasure reading for you.
Thank you for everything, okay?
Thank you so much.
Sweetheart.
Don't, yeah.
He mirrors. Oh my god. I'm sorry. Yeah
That's a dirt bag
Yeah, you know, you know, if you the way people treat animals, you know
She treats you a lot. That's that's prairie page. Jen. If you want to come
I don't know if you are on or come up on the panel and Jen, but yeah, they're pretty big great
great intuitive
clairvoyant
terabiter she's a bisscher a hunter
You know, she's uh, what are you mounting page or no?
I think she's in the Canadian Canadian police force I'm not sure
Are you oh, no, that's page. It's prairie page
Prairie page and the prairie page of the channel prairie page and wildflowers very prairie page wins
When's in my pretty page wildfire page?
This is a way hey, sorry, I was had it help me
Hi, so I had a gentleman say hi to you Jen is in the chat
Didn't want to say hi pretty page and she's shy, but she went back when I ask you a question
I'm not sure, but she's a really sweet sweet person remember today the channel
Also like page I got like 20 members 20 members is probably the last couple of days
I donated a few of them and
and
We had a few wonderful donators including Jen
You're already putting that vibration out there and already receiving yeah, and I've been doing more readings today and
You know there's been calmer like less drama, but you know more more readings and
Chat interaction
So it's going great 24 people awesome guys
Yeah, I get bad with the little help my friends. What's that? What's that song?
What song?
I don't I don't I don't want to trigger the business of big pipes with seeing this Beatles song
What's the Beatles? I think he's he was I think he was live. I was like
He told a story page. He said he
He like let this like muscular woman
Peg him for two hours
It was either with an eight is dildo or the Dr. Pepper ball. I'm not sure
Okay, yeah
Yeah, and I just say and then he like started like saying weird and then he just kept talking like weird to me
Oh, and then he had like this like
digital or the symbol on screen someone's like oh that's chaos magic and I was oh
that kind of explain why you like had up all the time and then he I blocked him
and then he said he said he hexed me and six six six
I'm not asking. Oh, I'm just saying what he was trying to do you for magic. Oh
Jamie was oh
Please ask psyche. Let me see. I'm trying to figure out what said I
Don't know what you guys in Jamie. I don't see more. This is
You ask again, Jamie, I don't think him up the question him
Oh, to buy memberships. Yeah, there's I don't have the discord one is uh is the current but there is the membership link and
Much appreciated for everything guys
Have a fun night where we can do more reading and 26 people in chat. Let's see genie's posting the rules
They're shut the lane
I move yeah, I was gonna say better do some spiritual shit. It'd be rude not to if that's already the vibe
Look I got page here's what I got today. Look. Okay. I'm looking oh
It's wicked beautiful, and it's like oh I love it reminds me of like little
to wrap me to be like that
See fun those so guys just imagine smoke is like
clearing everything from everywhere
This is a kind of like a rakey almost because
This too
Everybody be sure to like, you know, okay look at your face. Look at your face. You see look at your face looks like Alexander McQueen's little face
Yeah, when he's angry
Like his little guy that you drew of him
Yeah
Well, I think that I need to have a koo to the
Yeah, let's do some spiritual shit
Let's do some spiritual shit. Love it.
Ugh. It feels like I didn't even have a day off.
And it wasn't even a day off because I had to go do a bunch of other stuff and get up at like 6 o'clock this morning anyways.
I have to work tomorrow and every other day till I think...
What day is it tomorrow? Tuesday? No, Wednesday.
Tomorrow is Wednesday, yeah.
Well, it's all in one in one hour of the Wednesday
Well, that's a nice cleanse session. Thank you psych. Yeah, there you go guys just imagine smoke clearing away all negativity
and all the smoke just like
pushing it everything negative and clearing the way for
Beautiful energy
It's all going out the window all the negative going out the window everything
All the smoke will take all the negative with it, okay?
Okay, your cleanse now. Yeah, it feels better. Okay, let's close the ride
How do the cats feel good calm yeah, well I got Lola and tricks didn't right next to me Lola you're good
Lola is watching me like what the hell are you doing? What are you smoke? What is that burning?
What are you doing?
Just watching the smoke
My cats go crazy when I burn stuff like that or like the Palo Santo or the
Pretty much anything of that nature, but I think it kind of falls into like the catnip family
Yeah, I know yeah, I wonder if cats like sage, but
Yeah, there's so many amazing botanicals that we use I kind of like don't even think about it
But I've been in the Chinese Chinese that Empress gardens and you just walk through the million like
Also, there's a there's a garden in England. It has all the poisonous plants. It's a poison garden
I want to go there one day. Have you ever seen that? Yeah, but I don't think I could trust myself there
I think I would I would actually kill myself
Touching a plant
Page would be collect page would come in with a basket to collect everything for her potions my pocket three cabinet
But I would also accidentally probably touched one of you. I forgot the gloves and then just dropped my knees
Who Landers says you live in crystal healing as well. What do you think about crystals page? Oh, that crystals
You guys know this. I mean some I feel like some people it's we can never really have enough crystals
But just make sure you're not getting
fake crystals or too many tumbled stones and stuff like that because crystals in their raw natural form are
the most powerful
Right. I mean anyone can make manufacturers like who looking like
In the glass but these crystals, this is like billions of years in like the earth and
And it's like and then and it's like this high concentrated energy in it
They have different effects depending on the crystal, but yeah, you want to these natural crystals
they've been aged over billions of years and
Also sell them online too like they'll just like paint fucking really polished rocks to look like let's say like a
Dummy shish jasper like wand or something
Yeah, and then it falls in the ground and it's like it's got just like chalk fucking cement whatever
It's not it's not it's not crystal at all
So it's just you can get ripped off really easily and just just fake stones and things like that, right?
Yeah, yeah, so you want to go to like a you know
I would say go to your local like either a new-age shop or any kind of special
I actually I've been to a crystal store
But it closed down with this one lady had a storage this whole crystal stuff. I think she like shut down, but
No, go to a new-age store support or support or find uh, some in your area
Want like a bathtub like a crystal bathtub be the amethyst or like any of the crystals
I would take any of them, but that would be so beautiful and I've seen a lot of those going to houses now, and I'm like I
Won't be able to afford something like that in 10 lifetimes my dad. So
Well, yeah, it's really pretty
We never know it's like, you know, what will happen in this life. It'll give you great opportunities
We come across that kid. Yeah, we never know
Might strike goals
And all you guys amethyst bath tubs, you never know. Yeah, maybe cycle
Yeah, maybe I'll start a commune and then it will be for the best
I'll close on service at hand all day long. Yes. Yes
Good idea, we'd all bring something to the table. Yes
I think uh, but I think you know working together we can make make a lot of things happen working alone
We can make some things happen, but you know, it'll be more limited work together. We can make big things happen
And we're gonna make should be about based on the channel should be everybody has like a little character a little guy
We'll collect collect commune
Chaos or something like that. I don't know
Yeah
Prairie page
Who's
Okay, so okay, so they used to sit. Yeah, this is cell and there's a tom shopping
Tom shopping when they sold some like second releases and second readings of course, but then there was like some like
There was one place where they sold candles like their color candles and like the kind of new age vibe
But I wish there would be more New Age stores though.
I mean, they're kind of hard to find now.
We got a lot of funky little, we got a lot of stuff like that around here.
Yeah.
Well, I think there's some talented artists around here.
We have a lot of artists here. We have a lot of hairdressers.
Yeah, you can throw a rock and hit a liquor store. It's fucking hair salon for sure. They're only every quarter
Have I done a hoodoo tarot for you Paige?
Um, I don't think that you have but we both love that deck. You could totally pull me one if you
Wondered however many you want to pull. Okay. I just have to draw my hands off. Okay
Uh, let's do it. It's more hoodoo
I'm here, here we go.
Okay, tell me when to stop.
Stop.
My face is going.
Okay.
Okay, Paige, you got this.
Did I create some kind of madness? What what's happening?
Okay, so you get this nine of this is a nine of coins, okay?
So it's a nine pinnacles. It's so there's a woman and she has a cat on her lap. Yeah
Okay, and
so nine of pinnacles is you know, usually this
Part of like abundance if you've got you got abundance around you. You're comfortable. You have the cat in your lap
But it's so I got the nine of
Nine of and you're motionally
Materially, you're satisfied.
Golden seal flowers, as the woman lounges at home
with all the trappings of luxury and refinement.
The woman knows you're probably jealous of her,
so she dons a dress with a pattern
that protects her from the evil eye.
In case that doesn't work,
then she has a serocenia plant nearby,
which is said to protect its owner from negative energy.
It says positive, self-reliance, well-deserved success,
Self-employed property owner inheritance material gain creature comforts of skill lifestyle
These are times spent alone luxury discipline avoiding the bad part of town
Enjoyment of the finer things in life people society consider classy
Taking the time to relax and unwind. Okay
There's that one. I'll get one for you. Okay. Oh, I got two
Oh
Okay, so there's been some kind of like competition like a it's five of six
There's been like some kind of like fighting
Maybe in a group. It says the image a teenager looks across as four of his peers talk maliciously behind her back
She will cross jinx them later and it says healthy competition, diversity, assertiveness,
having faith that you can win, arguments that reveal the truth, martial arts, finding common
ground, a battle of wits, the bake club, relief from tension and breaking the ice.
You got that five, but you also got this two, so this is a two of sticks, this is a two
of wands.
You know sometimes it has two people putting the ones together, but this one has one person with with the two ones
Okay, so it's like more of like a I think it's more of like your own power
involved in this it says
The plant comfrey and it says the man in the card depicts Dr. Sandy Jenkins, the root worker who gave Frederick Douglass a route to protect him from being abused by a sadistic overseer.
Douglas was never bothered by the man again. Here Sandy is shown gazing out at the sand miles River of Maryland.
I'm afraid to go against the grain deciding to travel or move over sea and the power to persuade and influence people
And so I have comfrey, but actually we have comfrey put in our garden. We're not supposed to
Yeah
Well, there you go. That was like uh
That's like the plant of that card and that's like you know symbolic of like
It's one of those powerful healing plants in the whole planet. Yeah
Comfrey so, I mean, yeah
who's a very it's very cool because it also is like this it's like also like you know
like some of the african uh folk folk magic mixed with like the european
yeah twist to it because the europeans would like hire them and like work with them and sometimes
they were you know biracial or and so it's like it's like a great blending and so it's like yeah
so where how's everyone in the chat yeah that was it was cute i like that i like that reading for
You're welcome
Yeah, it's like
Everybody tired from partying on it. You how long did those lives go last night?
My live or yeah, I mean
Beedahs who's so freaking long?
Yeah, beat of I'll beat is I woke up at like ten o'clock is more six o'clock seven o'clock beat it was on this morning when I was on
Yeah, and I see that Kate is doing longer lives
Well, it's good. It's like, you know, it's like that's the thing. I know maybe hopefully maybe I inspire some people in a way
But it's like, you know
You was like, oh, well, and she's like I'm doing longer lives because now I'm not helping psyche
And it's like yeah, and that but that's you know, it's true. It's like sometimes when we're like helping other channels
We're not spending as much time on our own channel. And so, you know, we want to make sure that we
You know, when do you oh nice the look at Jamie's doing nice. Oh, thank you
We make sure that we're you know, we try to support each other's channels and but also
You know if we have a channel
You know have our own have our own platform to open and you know, it's not a competition
It's like we want to help everybody like I'll be sure to like
Allow all these people in my show talking the panel promote their shows
Now we can visit everyone there's that guys there's plenty of people there's plenty of people in the world we can bring
Community as big as it is like, you know, that's how you you know started. Yeah
Yeah, we can build an empire like let's let's bring a million people into the community like you know
we can all do it together world and
There's out of a million people. That's like 1% of like of like a bit of a
Of like two billion, I don't know it's like it's like or you know less than one percent
It's like a tiny little percentage of like the amount of people on YouTube
Most of those people would probably be interested
Most of them are probably looking for the channel already and more would be interested if they found it, you know, you never know so we have to
support people
Oh here
Hold on see why
So hi
What's up, buddy? How are you?
Mom she's I was good
Hey, do you remember she why yeah, I just didn't want to interrupt him. How are you doing hon?
You're more and more fucking drama
This bitch took my channel again two days ago, bro. I'm starting over again, bitch. It's this bitch on
This bitch is a psychopath, bro
How'd you take it now what happened? No, this bitch this bitch done erased my fucking channel, bro
This just took my channel again, but this is a psychopath on the internet, bro
She can take anybody's channel this bitch is out of her fucking mind, bro
How can anyone take anybody's channel?
This bitch that took 10 15 people's channels sees docks and people's criminal records
He doing all this shit man in the bus this whole want to ask me my pot really from the dry down
It just popped his bitch
Man, but I don't even want to tell you I'm just man. I just can't think
I mean, you're not monetizing so how can the channel really be can you start more channels or?
Put a picture bro this bitch over here listening. She's her whole life is on the internet
She sits on here 20 hours 24 hours a day, bro
She goes panel to panel screaming and people she sits on there, bro
She got a hundred enemies, bro
People don't like this bitch just keeps coming around coming around people are scared of this bitch. She just keeps it up though
This bitch jelly, bro. She's just out of her fucking mind. She's a psychopath, bro
This bitch is out of her fucking mind. I'm in this bitch, too, bro. Okay
You ask me questions
Presses it a different a different wording
No, well, I did I don't know about don't make threats. I ain't a kid. I make promises
But she's letting you know she out. She's out of her mind, man
I never seen nobody docked and do this shit that this girl knows how to do bro
She knows how to take your channel, bro
She knows how to hit you with three strikes bro in one one time you feel me and just get your channel terminated
That's what she did the other day, bro. I was just talking to pray the other day
You know what I mean? Yeah, what was this talk? She was just on my pen and then the channel got a race
You got a race right after that. That's why I went live cuz I knew she was gonna do it
Well, but what's good man good with y'all though man y'all good
What's up my G
What's up, Jereo
I'm uh, I had to like reinstall my uh, all computer. Oh, you did?
Welcome back. Is yeah
Is that Chris yeah, what up? What up? Yeah, what's up, boy?
I'm downloading right now. I'm downloading GTA 5. I want to play with the homie. So fucking
It's in your life. I want to sell comes in with like I haven't been on for a fucking night my son my computer fucked up my hard drive died
Well, yeah
It's like how come you don't come no more, bro. You too good or what bro?
I haven't seen your channel yet. I mean, you said you had like three different
This month is the fourth the fifth time it's been ticking down, bro
So this the new one so y'all subscribe or whatever you think if you can drop the link or hit it
Because you know, I don't know how to do those shit. I just got it back today, bro. So
Yeah
Well, how'd you get you got bands? No, this is this psychic this girl is just taking my channel, bro
She just she back my criminal wreck. She's doing all this shit. She shuts down 10 15 people's channel
This bitch is a psychopath, bro
You know what I'm saying, it's gonna take time, but we gonna stop this girl. She's dumb. She's all over the end of season
Nucca's bro. Her whole life is based on this. She knows every trick in the bush
She knows this bitch is just on me, bro. You feel me? You know what I mean?
I've never seen no person like this. I've never met nobody so psychotic. They don't have a life, bro
They just keep fucking with people. It's not me, but she's doing this shit to about 30 40 people
The bitch is out of her fucking mind, bro
Hey, I mean is she fat
Yeah, we exposed the real pictures, but she tried she's alive. She's cuz she's a compulsive liar, bro
She's saying that's not her. We got all her shit. Yeah, we've been doxing her same shit, bro. You feel me?
Listic bro, I gave the girl the keys to my channel. She got so man. My channel was blown up had about
You know, I like black women. They said with that about man
We started blowing the channel of it started growing growing. She got so jealous, bro
She's seen all these sisters coming up in there, bro
And this and that and the girl just erased my channel, bro
So then I get it back, right? Just got it back this motherfucker three weeks, bro
Wasn't three four weeks into it. This girl just got my channel shut down yesterday day before yesterday
Page was just on my shit talking to her and Tracy
Tracy probably seen it too Tracy. No my channel got erased against you probably like what the hell bro
I haven't even seen all my dog Tracy like bro
So but yeah, man, it's like bro this girl's out of her mind bro. She's doxing people bro
She's doing this shit to all kinds. She got so many enemies, bro. I'm telling you they're gonna ever she gonna end up getting wiped
I'm telling you bro. There's people on here ain't gonna play with you, bro
There's people on here. You can't play with everybody on the internet, bro. You feel me?
You know
Hey, man, let me tell you something if I didn't want to go back to that cage
20s I'm a grown man 46 if I was back in my 20s 30s, I would have been took a plane ticket
I know where address I got no exactly where she at, but I know she'll call
But you know if I go down there, they're gonna call the police. You know that shit, bro
They talk that gangsta shit, but if I was to get off the plane and go over there, you know, what's gonna happen, bro
They're gonna call the cops. They ain't about that shit, bro. They talk this
Motherfucker's a scary than a motherfucker, bro
That's the only reason I ain't jumped on a plane getting just bashed this whole man because I know i'ma go to jail, bro
You feel me?
I'm the same way, I'm the same way, like if I say something like to somebody on the internet, like I mean it, I'll back it up, type shit, you know what I mean?
Well, but I'm not even fucking with this motherfucker. This motherfucker just comes over and listens to people to
Listening and looking for something that she can try to strike me on a picture of her this and that
But she's sitting here playing a dangerous game because she's sitting here fucking with people
And then when people do it to her she want to cry and play victim like bitch every motherfucker ain't gonna play
Somebody's gonna end up take bro. You can't play with everybody out here, bro
Like you see that's the problem with everybody. They think this sits a game out here, bro
This ain't no game, bro
That's the problem with people they play in life like this is some video game a motherfucker will knock your motherfuckin
Look I heard about it, but what was the cake? Well, what happened, bro?
They had they had YouTube beef. They had fucking they were both streamers out here in Vegas
They walk and they walked around the strip every day and like record the strip and like
Chill the other one
Yeah, the other the other one the dude that got shot had like multiple videos
I think his channel still up, but he had multiple videos on his channel like fucking just like dedicated to talking shit about this
Other guy and the other guy the other guys from fucking Northern, California like fucking he's been in the I can guarantee he's been in prison
He's fucking
And fucking just the fuck he's a plate. You know, I mean doesn't fuck around like regardless of fucking internet bullshit and
You know, so fucking came up, you know, you see every century see the clips, right?
So so so so the one that got shot. He's dead, right? Oh, did he let did he make it?
The youtuber killed him and his wife
Right there so he just walked right into both
On stream
That's why I'm trying to tell you people act like they know who they playing with you don't know what you don't know
What people are going through look man
I could be walking down the street bro in a motherfucker run up on me and just start fucking with me
I could have lost my mama five minutes ago and you come over here with that
But man, I knew motherfucker gonna kill you bro. You can't be playing with people on here
That's what that's what people think that they can just fuck around and play with people out here, bro
We don't work like that life don't work like that
You feel me, bro. I'm from I'm from fucking San Bernardino County from Southern California
I'd like I know people fuck trip on you if you want you just going in to pay your gas like you mad dog
Let me hold me. What's up? Where are you from though? Yeah?
Yeah
Like me just pull out that pistol blast a bitch has then they gonna be looking stupid then they gonna say I'm wrong
He's gonna call me a monster on the news while the white media is gonna sit there portray me like I'm some fucking monster
You feel me. Oh, this motherfucker get a criminal record. He's the bad guy here
Okay, but you didn't just say how these dudes walking up to me talking that shit, bro
You can't be doing that shit. That's the problem with these dudes out here. They think they tough
Think they can walk up to anybody with that bullshit and then when somebody take they fucking life
Everybody want it. Oh now you ready to put them up up behind bars for the rest of their life
No, you said that motherfucking shouldn't have walked up to me with that bullshit in the first place, bro
That's why it's been says dead. That's the problem with this way
Yeah
That's why I keep people this ain't no game, bro. People ain't playing on here, bro. This ain't no fucking game
It's the problem with people with people bro, you don't play with nobody out here, but it's grown men you fucking fucking
That's what I'm saying. I like I don't you know people fucking a company
Oh, I can't front. I'm like, oh, I was drunk like I don't care if you're a drunk dog like fucking what you say
Bro, yeah, that's why people tell people all the time man
Don't let that alcohol get your ass motherfucking will bro and get you y'all sit here and drink and get full alcohol
Start talking crazy to people how drunk people ask start putting your hands on some motherfucking gonna take your life out here, bro
I can't stand drunk people, bro. They don't know how to control. They look at me like it's a scene, bro
Like I listen asshole asshole calm down calm the fuck down
I'm gonna have to this with
respectfully
Disagreeable what you're saying right now, bitch
Oh, and I'm gonna tell you why
If you can shut the fuck up for two seconds for your stupid ass
Are you gonna use your mom dying?
You know
Just let it out and then what I can talk I'll talk
Which are big-ass mouth
So you're gonna use your mom dying as an excuse to attack somebody if they call you pussy on the street
Cuz your mom just died
So now you're using that as an excuse like yo, you don't know what I've been through son
Now you're dead and I'm gonna pull out a glock and blow your head off. That's the most pussy shit. I've ever heard of my life
You can't control the monster brother
Fuck of your mom your dad your sister your brother died that day
and i come and smack you in the face you better control that monster homeboy
and what what what are you gonna do blow my head open then you end up in jail like a loser for the
rest of your life so now your mom's dad and you're in jail because you are a little boy
that can't control your ego shut the fuck up what you're saying is the weakest shit i've
heard in my life homeboy you the first nigga gonna run bitch ass nigga internet ass bitch
Yeah, whatever bruh. I seen you little Puerto Rican bullshit ass. You bro, you haven't left high school
You're still stuck in the same gear from fucking the 1980s my boy
the fuck up you just said it's okay to blow someone's head off because maybe
they don't know what i'm going through that day
so you have much of a pussy that you're gonna hide behind your little feelings so so so much
I thought I'm gonna say he doesn't understand what fucking what he meant like fucking like
He the first nigga get his job broke man, he ain't about that city just roll
If I see him
He might have just broke up with his fucking girlfriend or his wife or whatever dude. He's got a bad day
He's gonna fucking pop
Cornerstone right now. He wouldn't talk like that bro because I break his bitch ass job, bro
Running his motherfucking dick suckers man
Don't use that big mouth to swallow some motherfucking nut. That's what he need to do because I know he's
Know he sucked it. Oh
Fake-ass cop, bro always come by here police officer bitch, please
Mother gonna beat your bitch ass throw the cuffs on you and drag your bitch ass down the street
Yeah, I hear you. I hear you bro. I'm fucking you know, I'm trying to fucking I'm trying my best to like not get in trouble type shit
You know, I can't stand that motherfucker like nobody else can I don't know why I say great
I that beats all he does is screamed like a little old hoe, bro
They don't mean something kill him out there. Just see that's the problem
I'll be telling you these dudes on the internet. He ain't talking like that in the real world
You think he going out in the real world talking shit talking the way he does on here motherfucker kill him in five minutes, bro
Somebody to kill his
Well, how are we doing it?
Just saying you know, I can't stand that bill. That's all he does is scream
Bro, I know that's your boy, but he don't know how to talk to people somebody gonna take his life
That motherfucker I killed in Vegas. It should have been him
That's who it should have been. I wasn't no sleep the motherfucker told me he died the next five minutes. I'll parade that shit
Do's like that. They need to
Clip or that shit is crazy, bro. Yeah, well, they got a clip of it
I can't show
They got a clip of that dude killing that they got a clip for me. Yeah, I think you can look it up
You can show you can share the clip in the back chat. Have you seen it? I
Wouldn't want to watch that mean no just saying have you seen it? I haven't seen it
He'd really watch at least in Georgia. She's seen it
Here's did you see it?
Chris thought
Yeah, I see it bro. I knew I knew I knew both the streamers do I didn't know personally, but I knew who they were and
Yeah
It's all bad fuck I can't write you know fucking on like a lot of live on live stream
Motherfuckin got pop five times on live stream and the chick holding the camera that fuck I was like, are you serious boom boom?
How many times did he shoot that dude in his wife?
seven seven shots all together five in the and five in the guy and then two in the
chick the first one hitter the chest another one that's going to hit the
head shot so you're telling me the beat so let me ask you this was the beef with
them because of their champ but different channels and they were like we're like
did they explain where it started from or what yeah they were both youtubers
livestreamers on the biggest they would stream the strip and like one of the
Yeah
That sounds just like that girl jelly broke that be on my that's what she's doing everybody and that's why everybody keep telling
The motherfuck don't kill your bitch ass, bro. I'm just saying
This is a psychotic motherfucker site. She's psychotic, bro. She is bro not even playing
She's doing this to like 15 20 people somebody's gonna kill a site. I'm telling you I would have been done it
But I already know what's gonna happen to me if I go out
No site, but you can't keep people like that site. I know this miss is a demon. She's
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
I mean yacht fella he was trolling him or some stupid. He was trolling him
Yeah, it's very sad guys and it's like even like no
But that's like that's a good thing. It's like, you know, that's why people really don't
Do do that kind of thing because you know, it's not a pretty good energy to have somebody
With a bloodlust coming after you. Do you why the champ? What's up Nick? How are you?
As everyone do it I'll show the screen if you want if you want to see it
Oh, I have the whole I can't I don't know. Can you just say the link? Can't show the link in the back or something?
Or tell I can't I can't I don't want to show in my show. I just don't know if it's copyright or it's like gonna be again
I don't
It's okay guys it's gonna go look go look go look it up. I just I can't play stuff on my show. I'm sorry guys, but
Unfortunately, I'm just like I can't play any other material in my show right now
But guys you can go look up there tell tell the clip is named Chris and then people can go visit
I can barely hear you dude
Just tell what the clip is named and people can go visit on YouTube, but I can't play on the show
All right, well fuck
What's it called?
Mean the Las Vegas shooting near Bellagio fountains live stream, okay
Yeah
Okay, make sure you visit that
Rock the cash rock the cash
Yeah
Well, no, that's a sign. I was playing when they got popped. That's crazy. Yeah
Yeah, well
Maybe it's a sigh up, but maybe it could be a sigh up. I'm not 100% sure it sounds like
Well, how do I like I mean look it up and watch it off like wow, you know a lot of you haven't I
Have a phone
Motherfuckers don't you know
YouTubers fucking that are like getting money and fucking they have some other youtubers like striking videos and type shit
Full didn't he didn't play around it. So fucking he's like easy. He's like Willie
The guys get life without without parole
You know, I mean like the guys obviously, you know, he turned himself in afterwards
Just so like he didn't go on the run and probably get caught and get the death penalty type shit
I mean, this was execution type shit. He executed these guys like right there
Like he just came up just like pop pop pop pop
Pop pop and like walked away. I mean, and you know
Yeah, but that's what happens sometimes when you know, it's like people will believe someone they think has no power
They'll believe somebody that they they think is weaker than them
And you know what a gum is a gun is a great equalizer, you know a gun all of a sudden doesn't matter how how big or small you are
You can as long as you get your hand
Like I said, it's a fucking wake-up call for fucking busters on the internet
They sit there and talk shit because you know some people fucking take it serious
When you fucking when you talk shit them other fuckers like they'll fucking come to your house or they'll fucking do whatever you'd like
You know if you're not ready to fucking back it up and fucking and fucking you know I mean
Then don't fucking don't fucking say anything. Well. Yeah, but I mean with the internet at the same time is like there's so much that's like
I say something on the internet, I fuck it. I will talk to you into your face and say the same thing
Like I'm not I'm not I'm not joking
Or whatever on here. I'm not trying to fucking play games. You know, exactly Chris. I'm feeling you bro. Yeah
but I think they're like bring it like internet beefs into the real world into like
actually
Harmony for me. I think that's taking it too far. It's like, you know say anything you want like talk all the shit you want like
On their shows and stuff like that. Just like
When you like when you gotta fit it over something over the internet
They're gonna like actually like spend time energy and risk your life and freedom to go. Hey Jennifer
Thank you for the thank you for the super sticker. That's so sweet of you. You're awesome
Thank you so much. Hope you're enjoying the show
Yeah, but it's like, you know violence is not the answer. It's you know, some people have mental health issues
That's why they're constantly threatening or doing this kind of stuff. We don't really you don't really know the whole history of
Everything so
It's hard to it's hard to give an honest assessment, right?
Is this something new would happen? No, I think we're telling the same story. You need the dirt this might be good
Yeah, we're just talking about you know the reasons for it
You know, but it's really relatable as a YouTube creator, especially someone that's you know someone's striked before or you know
You know, it's like, you know, I've got the clip, but you know, it's like, you know, it's like, if you want to, you know, I mean, I just can't, I can't, I can't play the clip.
I just, I just can't, I just can't play a clip from my show, but everyone, you know, Las Vegas shooting clip on YouTube.
You know, strike you.
Yeah, well, I'm just, I'm just, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been, I've been.
I
There's a shooting too. I don't really don't want a shooting on my show like I don't want to like you know
So what like some so hot?
Chris, how do I find I find it?
You got an X
Do I got what X like an X like a Twitter
I
Just go on YouTube and go Las Vegas shooting live or like
Couple
You pop they ask bro, what did he do did he get how long did he get caught how long it took for them to kill to get him
Well, he ran he got away
He got away the cops were looking for like a day and then fucking he turned himself in like a day later. Yeah
How old was the guy that pop that pop boat done?
Like 40 like 38 something like that. Yeah, he's done. He ain't coming home. He ain't coming home
He's 40
He's done. He's done. He might even he might not have a chance at 15 20 broke is they were they gonna give him about
Yeah
He's trying to
Claim a self-defense
Man, come on man. You know claims say you just walk these people and just our problem. Oh, come on. Yeah
He's walking and then you know, it's a it's a it's a black guy and his black girlfriend, right and
Uh, they they had, you know, they they already know each other, right?
So he's walking and as the chick comes up, he's like, you better not come around here trying to talk shit
The other guy walked the the her the chick's husband was like, what's up blood and he's like pop pop pop pop
And then fucking she's like, are you serious then?
pop pop
And see and i'm gonna show you how crazy it is because when you get on when you get into it with these people on here
There'll be that you always hear people say oh you ain't gonna do nothing you ain't gonna do nothing blah blah blah
But then when that shit happened you'll be a task then what you feel me?
But but I'm just telling you
It's just a wake-up call for people that fucking, you know, come on Internet
Exactly, bro, this shit ain't no fucking game, bro. I don't you know
Right, I mean it's a game. It's not a game, but it is a game and it's like, you know, it's like it's not we're not supposed to
They get that seriously where we're actually harassing people in real life
That's why it's like the no doxing no threatening. They just like keep it
You know, it's like if you people will talk shit in front of somebody they wouldn't say it in person
Sometimes they they're just talking because they're very safe to be thousand miles away behind the camera
They don't they're just talking shit like you know, it's like if someone actually shows up
Don't say you can't keep playing like that. No, bro people. Everybody's not playing out here site
Well, I know I'm saying you know, you don't want to mess with people
I said you don't want to bully people either because you don't know if you bully people
You don't know if they're gonna they're gonna snap, you know, that's what the
CUL you be any and
Like telling me about about this female, bro
You don't understand this motherfucker's added all day and you think some of us ain't ready to snap, bro
I'm telling you
I know but I know but you know, it's like
Really either what if she has these mental health issues? She maybe belongs in a
She knows
Yeah, then you have to leave just like you know just like uh pretty much not interacting this
Close all ways of communication, you know
But mental health and we don't act like that and we don't do this type of fucking psychotic ass shit though, bro
I suffer from mental head like a lot of people do bro, but you don't see me doing this type of whole ass shit, bro
You know what I mean? That's all I'm saying, bro
Yeah
Hopefully hopefully she maybe get some help and
No, she's she's all here screaming 24 out literally. I'm not exaggerating site
Then you know who she is because you used to be in there, bro with her jelly
Jelly, she's fucked up. You remember what you might not be your mind now
But site when you was in the track, you know who jelly is bro
You know, if you think about it and you remember you you know who she is
But I know you guys have called the cops
Okay, well, I
That's not even her real name, bro. That's why I'm saying
That's not even it's just we don't want it
We don't want to say the name too many times you'll show up and then all chaos
I think it's a beetle
Hey, it's like subscribe bro, it can come show up bro straight up though, man. Stop stop playing for real
You say that bro, but you got it. I mean make sure you subscribe to it though, bro
Yeah, cuz I'm
It's okay women. It's like, you know what, you know, you can start over as many times as you need to if you have an audience to follow you
You know, you can always like, you know that everyone know your new channel over here and
You know, and you can slowly build it is just build it
You know, it's like it's not I don't know if it was monetized or not, but you know, you can have many channels
Like being monetized, you know, they'll never monetize the trap, bro. You know that shit
CB's interested in terrarium tonight CB just let me know
They got a free reading or I have I put the bear up for even wanted longer reading tonight
I got longer
I need to read bro. I go psychotic site. Well reading tonight
Fuck yeah, before I especially what the bitch has been doing bro stalking me and all like bro
I need you to tell me something bro. Don't tell me what I want to you. Tell me what you see
Okay, so king as a king of coins and so you are you are in this like a button of energy
You are able to yeah, you know, he's he's got some coins in his hand. He's like you're seeing some gold you got you got
Um, you know, you got a lot of things going for you already, you know, and you're able to like create abundance, you know, you
know, the king of pentacles is always able to create abundance and
Yeah, make ideas flourish. Okay. Oh, we got here. Who's it? Oh, I want we got the king of pentacle and queen of pentacle
I love you. You know, there's a I don't know. This is more of a ratchet kind of queen of pentacles, but
You
This yeah, these are these are the Disney villains cars. So but yeah, so this is a queen of coin
Yeah, I got the king of coins. And so this is kind of like these explain it to me. Sorry
Well, I mean so the the pentacles have to do with like, you know, the earthly
things the material of this world and you know making money and and
Manifesting and so
It just it looks to me like you know, you have it's like you you're due to you're due to work with this woman
Like there's a couple. It's like, you know, there's a couple there somehow. I don't know if you're dating somebody or
You dropped off, but I'll just do one more for you. I'm T. Y. If you're watching
Three of swords. Oh wow this heartbreak. Okay, big heartbreak, you know, this heartbreaking will heal
You know it always can heal, but yeah, you you've had your heart broken
We only have Tom Selleck. Oh, we have Tom Selleck in the chat
Oh look at Tom Selleck LD
Is that LD
Yeah, well, it's Tom Selleck. I think look at the mustache. I can't fucking hear
Hold on. Okay
But T. Y. Yeah three of swords. There's even heartbreak. I'll give you some advice for the future
T. Y. Your advice for the future says
Okay, this says
It's gonna be the nine of swords, okay
Nine of swords is like this is like some solitude extending some time thinking
You know, there's you know, there's a lot of even the worrying a lot. It's like, you know
You don't want to worry as much. Just like just like a try meditating try a deep breathing
Yeah, let me turn the light real quick. Let's take it up. It says, is something dark lurking
just out of sight? The night of swords, card represents worry and dread. Don't let fear
overwhelm you. When you confront your fears, you may just find that there is no need to
Yo, yo, what up? Can you hear me? Yeah, all right, what's up, bro? Now you've been man
Just working man, just trying to get along here, you know life type shit
You get them bills paid bro. You got fucking a quervo fireball old trustee
You guys hang out. Hey, when do you get it? When do you just say a mustache? I mean, it doesn't look bad. I guess
No, you know how I'm a little upset. I was upset psych didn't draw a picture of me
I saw he was drawing pictures of everyone. I want to I want a portrait
Yeah, I'm driving. I'll draw a picture
Oh, yeah
Marker, I want to get a good, you know
I need you on full screen. I'm gonna go full screen for just a minute. Okay. There we go. I'm drawing a picture of them guys
Oh, should I take the sunglasses off? I don't know. Yeah, I got you. Okay
Okay
Well, you do you do like a quick sketch or what? Yeah
Yeah, he's been like drawing pictures of everyone. I'm like damn
I saw he did one for Gotti and I think JT and a couple of other people. I was like, oh, I want to picture it on
Yeah, uh
It's kind of weird the mustache is like different because you don't know it happens the first time me yeah me seeing you have one right
Yeah, I've been growing up for like a couple weeks now
I think Tom Selleck, right exactly bro. I'm a stunt double
Magnum PI
Yeah
Yeah, I was I was trying to because a psych hasn't seen the the video of that full they got shot on the strip
Yeah, that's crazy, man
Any updates on that any updates on that or?
We'll try to save you know
No, I didn't that she ain't gonna fly in Nevada. They got death penalty out there, bro
You ain't gonna gun down a husband and wife and claim self-defense in front of the blog. Yeah, yeah in front of the Bellagio
I think the he's gonna maybe like, you know, knock at the death penalty just because he turned himself in like type shit
I mean, I don't mean shit
Fuck that. Yeah, that don't mean that don't mean see it because he turned himself in that's still getting the dip and yeah
That don't mean
Damn about this
Well, I mean, at least he did go on the run and he caught like, you know months later touch it
I don't know. So what there ain't no way I would have shot two motherfuckers a little alone
But if I did bro out there ain't no way I'm turning myself in
Guys ready
Oh, wait, can you pull it back a little bit? I want to get a screenshot. I get the whole thing
What is is that my dog? Yeah, why do I have pepperoni nipples?
Yeah, that's perfect man. Thank you. I appreciate that. I love it man. Good. I got a black eye. I
Love it definitely gonna make that my fucking profile picture from now on
Awesome. Thank you. Thank you. I really appreciate that. Well, I'm so left out. I was like, man, he's doing it for everyone, not for me
Thank you. I'm trying to do it for everyone. I'll do it for Chris K. Chris K wants you
Yeah, Chris K used to hang out when I lived in Vegas, man being Chris K. Close. Hi, bro. My boy right there
Yeah
Hey, there's Lea
Nice check going on
as they want to go on
This is like maybe a little, you know, little ruthless, you got a lot of energies coming together.
Is that like a Disney set?
Yeah, this is Disney, it's a Disney, uh, the seven of wands.
As this is the villains at seven of ones it says seven ones
Which suggests you're facing tough competition if someone's trying to get between you and your goals hold your ground
This isn't the time to let down your guard. Keep your defenses up. Give it your all. Yeah, so, you know
I appreciate it. Yeah, you were behind your defense, you know, just be be like a
Don't know. I know it's like if she's striking you if you post her photo on your show. Just don't post her
Don't mention it post your photo on your show like it. She'll give her a reason to strike you basically or else, you know
You know she'll keep be agitated and she'll feel like it's a thing personal
She'll keep fighting just like speed starver of the attention and energy, right? Okay
Cool guys, how are we doing 1151? I've been on for like four hours. Hey
That
Carousel, yeah, if I blink 182 off of the Cheshire cat album Chris K got me into it
And it's like on my playlist now. I listen to it like every day man. If that song goes hard
Cool, it's K. You're inspiring
Yeah, yeah, we're like a lot of the same music and shit like that punk rock, you know
Like he's got a real taste for that West Coast punk rock
Shit you fucking you know East Coast East Coast hardcore dude. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I mean you're singing misfits man
I'm in Jersey where they're from bro
I've seen a missus a concert have you yeah, okay, let's go
Nice
Fuck with me, bro, don't just tell me but drop it whatever bro make sure I'm just getting back started
Come on everyone
Find you I find T wise channel. I mean if Jamie if you can find T wise channel and share that'd be great
I'll be sure to find your channel and I will always share on my channel for sure. I'll from for sure
TY
So
Are you gonna do something special?
No, I'll put your name in and find it
or not because some people can't find you bro some people can say they can't find you so you know
put your channel name in the in the chat you just type you put at is your channel has a
like a like the at name yeah just type it's channel name chat what if i can't see it
you know i'm bad it's not a link just type it in chat just type the channel name in the chat
bell will come up people can search the channel name
I'll find it that way
Let me try to see you. All right. Hold on. It's like what you're not drinking tonight. Come on buster. Yeah, I'm drinking
I'm having a heart heart of the baby
Count it
Let's go back. It's like you can post it in that. Yeah, drop it in the back
You want to say hi dookie? Oh, yeah, I still got that dog
He ain't going nowhere, bro. Where that's my ride or die, bro
Right, right, you know, I fucking take him to Fremont Street. He coming with me everywhere. I go
Very sweet, I love that dog
Did I miss I suicidal tendencies play out here, bro, I missed it I
See was that a tendency to hey, um, Jamie's Cowboys is dropping link for you for you. It's
Oh, okay. Appreciate it. Jamie's cowboy. That's my guy man. What's up, James cowboy?
And you know he was in appreciate I appreciate
Cowboys
Oh, nice. Yeah, they were able to pull the the channel link cuz they got the wrench
Yeah
He's doing the channel since the beginning
I
Urban urban cowboy urban struggle. Hey, Chris. Don't be going live
He's on rumble. Yeah, you're on a different platform
What's rumble, what was that? Yeah, it's different. It's like you two kind of
Streaming platform that you can have like freedom of speech
Yeah
So like right on here like I you know
I have to buy my lip because I don't want to say shit to get a second trouble with this channel type shit
Yeah, okay
Because YouTube
I mean like honestly fuck YouTube
Yeah
I know
To know more bro without getting fucked by somebody bro this shit is so weak bro. It's shit. I got so weak man
I don't want I don't want to fuck it. I'm not gonna be censored. You know, I mean I say what I want
And if you two
If I ever get like bid on like a streaming platform and they're gonna be YouTube
I'm gonna have I'm gonna have people watching ads on my mother platform YouTube. You've you missed you missed your opportunity for my shit
Okay, that's why that's why I wish you look that's why I wish you look site cuz this shit this shit right here
YouTube is fucking big these fools will bet you like like that
Yeah
I've been bad. I've been bad. Yeah, I'm in trouble in YouTube. So I'm confident like
One spiteful asshole coming up here porn bombing you like you're done like, you know, I know I
I've been formal over a hundred times LD. Okay. Yeah, it's
Never had a problem for about a hundred times and we're about a hundred times
People flash now is just a fucking like just a chat and fucking I think I think I'm when I got banned
I made another one and like it got banned instantly afterwards because they knew was the same the same thing me
So I literally had like go on my phone like do with that. I different IP address and shit and fucking make another one yet
So hey, that's it. Yeah, listen, I don't I wish you'd look on this platform, bro
But you know, it's you why she got it
You I look
Try out mine. Yeah, I'm pretty sure
Thank you, Jamie and Jamie subs everyone else subscribe to the trap. We'll see how
It's like, you know how many times you fuck want to sleep and you know what you left me on here type shit if you feel
You do you realize I got to pull my dick out and you know, I mean
No, I'm just saying I'm going to show my day
I'm saying he's very respectful of the host
Yeah, I would never do that. I would never do that regardless. I would never do that to anybody
You know what I mean? So yeah
If we go backstage, can you show me your dick?
If we go backstage
It was a joke. It was a joke. Okay, never mind
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you
Yeah
Yeah, and you get pulling it up. Hey, did you did your lectures here to you? I say I did you like her or to do
Don't even fuck with me no more bro. She don't even come holler at me man. What's up DJ?
What's up, man? You don't even know me no more. What's up girl? Hey site you got a kick
Yeah, I don't I don't kick. I mean, I just use YouTube. I'm very focused on you
I mean, I might branch out and other streams or other
Platforms because I can do multiple streams off of a stream yard. Yeah, I can do that
I can do as many as I want actually stream on, you know, you can multi-stream on YouTube and kick cuz it's kind of the same fucking
You know, yeah, you could have them all going at the same time rumble kick YouTube and like it's all the same stream
But you're streaming on different platforms the same time
Yeah, I mean if I had I mean I just had the audience here
I probably would have an audience on there those streams for like a quite a while
He runs kick I didn't know that
Like some of the people that I see you know KC IP is KC IP
Right. No, you mean like you see I mean content God like
No KCIP it's like fucking that you get you get
Like promoted on kick you get verified on kicked where you get month you get fucking hourly money
And I've seen screenshots of some of these fools that are fucking with the case at like $200 an hour
Like just a stream
Yes, and I'm like but how are they making the moneys it off ad revenue like is there like you know advertisements or something
There's got to be someone there like monetizing it
It's like it's it's kick money that you get because the fucking guy Mr. Ross or whatever it's fucking some like millionaire or whatever
Like he's getting like here's the thing here
You know you want me to break it down like fucking kick has a steak which is a gambling fucking app platform
Yeah, so people that have KCIP are like required like if they stream they have to like stream like they're
Gambling on steak like at the end of the stream like for like an hour or 30 minutes and like play it off
You know, I'm being honest they play it off like oh, I just won this money
It's like to get people that are stupid to be like oh well
Maybe I'll make a make a steak account and try to gamble on steak and fucking you know, I mean, that's what it is
Okay, you know, but these motherfuckers like they get like like ice Poseidon fucking
Yeah, they have you know KCIP, which is like fucking you know me like $200 an hour
So if you street for like, you know, I mean that you do that Bailey type shit
And like some of the people that they give this KCIP to like they don't even know how to like I
Mean, I don't know if you know how to do it, but I can I do but like fucking
If you're like IRL streaming with your phone with a selfie stick you got there and like you get a bad signal and like
It'll go to like a fucking your clips
So you have like an RTMP server setup with the fucking with your OBS on your computer setup
You know these fools don't even have that they just like rip like the people some of the people that have KCIP are fucking stupid
You know, they just said they don't deserve it and they don't fucking they don't fucking uh
If I had it, I would fucking be happy about it and like fucking not take for granted type shit. So that's it
One of electric you can when I hang out electric, you know Chris K and TY and
Tom still like son double
You're talking about the Tom South the porn star
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Type yeah, you're gonna get my Magnum PI
Piece of pussy over here tripping bro, I'm downstairs bro fuck this motherfucker
Were you from Ty you from New York
Nah, man, I'm from Texas Houston, Texas. Oh
Nice man. He's living on a San Angelo for a little bit
Oh, you did
When I moved out of Vegas, I went to San Angelo for a little bit. It was nice, man
I like Texas once you guys legalize weed. I definitely go back
Man, I I said this like since I was a kid, bro
They wouldn't this would probably be the last state that legalized Texas if they
Man this I'm telling you man. That's why they got them signs. You already know don't mess with tell you
No, this state is bro. These mothers. I like it. They ain't gonna think you're actually going with the problem be honest with you
I don't
I don't I've been saying it for for three days
Texas is so against the federal government that like even if they made it legal federally Texas would probably still outlaw it fucking
They would they would
You're a hundred percent right bro
They would they would you're right. Well a thousand percent right they would
It's funny, you know, because like, you know, I grew up on the East Coast and it's like, you know
And on the East Coast when you say you want to like smoke a pig. We're talking about like, you know
Killing a cop in Texas talking about barbecue. Yeah
California talking about how he said about that woman
Hey for you, bro. Yeah, where you staying? Where you staying now? I'm in Jersey
Oh, you're in Jersey. Okay. Yeah, I was living in Vegas for a couple of years
That's how I know Chris K. It's from when I've been in Vegas and I was in Arizona for a little bit
Arizona's fly to a man. They got legal weed legal guns
Like yeah, I liked it out there, man. But yeah once once Texas legalize that shit. I would definitely go back
San Angelo was cool
Yeah, it's like
Yeah, I'm not coming on it man
Telling you man. I don't I'm 46 now, bro
It is little since I was a kid. I was like man
I always said we all said it out here like this might be the last thing if they do it
I don't see you man. I don't will be rich. I mean, I don't I don't see it
They're holding out man. They're they they they're holding out
Yeah, they are bro
They won't budge out here, bro. Just like gambling, bro. They won't even put we got to go to Louisiana man when we want to go
You know, you know, we got to go to Louisiana when we want to gamble. I
Didn't know that I'm a big gambler. I mean living in Vegas. I don't really gamble too much
You can't you can't live in Vegas if you're a big time gambler, man
Yeah, it's real. It's real too. What's your game? How you like you like playing craps or what's your game?
Man, I like sports bed man. I do on my
Man it's just right now. It's done now because the NBA final, so I
Were you rooting for you were you rooting for Oklahoma or the Pacers?
Oh, I thought I thought okay. See we're winning. Yeah
When he tore his AC out the first quarter, bro, that didn't really give him no chance
I knew I knew they were done for sure
I'm a I'm a Nick's fan man. And like yeah when when Tatum smashed his fucking Achilles. I was jumping and
I knew y'all was gonna do though. I thought y'all were gonna win the way Boston just everybody
No sport Boston just didn't feel like that Boston team. I started seeing in the first series
Dan y'all go
But Orlando, bro, I'm like god damn
I mean, all right, man, all they got is Tatum. They just got Tatum
That's why the next fucking smoke them by like 40 points. Yeah
Once they were done, they were done. They crumbled fucking crouton. Yeah
Yep, and they just got rid of what's called. They just traded a
What's my boy
Come on, anyways, Keetal. I remember they just got but they just tried they just they just got rid of
What's his name, man?
Anyways, man, I'll say but they just got so they just got rid of yeah, man the block
Do you like for football the
Dallas or you like the Texans
Well, you know, yeah, if you know anything about Texas, you know, Houston, we don't fuck with Dallas, bro
That's we
When we get a lot of prison, bro, when the Texans play the Dallas Cowboys, bro, it's a riot, bro
That's how bad it is, bro
Hey, all bullshit aside, bro, it's alright
that's how bad it is up in Houston and Dallas
I'm a Giants fan, I fucking hate Dallas
I hate the Eagles the most but
The cowboys, bro, I hate the motherfuckers
CJ Nico Collins, you know Texans got a squad like the Pittsburgh Steelers they want to they've always been one of my things
Yeah, one of the best teams. Yeah, yeah, they used to be they used to be they need to get back to that steel curtain man
Yeah
Yep
Hey, the fucking Giants fucked up. They traded shake one bro to the Eagles
Yeah championship to man say go on run man. I never thought Kansas City, but they fuck me out of so much money
I never thought they'd come with a gun like that. They look so fucking bad, bro
They look so bad that front line got to them. They could man. They got to them all night, bro
That game was over in there. I'm here in that that game was over bro damn near by half time, bro. That shit was over
Yeah
That game was open the second half, bro. That's he was done
Fuck Kansas City cheese bro fuck past my home's bro type shit. Does that make sense? Yeah?
It was like I hated both teams. I don't want either of them to fucking win
I'm gonna go to the hotel and make them I make them not be able to be able to sleep
I fucking hate past my home's dog. I'll throw hands with that fucking that fucking bitch
fucking
No, it's cool, dude
Don't say that my show
No, listen, I don't like Kansas City. Like these motherfuckers
All the calls they pay the refs to fucking get the calls and shit be like
Fuck them. I like a happy dude to see them fucking to lose me like 20 to 0 at the fucking half
Hey, that's what what you who is that crazy guy on the giant set smoke crack in the 90s and shit. What the fuck is his name?
He showed up to a game in handcuffs because the prostitute lost the tough key and like he showed up to a game in handcuffs
The fuck was his name?
I can't remember
Like I really don't know
Okay
Lawrence Taylor Lawrence we need a Lawrence Taylor would hire hookers for the opposing team
So they'd be too tired like during the game the next day
We have
How are we all doing, everyone having fun still?
I'll save as long as I can, I have like another
playing in their beer left.
I have a good sandwich.
I'm having fun.
That's crazy, bro, I can't say that, you know,
you're tripping right now, because I said the F word
on YouTube, you're like, oh my goodness.
good. How are you? Yeah. Great. You seem like you're doing better. You were going through it,
but you seem like you've come the other side. Yeah, well, we go through ups and downs, especially
I've been
Listen, what is that?
I fucking shit. What do you got? What is that? It's just a cartoon. What's wrong, Paige? Oh, it's like it's like a filter
It's like a filter. I think
Yeah
Why don't you just come up?
Hold on let me suck page to go to page. Oh, no, what's going on? Oh, nothing. I'm good
I don't want to talk about anything here anyways right now.
Okay, gotcha.
It's just been shit that's been going on, but it's all resolving itself, it's just day-by-day
shit, right?
But things are kind of gotta-
Gotcha.
Love it.
Congrats on the new job.
Yeah, thank you.
I was just gonna bring that up.
It's been a really good time.
I'm actually enjoying it.
That's so cool.
It's like this little piece of heaven away from my house, right?
It's like rare when you can enjoy your job.
So that's pretty awesome.
Yeah, I love it.
And I get to go golfing whenever I want.
I like a really high like casework area. I like that. I don't like it when it's slow, so it works for me.
Yeah, slow time just goes, it lags. But if you're busy, that makes the day go by faster. That's awesome.
I golfed once, I dislocated my shoulder, so I never golfed again.
Really?
Yeah, I did a, I did a drive and my shoulder just was like, bink, popped right out.
I I feel like golf is the most egotistical sport ever made like the
Feel that you play on is like miles and miles long and the hole is this big and the ball is this big
Like it's just so egotistical
And you gotta be quiet like you can't be loud or
anything
No, it's golf. You gotta be proper, but you get shit-faced and fuck around you have to wear special shirt
I know I love John Dailey. He's the best golfer ever
You know what golf stands for they should golf the word golf. What does it stand for?
Is that a Robin Williams joke? Oh, yeah, I think it really is true. This is true golf stands for
gentlemen only ladies forbidden
That should be the theme for your channel, I'm just kidding
Oh, come on. I had to have I know lady. I've just laid ladies ladies here keep me in line
Or else that would just be I just be so just be mud-wrestling with the in a speedo
Women say, hey, you know, get out, take a shower, you know.
Save your face.
I mean, I wouldn't complain about the mud wrestling and the speedo.
That would be pretty entertaining.
Okay.
So are you down, L.D., are you down, mud wrestling with me?
I mean, yeah, but I don't play fight. I'm a wrestle to win
Okay, and I you can't just give up immediately. That's not gonna be fair. You know, I need a little bit of fight
I need a little bit of resistance
On his back like you win
I have to do the ring stage. We haven't the biggest stage in Vegas. Okay, except for her piece that she'll come back with you
Oh, shit. Oh
gosh
Hey, so yeah, we're having fun tonight. It's 11. It's 12 15 now
I know it's I was going so fast you had mac and cheese
I had macaroni cheese sandwich with a macaroni cheese grilled cheese sandwich.
Was that good? Oh, it's okay. I almost finished the whole thing almost already. Where is that from?
Did you make it or? It's like a grilled cheese um restaurant. Yeah. I want a grilled cheese
restaurant by me. I don't think they have one. That's lame. Yeah. That sounds amazing. Very good.
I like cold grilled cheese
Do you like cold grilled cheese?
I mean not grilled cheese, I mean mac and cheese
I like cold pizza
Cold pizza?
That's good
Cold chicken? I like cold chicken
Cold chicken?
Cold chicken
In the new name of my channel
The animation you got that's it. That's it's funny
Yeah, you like the Alex animation. I played it tonight. Oh, yeah, cold Domino's chicken tender. Oh, yeah, they're cold chicken tenders
I can eat my eating sometimes a cold cheeseburger tastes. Okay. This is certain. She's something to do something. Don't you know?
but
Yeah, cold cheeseburgers hit or miss
Yeah, sushi is always good cold right well
I mean like they kept for like yeah unless it's like tempura or like barbecue eel or something like that
I mean, it's it's all good. Have you ever had chicken katsu? Yeah, sorry good
That's even good cold. I love Chinese food called like especially low-main. I love cold low-main
Yeah, oh the newly added news a good cold. Yeah, this is good
Yeah, well, he's talking about like Panda Express like fucking put it in the fridge and like eat it right out of the fridge. I
Had no idea Panda Express is the people that invented orange chicken
Yeah, I had no idea just found that out the other day that they Panda Express invented orange chicken
some guy was like mixing Hawaiian food from California with like Chinese food
and came up with orange chicken yeah some some guy the guy that meant some
young guy the cream of some young guy yeah
I have but it just makes me laugh every time because I have the sense of humor of a 12-year-old boy
Enjoy it
Everyone's cammed up. It's awesome
Yeah
She's gotta change her sweater. You're so cute Paige. I'm not cammed up, but close enough. Yeah
My camera's at a really bad angle like it's too. It's too high because my screen's really big so it's like
Looking down at me. I'm a little
Yeah, you look at what there's a manjula. This is the manjula effect. I was like, it's like
That's I remember DJ like to have blonde hair now. She's a redhead
Yeah, I think about hair you can change it and being a cartoon you can change your hair like all the time
Huh are you like a DJ I was I was a radio DJ though not a club DJ
Are you are you are you broke from broken Jubal in the morning? I am not
they do the second date update they call people like if you don't get a call back from like a date
they'll call the date and ask why you didn't come back oh what went wrong it's so good segment i
bet that's yeah and they'll have the other person on the phone like listening
here looks weird but i bet it tastes good
No, I catch up on your mac and cheese. I I like ketchup on everything. Honestly, I could eat it on apples practically
Almost
Hot sauce too. I put Tabasco on my sushi
Tom's cell extension will don't hate it until you try it
Roll with Tabasco is delicious
Delish, that was a big load of ketchup on their psyche
Like two tablespoons of ketchup on one bite. It looks like you're eating like a doctor
Didn't agree
Ranch barbecue honey mustard all on one thing james cowboys
I don't know about all of them. I probably could do all of them. I'm a sauce person for sure gotta love sauce. I
Mean, what would you do if you had to eat dry food all the time like
You don't want to have no cheeseburger bro cheeseburger
Cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheeseburger, cheese
Like you go on there, you talk to a random person, right?
You fucking skip through and you fucking talk to random people, right?
Oh, like Omega?
Oh, I've never heard...
Oh, like, I've heard of Omega.
I've heard of Omega.
What do I do?
Like, when I stream on my shit, I fucking, when I'm all, you know...
Monkey out.
I fucking, you know, as long as it ain't some little kid, I skip, you know what I mean?
Do you meet people on there?
I'm like, hey, y'all want a burger?
Hey, y'all want a hamburger?
And I got these burgers and then y'all want a cheeseburger?
Hey, Jimmy, come on.
Like, why don't you come on camera?
Why don't you come on?
And they see me doing that.
You know what I mean?
They're like, that's not good.
That's fine.
Thank you for having me up.
But it's like 3.30 in the morning.
And I got to work tomorrow.
Good night, Aldi.
Thank you for drawing that picture of me, dude.
I really appreciate that.
You're welcome.
You took a picture.
Nice.
Yeah.
Thank you for being a friend the Mona Lisa shall be hit me up. Whenever Doug you got my fucking
Definitely
Good night, ladies everybody
With the sunglasses on you think
Yeah, he does. He's like going to bed. He's like I gotta go to bed puts it
man
Just take off your shirt
Take off your shirt take off your shirt down Chris. I don't understand the cheeseburger that is
Supposed to be like a sketch comedy thing like some fuck. Yeah, like some fucking crackhead
That's fucking it's trying to like get rid of his burgers and like a get some crack for it
Yeah, you got a itch faster you got a itch more yeah
Is it like, is it like, is it like, who's that got Bluto from Popeye or who's the guy that was like, can I have a wimpy or who's gonna have a cheeseburger today, I'll pay it today, yeah.
I think so.
Um, Chris K, if you had a monkey on your back, would you let him stay or would you beat him off?
Uh, like why, it depends if it's fucking a monkey I know.
That's a good answer, I like that.
You know like some fucking monkey
So you'd beat it off
But oh, if I was like a monkey trainer
I never met a monkey I didn't like well actually the ones that put throw poo at you. I'm not a fan of those guys
Well, I let you know
And the monkeys throw poo out their cage. Oh, yeah
Okay
That was in humble
Hey, listen a be here tomorrow night about 10 30
What's happening tomorrow what a what did I stutter motherfucker? Did I stutter?
What you afraid to come to this table at night
He's auditioning hey, you ain't afraid to have a black man steal for you are you
Hope you find your way on Compton Avenue motherfucker
Listen, you know, that's what I am a month. Yeah, I've been like a random person will come up. I'll be like hey
I'm like, hey, bro. What's up? Hey, be here tomorrow night, about 1030.
They're like, what's going on to 1030? I'm like, what, did I stutter? You know,
they trip out. They trip out. It's fun.
Oh, so you're reminding me over tomorrow at 1030? I'll be at your house.
Hey, listen, uh, hey, this is a, you know, I'm not trying to, uh, hey, I don't want to say it.
There's another call, but it's like a fucking offensive word.
I can come over?
Come on over and do the twist
Yeah
Love you so much
Guys, I think Chris is hitting on me. What's happening? I think so too. Listen. Hey, you can't listen when you can't pull it in here. I
Can't do it
I have to say the n-word he reminds me. I call him
I'll give it to you. I'll give it to you slowly. Hey Fred. Hey Fred. I'll just say now, you know
I'll just you know, I'll say we're like, hey listen when you keep pulling your day. Do you see a sign?
What don't say don't say yeah, yeah, I mean I'm not gonna fucking
Chocolate starfish and the hot dog flavored water. Yeah
There you go. I'm sorry. My daughter woke up. So I had to rip her back for a minute. Oh
Listen when you came pulling in here today, did you see a sign in front of my house and said
You know why you didn't see that time?
Because storage is anywhere in my business.
He's doing an acting class, I think.
We're doing an acting seminar.
If I don't come home, I'm going to get divorced.
I want to help you guys out.
But I'm trying to lose my wife, doing it.
Yeah?
You guys got to make some phone calls.
You got to call some people. We'll do it.
And get the fuck out of my house before she gets home.
Graveyard shift at the hospital.
The phone is in my room.
I suggest you get started.
Is that from a real movie?
Yeah, that's Pulp Fiction.
I was like, is this really happening right now?
No. I was like, I was afraid.
We are in Pulp Fiction.
I was afraid for my life, I mean.
I was, I was in fear.
A movie is like two movies in one.
When you were getting out of Pulp Fiction.
When you were getting upset about sports stuff earlier before I left that when you guys have ever started fighting
I would you were going on and reminded me of that one sit from fucking what is it called anger management when he gets mad
He's like
Moving in my head
Angry sharks are swimming in my head
I don't know if I've ever seen it
I'm so freaking fake and stressed.
Who's in it?
Oh, it's Adam Sandler and Jack Nicholson and.
Wait, what movie is it?
Anger Management.
Oh, Anger Management, okay.
Yeah, I don't know who that chick is,
but she's pretty renowned actress.
It's got Heather Graham, Heather Graham in it.
Oh, Heather Graham, yeah.
Yeah, and fucking, it's the funniest, funny part.
He's like
Anyways, what are you guys talking about that movie?
Why cuz I brought it up just now because you reminded me of the guy who gets mad and the fucking at the sports thing
That he's listening to in his headphones at the management meeting. He's like
He's trying to knock it out. Yeah, sirs flip it out to sirs vibrate and getting all red
Anyway
What's going on? Hey Justin
Hey, it's been a great day. It's you know, I think about 20 memberships in the past couple of days
Yeah
Memberships are nice because then they can't leave once they are
Yes, hotel, California. Yeah, and
What else? Oh, yeah, it's a lot of readings tonight a lot of readings. So
Good
What hey, where are you from? Oh, I'm from Canada
Shit, I live right near the beach
What beach
The fucking I'm in Vegas. Oh, there's no beach there
I know I was fucking is it's fucking a joke
It's a joke
Yeah, like try to try to say like me like right near the beach boy
Right near the beach boy
No, that was that was sloppy
I haven't practiced you gotta let me practice at least come on
Take your time. I'm not gonna do it
No, but I'm doing it
I've been in the babies like five years
I'm burnt on this shit honestly. I'm burnt
Listen, I'm gonna listen. I'm gonna move down to it's like I'm gonna win with like
He was you're gonna move in with psych. I think you better ask him on a date first
DJ like you look like you're
Blending in with the tapestry tapestry and all of our bedrooms
I was just looking to change my background. I can't decide what to change it to though
Yeah
Well, anything you do has been cool so far. So surprise us. I'm sure we'll be just we'll love it. Oh
You're too sweet
Hey, what happened with what's with your president to drove? What happened that guy?
He's gone. That's all the matters. I want to talk about him. Why the fuck can we talk about him?
Do you have now is better right I guess no, it's not but we're not talking about politics
Yeah
Sorry, I'll just get all fired up and I just got un-fired up
I hear you. I hear you because I'm in a listen. Uh,
I you know, I like I like Canada dude. I everybody I've met on
The internet and in real life from Canada are cool people. That's what I'm saying
Yeah, well, I like America
I you know Canada like fucking like their allies seem nicer for some reason. We're not that's the thing like we're really
We're like low-key ignorant high-key nice
Really?
You're pretty smart Paige. Yeah, I don't see you ignorant
I have my days
Well, yeah
When I when I meant ignorant I meant like like like rude like rough and like like abrasive and like we can be really like assholes
Oh, okay. We call it ignorant. We call it ignorant. I don't know ignorant. I know ignorant. Yeah. Yeah, okay. I
Like I don't have that reputation like Americans do
No, you write polar bears and drink maple syrup
Right, I like the fucking the pot leaf Canadians lag. That's just dope
Yep
Justin I remember Santa Cruz skateboards, too. I used to have one
I was a kid. I
Still have some of the old fucking og skate shit and like
It's vintage now, and I just kept it. It's just in my closet. It's just like a relic
Did you have a pogo ball remember those pogo balls?
I didn't have one, but like if my friends did, I know what you're talking about.
Do you bounce on it?
Oh my god, those were rad.
Oh, go ball.
I remember that, I remember one time the, because it was a plastic and the ball popped out one time.
It was like, fucked after that, like it never like poga away.
You never pogo'd again
Yeah, I mean it would but it would like always like pop out and it was like scuffed. You had to like get a new one
It's a little pogo ball that couldn't
Yeah, okay. Here's the quiz. Anybody know what this design of my background is from
It looks like it's from like fucking minecraft not not minecraft. It's a game though. It's an old-school game, right?
No, not a game. Really?
It's something in real life
That sounds made up because that doesn't look like real life shit
Yeah, I thought it was like some type of like a car again
Like are we just all fucking with each other tonight? I'll give you a clue. It's a carpet, but where is it?
Where's the special carpet from? Oh
Is there's a fucking like a like a haul like a
To give poor games though isn't it for an activity?
What the background is based on that, right? It's a carpet. Yeah, but like
The mind calendar a little bit. Okay the mind calendar. I have no clue. This is where I'm not smart apparently
No, no, this is a really obscure
This is a hard one
Does anyone in the chat know?
Circus circus Jamie's Cowboys that is a good guess
But, not correct, but that's a great guess.
Somebody from Vegas? Or some golf course or something?
No, not Disneyland.
Lego? No, I'm kidding, not Lego.
I have no clue.
Okay
It's random. It's the Portland Airport like nobody
I know that was underwhelming God I suck. I mean you go to fucking Portland Airport on a daily basis or what?
No, okay. What about this one you guys will know this one
That's been the shiny. Yeah
So
This is a random thing that Hagrid started it on his show puzzle box
He would this was his background and then the next season he got
Another carpet and then I got carpets is my background. It's just
random, but
Circus circus, I'd like to see what their carpets like. Let's look it up
My buddy used to live in this basement suite and it was an older house and it was fucking crazy carpeted like I can't remember what the pattern is called
But anyways, and it was like textured and it's soft and it had gold lights down there
And it was really really trippy so the plug in there was just carpet everywhere different kinds of carpet on the walls
And on the floor and we did mushrooms in there one time and it was probably one of the worst trips I've ever had
Oh really was it it wasn't a good trip?
No, because I couldn't find somewhere to be I was like it was just too much going on in one area
I was like I don't know what thing to be near what this is it became overwhelming
I see yeah
And the cops came there and everything so that was very fun too. Oh
First time I did mushrooms page was at Disneyland. That's crazy
Yeah, first time I did mushrooms in my friend's grandma's trailer
Okay, that is crazy
Okay, you can get shrooms out here in Vegas you can't you can
What I know I know I know it's from anywhere
Get him to the Greek he's like turns out it's quite easy to get drugs in Las Vegas
Well, I felt pretty crazy I felt like you know, I gotta be I gotta be in the vibe to do that shit though, you know
Yeah, it's always an energetic vibe anything like that
Sorry to fear less death less after doing DMT. Is that a thing is it supposed to make you come to terms with?
Well, it's a it's a release in the body naturally when you're close to death. Oh, that's right
That's right. I've heard that but scared to die. I'm just scared
I think that the state the thought of how you died, you know what I mean?
I think it's not like yeah, like I don't want to suffer. That's the thing
Because suffering didn't go along with it. I wouldn't be so concerned. You know what I mean, right?
Well suffering goes on more with life than with death. I mean death once you once you pass death. It's like
It's very peaceful too, so it's you know
Well, it's like no matter how horrible or terrible is it at least the pain does
Exactly
Well, we're all guaranteed to shit eat and die
Do you remember being on DMT? Do you remember it?
Well, yeah, I mean I've been doing it a few times lately
And like do are you having kind of thoughts or is it more of a physical high?
Oh, it's like a lot or physically
I'm really thinking as much. It's like it's like it's just like the visuals take over like
If you watch music videos
Yeah, it's crazy. It's just great. It's like it's a very very powerful it lasts a short time
Today I did it I wasn't really I wasn't really
And the best mindset have you done salvia before? Yeah, no
Yeah, I was just I did it once to and never again
But I was just wondering if it compared how it compared to that or because that was really fast too
It felt like it lasted a long time, but it was only like a minute. Yeah
Yeah
That kind of like DMT it doesn't last that long does it that's like 10 15 minutes
You feel like you have some residuals though from it still
It might there might be you see you never know it's because
You never know how long will affect you or like how it affects you. It's like it can just change you
It's just like change your like
Yeah
I mean, I'm gonna talk you pot too. I did a bunch of hits. I took a spiritual bath today
And I have a beer my son of the me I'm finishing this last heart like sorry the minute try to see if as long as I can
Did DJ, did any patient ever tell you of a near-death experience?
Um...
Let me think on that one.
Nothing's jumping out, so I don't think so.
I mean, I sat with a lot of people when they died, so...
They didn't get a chance to tell me about it afterwards. I just held their hands, you know?
Wait, hold on.
Let me can I read your cards real quick?
Electric can you read your cards me? Yeah
Chris's readings. Oh, I didn't know that. Okay. Sure. Yeah
Who eyes you know, it's like a Smith, what is that?
Smith no, yeah
Hello, no, listen don't lie
No, Smith I
Can't you know I can't do it if fucking if I hit the nail on the head and you fucking lie about it
I'm sure he's messing with me
Are you doing the acting class again?
How did you get how did you guess he's turning his dj like this man? Yeah
Please
That would be a funny skit if you were a tarot reader, but like you couldn't shuffle
Or like you just took an hour to shuffle
Look at those kitty eyes. You look like a sphinx kitty
I
Think about kitty eyes
Yeah
Damn
Oh, he's doing a whole layout you're you got a sister no
You have a maybe it's you do you have a save a daughter no
Well, then who the fuck is your mom like is your mom have somebody that she watches over
No, I don't think so
Okay, maybe wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute. Are you actually tapped into like my energy or psychs or something?
No, there's the
Maybe it's you are you fucking why are you like why are you like looking at somebody else's?
relationship
Looking at someone else's relationship how?
Like from a distance and should you like fucking you want to be these these
These people like cuz they did this went on like that these people you know
No, actually, they just went somewhere. No
think that I think you I think that they there is but yeah you got a you're
dad you're dad like was the was like the main one I don't know if he's still
Does he do this something with snakes?
No
There's a lot of one time we went to like a county fair and I held a snake
Cuz it fucks my shit up like I'm not gonna wait. I'm not lying. I wouldn't I wouldn't lie. I wouldn't fuck with you
But we did go to a county fair once and I held a snake my dad took me there
Right and he fucking he held you on his shoulders
I don't remember that part.
I can't do it, I can't do this reading dude.
Why are you mad at her if it doesn't resonate with her?
I'm hitting this shit, I'm hitting it and she's like, oh no.
And so I can say I'm fucking hitting it like, yes it is, right.
It's true.
You and I both know this fucking channelers,
that's not fair to do to her.
And you know that.
And you know I'm not fighting with you, but I will if you want.
But just don't, that's mean, you know that.
If I was reading you and you come I wouldn't come at you. Maybe that's why I said you connect with someone else's energy
Did you ask to chat if maybe they would resonate with some of them because that can happen too and you know that
It's a lot of energy is getting up in here, right? And if message I say it again. I miss what you said. I miss what you say
Not gonna repeat it. You just know better
Calm down you're good
Somebody appreciate this, fuck that one, right?
There's something a lot with your dad.
I don't know what's going on with your dad.
You said you fucking don't have a sister.
Your dad has other kids, so for somebody else.
With somebody else.
Like, does that make sense?
Well, my dad has me and my brother.
And then he became gay, and so then he didn't have any more kids because he was having man sex
So it doesn't produce any children
That could fit with the card
Huh no go ahead
Good
No, it's like you feel like you don't you try to like fucking know you don't you don't want me to like read your shit
I'm like a really sensitive empath. I'm pretty much an open book
Maybe I have like a stone on oh, maybe it's my ring I'll take it off
Okay
Um, so, you know, is there a, I mean, I don't know who it is, somebody that like passed
I mean, how did
Actually, you remind me of my friend who just passed away
You look very very similar to him
Okay
So, okay, so he was younger don't tell me what happened. Let me see if I can get it
Tell like think about what he's what what happened?
Is that can you that yeah
I'm trying not to be invasive and tap him, but I guess-
What is the, what is it? Did he, did something broke? Broke, broke down?
Yeah.
No. Is that what happened?
I guess you can say that. That's one way to put it.
It wasn't a,
no, it wasn't like a heart attack.
Something which, so he got scared. So something happened, like it wasn't a,
was it normal, a normal like way to die?
Right
It was a weather weather
No, no you were closer before
It's okay, you know you don't have to know all the answers. It's okay if you don't know all the answers
Sometimes it's hard to get specifics, you know, you get more of a general read
So I don't know is it is his name Brandon?
No, well, who's that?
The only Brandon I know is a a friend of mine from high school
All right fucking you
So somebody you knew fucking just passed away
Me good
Yeah, I want to say I can tell you the only thing that I know is that I heard that it was from pneumonia
But like nobody I don't really know the answer. So that's maybe why you couldn't pick up on it
Yeah, that's kind of like
Determined I mean, how do you just randomly catch pneumonia?
don't know and I he was sick and then he's like 52 and then he passed away from
pneumonia like that's really rare that's pretty young I mean people do pass away
from pneumonia that's not rare but at that age it's rare you know usually it's
patients that are older or something
I mean, there's just somebody that's been trying to like get you into like going growing like a
You're a little like fucking like a garden
Or no
I'm not hitting it
That's okay
You're trying hard
Nobody's been trying to give me to grow a garden. No, but I should you know, you don't you don't you don't try to grow like vegetables
No, my neighbor does that right outside my window. So
Every time I go to the bathroom I stare at her vegetables growing
Is your name with like something with an M?
Yeah, I'm not getting by, you know, it's weird. You're not uh, it's not yeah
It maybe it's just like a off connection, maybe it's the sound
Or off or something
I don't think so page no
I could try I mean I could try again or whatever. I mean, yeah pay a page you read cards, too, right? I
Do a lot of things but I do yeah, yeah
What what?
If you do hers do you have anything for me page?
Yeah, see
See like you fucking you have to get in the vibe, you know, she knows you know, you know, I have to do same thing
I just wasn't like I
know
Yeah
You know what DJ? I'm gonna pull you a Queens of hip-hop because you're our DJ. Oh, sweet
I didn't even know you had a Queens of hip-hop deck. That's right. I got fucking crazy decks
They're all over the place. I've got like dark ones dirty ones funny ones fucking. Oh, wow
I'll definitely take the hip-hop ones or the dirty ones
I know right
So wow, that's a fancy like whole thing. It's a whole fucking thing. Yeah, the whole thing
I'm gonna do a spirit messages after what our spirit card after three as well
I'm gonna pull three of them, but so for these just give me a second
I'd like to tap into them and I just kind of get a feel for what's going on in your energy
Okay
Before I pull cards, okay
So I feel like there's a project that you're working on I feel like it's kind of just even brainstorming on something
That's a new idea that's going to be somehow either like
A promotional thing for a business for you or a business that you're affiliated with or like a new venture of sorts
I feel like you've got an opportunity and it's kind of was just like oh you thought about it
Just as a thought and laughed it off
But the more you thought about it and the more persistent this offer to the person who's giving you this offer
It's like really wanting to either work with you or
or is very interested in what you do and would like you to do work for them there's something
going on with that where I think you're going through this transition where also you might not
be so comfortable in your home life right now but not maybe like with the people that you live
because you could live alone I don't know but just maybe the place that you're living at I don't
know if there's like issues with it or I'm sure yeah there's issues with the neighbor probably
I want to tell you that that may not get resolved unless there's like authorities involved for some reason. I'm seeing that I don't know why.
Yeah, he's a psychopath and really not a good guy. It won't get resolved.
I feel like he's super malicious. I'm getting like that like old nebbercracker next door like get off my lawn just an old disappear.
Yeah, but funny thing is he's like younger than me but he is like that's how he is, yeah.
Like he like he stole my garbage cans. Who steals garbage cans, right?
And like I'm his block my car in so I can't get out like just he's a miserable person
He's very petty. He's just very petty
Yeah, let's just petty like good, you know
Like steal your cat and drive it three blocks or four blocks and then possibly
Leave it there and be like, oh, I got you cat. You know what I mean? Yeah
Um, also, I feel like...
Is there somebody that's interested in you but, like, you aren't interested in them?
And you kind of just found out that they were interested in you?
And, like, it really bothered...
Kind of just threw off to, like, the dynamic of your guys', like, friendship or relationship
because you're not... it just is awkward a little bit now.
In any way like a business it's some sort of relationship of sorts
Just like I don't know if it's a to be a story you go to every day that you interact with the same cashier
It could be someone that lives in your neighborhood. It could be you know what I mean?
It's somebody that you yeah all the time that you're not okay. Okay, who's just kind of taking your like your kindness for like
Like an invitation, you know, I mean like vulnerability in a way and yeah, I kind of think so
Um, so we've got respect we got Queen Latifah coming out. Oh
Yeah, the Queen herself
What's your favorite Queen Latifah song? I?
Don't have one okay. Well, I guess homework is is that oh gee you've heard her music though, right or just watch track. Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah
Okay, so whatever song comes to your mind first when you think of that
That song is the one you're supposed to listen to and see whatever meaning you get from it that resonates, right?
But okay like quick gist what it means in this book
And then I'll give you your message. Okay. Thanks for letting me tap into your energy. It's a good time. Yeah
Your energy smells like cinnamon
Or is that fireball does it?
Your energy smells like potpourri. That's the word for it potpourri. You remember that's potpourri
Yeah, it's just random like a random sniff. I don't my energy is really kind of mellow right now
Cuz I'm all up in it
There's only room for one hyper person in there
Oh, this book, this is...
Oh my gosh, Psych, Spinderella. That's hilarious. I didn't know that that was Spinderella.
Ahh, I like Spinderella too.
this is like super cool when I first got this deck I actually mean my girlfriend
right here and we're hanging out in the summertime and we're just like listening
to music all day and I'm like well I don't know how to use the deck and I
was like and I never look at the book so before I even looked at it I just wanted
to see what the cards were and I was like well just shuffle them and then
we'll just grab cards one for one and we'll listen to a song right and so we
just the whole deck and then I looked in the book and that's what you're supposed
You are psychic prairie page. See you are psychic
Okay, so it's like principles and resolve like hard-headedness and so just like standing up for it's like
She's just such a somebody you want to respect. She holds herself carries herself high. She presents herself. Well, she demands
There's no other way. There's no other choice. Um, and I feel like
Just maintaining your your poise and your you know reputation and even the shit with the neighbor
It'll resolve it will come to a resolve, you know dealing with hard-headedness and stubborn old fuckers
You know what I mean, or just like, you know trash cans feeling old neighbors
You have to rent the trash can or whatever they take and you gotta pay for it, right?
No, no, they just give us the trash cans here in the city. Oh
I lived in Calgary once and our neighbors, I don't know if the fuck ever happened to
our trash can, but like we never seen it ever again, we didn't buy any ones, so.
Yeah, I just know he did it because like he had two trash cans and I had three and then
the next day I had one and he had four.
I'm like, well I did the math, math is math and it works out.
Oh my god, such an idiot, just one second, so it's not the bunch of crap.
She's so bad dude, she'll look right at me
and like, I'll give her trouble and she'll don't.
She'll do a little burnout and run away
and like meow at me and then go hide.
Aw, what was she doing?
She was getting into trouble.
She's always fucking with stuff.
She steals like, she'll steal stuff off the counter.
She steals everything.
She's just like a little klepto.
She's a little klepto and she's a klepto kitty.
And she's just great.
She's like living with a little crack head.
it's like chris increases bike ever goes missing or the copper in my trailer i'm gonna blame the cat
i love it okay missy for this deck i'm gonna get you to oh hold on i can either just do a jump
card but i feel like when it's sometimes and actually not very often but in this particular case
I would like for you to be involved as like Chris is doing like interactively to certain decks
I would like to do that so that you feel like you're involved into it as well
Not just me doing just jump cards for you because okay
I'm gonna take that in a non-personal way and because this is a very special deck because it's spirit messages
It's a personal death. Okay, so we're gonna thank the energy out and you can tell me what
When you thought about it, I knew it. It could feel it. Yeah, I'm gonna do top bottom and middle
Okay, well that sounded wrong, but we're doing it
Yeah, y'all
Sandwich time
Okay, we have serenity
believe and take a moment
so
That's that card. I shall read it to you the most important relationship you can have is with yourself
This is a time to honor nurture and love yourself more by seeking out and wrote and what oh and removing any negative feelings and emotions
That are left over from yesterday. Don't let past issues and resentments interfere with your security serenity today
That word keeps coming up a lot today. Actually. I've heard it about 45 times serenity. Yeah
Huh, like I heard it on other readings today. I've heard it so many times 45 was a bit dramatic, but it's been a lot
so believe
Okay, there's a lot of blue it's funny. This is just a very um, it's a very mellow like
Pallet colors, you know what I mean? They're very there's vibrant cards in here
But these ones are just really mellow like you said you were feeling earlier
Yeah, now Trinity like that feeling of being kind of when you go under water
And it's like you're just underneath the water and it's just quiet
You can hear things, but it's far enough away. It's kind of you still have that that serenity around you and you're round
It's just finding that peace and that calm in the storm in the fucking chaos in with whatever
Situations going on because that's who you are. That's that poise. That's how you carry yourself, right?
You are serenity like you just have that in your essence or aura
So make sure that you don't forget that sometimes because I imagine you can lose your cool a little bit like the rest of us
Because we're all human, right? Oh, yeah
Okay, so believe. The force that works through your soul, determining what's possible or impossible,
sorry, the difference between success over failure and above all who you are is the power of your
belief. So believing in yourself and knowing these gifts and having them and not
in checking, it's like to check yourself before you wreck yourself, right?
Yeah, I like that.
There you go. So it's like that. And then we have take a moment.
And all of these people have their eyes closed if you hadn't noticed.
I saw that.
Is the whole deck like that?
No, it's not.
They're not all like that.
No, these guys have their eyes they're open all of them. Oh
Wow, but these guys are just like it's meditation
It's that letting the light in and the light out just kind of recharging being balanced
Finding that harmony closing your eyes and using all your senses otherwise to feel in here and connect again
You know getting in touch with yourself
Feeling it believing it and standing in who you are right because we all forget so taking a moment
Stop now. It's not the time to rush into a decision. You're about to make what did I fucking say when I started the reading
I always this is why I love doing what I spit my shit first because yeah
You're like I'm gonna take a minute to connect with your energy
Well, not that but just told you like I thought you were in the middle of a big decision that you were trying to make and then you
Just need to like you know weigh it out kind of sort of and this card clarifies it and I love when the last card does that
Cuz I look like a dipshit throughout the whole reading for the road. No, no, it's okay. It's okay. No, but it's just my style
Everybody keeps saying that I got another I had a reading. It wasn't a personal reading, but it was just like a group reading
Same thing that there's some decision that needs to be made, but I don't know what that is yet
I think something coming up then
Well, you know what we'll clarify we'll find out we'll find out maybe Chris can pull apart that cuz he was trying
My shit, I mean your father was there a lot in mind
So maybe she's like has to ask her father or was like that do something
Cuz like we can start connecting some dots right so
And now it's not the time to rush into this so before you make an important decision or she's like anything
Yeah, maybe here the father will trip on her if she does it. She's like scared to do it
because her dad will fucking be like, what are you doing?
No, my dad's really very supportive.
He wouldn't, he wouldn't trip on.
I mean, unless I was doing something illegal,
then he'd probably trip out, but.
Yeah, I don't know what it is, but it's, yeah.
DJ Electric's gonna be a street pharmacist.
I do know how to dose medication. That's for sure there you got
So it's like legally you can do it. So take a moment to pause and quiet your mind
So you can ask your soul for guidance before you act or move forward now
That's really funny because this is exactly what these people are doing. That's why all their eyes are closed
You know what I mean? They're all taking a moment. They're finding that piece. They're finding that serenity
They're trying to find that that belief in themselves to push forward
continue and know that they can do it believe that they can do it so whatever
you want to do you can do it obviously and that's t-shirt cliche shit page but
it's true you know it's true I've always believed that and you know I do believe
that that's good thank you thank you that that's that's good that I really do
Take time for yourself. Yeah, take time and just sit in the moment because I just been go go go and
like
Even today I was cleaning the house. I'm like
This is like a meditation because I haven't done this in weeks like I really needed to do that
And it was like I could make that even a meditation, you know
Well, it's funny because you said like well, I don't I don't actually know what your decision thing is about and it's like
Well, maybe that's what you need is this time to take a moment because you're so distracted with going with everything going on
You've had thought about yourself or listened in a while, right?
So it's like maybe that's it just taking that moment in that
Finding that calm place so that you can you can find out what's your need to hear
Do you know what I mean like outside of this just for you? Yeah
That's the message that I take from it definitely and Jamie's Cowboys is asking to if you can do hers next
Don't be afraid
Yeah, okay. Thank you
Good job
Thank you
Hey, Bish, what's up buddy? Just give me one second and I will do it.
Justin, you said in one of your chats that you had a job interview today. Good job.
Congratulations. I hope it went well and you get the job.
Proud of you, buddy.
Chris, why don't you pull like, why don't you see if you can see what we can do we just did now?
You can like
Into James
Jamie's cowboys. So like, you know cuz chatter do what you just did but see if you can have better luck tapping into Jamie
She's in blue in chat
Right. I don't have a
Sykes chat up. Let me get it up. Okay. Oh, yeah
And then I'll, I'll poke her too. Yeah. Actually, just one second. My name will be long.
I'm just going to chuck on Grace too.
Psyche, there you are. How's it going?
I'm taking a load off.
You're quiet tonight.
As high as a kite.
That was a high smile right there. That was so cute.
All right, let's see.
Did I download that video
What's up
Yeah, I'm doing I'm like 68 of 90 yeah, I'm back so
Download it yo
I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just going to shut the fuck up, I'm just
go to the store and we had to put note on the door like what's happening that's like he's uh brain
cells are gonna be well 75 75 they're good no they're like never they're gonna like not
they're not gonna be right back it's like brain retired no they are gonna be right back because
they're re they're finding new routes to get to the same place like destination they're rewiring
I'm trying to read these cards for here on Sykes right now.
Can you come through and not fucking trip out or what?
What happened?
I don't know what's happening.
Oh, no, I'm talking to my buddy.
Oh, Isaac, you talking to us the fuck?
Oh, oh, just mute us then.
No, it's cool page is gonna do Jamie's reading. No, no, he's gonna he's gonna do he's gonna start hers like I want to see
Yeah, let me get up into her cuz that was fair
Jamie's cowboy. Yeah
She said she had a question she said and then I'll do it for you
She said can you do my next page? Did I do the right thing? That was her question. Oh, did she do the right thing?
Maybe I should start did you want me to start it and then you can finish with retail cards or something because it's easier
Sometimes to throw some more. I mean, I gotta I mean the way you know
Or what's your style
She can't she can't like up or whatever
She could come up here. It's harder
Oh my gosh, I message speed I haven't heard back from her
What yeah, he does my girl
I know
Last time I talked to her. She was mad at me. So I don't know. I don't even I
Don't know why I
Mean if she's in chat like I gotta ask like I gotta know how many shuffle she wants
first
Like two or three
He's asking if you could come up here. Do you want to come up here? I'll do the reading for you like then
We're up all in the same little three
Okay
Seem like a solid three on that
You have an eyelash that keeps getting like curling under my other eyelash
I tried to put on fake eyelashes today Paige cuz I'm not good at it like I've never really worn them
Yeah, I really don't fuck with them, and I'm like all I did I think was get glue in my eye
Yeah, they didn't even look good they look stupid. I'm like they don't look good on me. No, this is not
They just don't work. I can't girl. I don't girl very well. No
I I can but
Not super girl, but I can't grow but not eyelash girl. I don't know
I've had eyelash extensions before and I like those but yeah
That was a long time ago. It's gonna be hard. You know, we're gonna have to wait for responses, right?
Okay, we'll come down and just relax. You're good. You can just give a reading you don't have to
You just start talking just start doing your thing like I'll be quiet. I'll be quiet
He's got like a sister or something
Music quick
Right
I don't know. I know who it is, but like somebody that you like and maybe it maybe it's your mom that you fucking me
there's multiple people though that that
Like three of them that like your mom a lot and something to do with the ocean
like you want to go to the ocean, I don't know if you live there, but
And you're attracted to somebody that's younger than you and
But
They're like, I don't know something like crazy happened
Recently and I don't know if she has a daughter and then
Maybe multiple feel like malt like a son also and that's it
That's fast
When Mike is really fucking muted, I can clarify some of these things for you.
You're actually quite spot on for her.
So just because I work with her all the time, so it's almost unfair for me to
read because we do like work sessions and shit together, right?
So anyways, I'm always, I can be tapped into her energy at all times, but so there
was recently an incident with like a, a very close, almost like sister-esque
You got you got the three women thing, right?
Like so there's there was a friend and her mom and Trinada who's passed away but lived in the house, too
There's this kind of you got the trio of the three feminine energies, correct?
And the falling out with one of them is correct as well
That was just recent and it was it was quite painful and
Also, she does live by the water. She lives in California. So you were actually quite spot-on
Yeah, and there's a I don't know. There's like something I
Mean it can't be that hard just you start trying to say a struggle, but I don't know what it would be
Yeah
Well like I said
No, that's good. And yeah, struggling with a lot of these all of these areas is exactly probably she feels like she's struggling
What what did I do? What could I do? You know what I mean? That's struggling with that acceptance or the thought or misunderstanding or you know, like
Just no clarity sometimes
It's like overwhelmed with something right now, I don't know. I don't know if it's a I want to say this yet
Does she have like kids?
no no kids well then who what who is this i'm overwhelmed and i have a kid
but no you're really spot on for jamie's reading you can read me later i'll let you
i'll maybe i'll let you tap in i'm just kidding i'm being sassy um jamie
Let's do okay, so I'm gonna do fall on his
Clarify his some of his cards. We're just gonna continue at the same rating because it's
Obviously spot-on, but I'm gonna do a spirit message for you, and I'm gonna do maybe a couple of these cards
I'm gonna do a little bit different than DJs
Because all of you are different and unique and you need different things
Okay, I know that this is just beneficial for you
Butterfly is Jamie who got what's a butterfly lately in the art or what?
Are you seeing a specific color butterfly that sees you comes I don't know sits on the truck window or
Just is always kind of around. You just always notice that that
Particular color or type of butterflies. I mean they're not a huge butterfly, but just a little one
Just yay or nay me in the chat
DJ do you want to just like I'll just pull it up
It's hard. It's hard when they can't when they're not here to talk. I love you.
It's alright. I don't mind.
Can you just watch the team she says yes or no?
I'm just going to keep going.
Yeah.
You just got, you got teammates up here, right?
We can help. That's what we're all here for.
Okay. This is for Jamie.
I know I'm not wrong about the butterfly anyway,
so she can say whatever she wants. I'm not wrong.
She has like somebody that she likes,
but the guy is younger.
Maybe maybe that's what it's maybe the guy like it has like a daughter
I don't know
Well, yeah, like she's like attracted right now. I
Got three that came out and they're perfect
That's crazy, you know, and it clarifies because you keep talking with this. Okay, so we have love
Love is the foundation of your existence and you're just
as worthy of receiving as you are of giving love and compassion.
While love can be a beautiful emotion it's equally a form
of an energy that propels you through life.
Okay.
And then we have the grounding yourself card.
Come out with that one as well.
And.
Being distracted, unfocused, tired, and irritated, and impatient are all signs that you are ungrounded.
Now is the time to become centered and allow spirit to help you ground yourself and reconnect with the divine source.
Okay, and then we have memories.
Which is your memories are like diamonds in the treasure chest of your spirit.
More and more memories are arising within you every day.
Remember the happier moments with your loved ones
who are here in spirit, or here in the spirit world
for neither time nor distance can stop energy
and the flow of energetic love
that you have for one another.
So this for me is definitely,
clarifying obviously that it's been really really difficult and or almost, you know, it's trying to be tried
You tried to cut ties with this person
you know that you felt a connection to and
Plutonic love because this wasn't a romantic relationship the one that he's talking about is something that's newer
I believe that's just fresh and kind of an idea
But that's what that's what that's what that's what I've the one that she's got
Yeah, she had a bad relationship
Well, it was her best. She had like with a friend
So like her heart got broken that way like that kind of love and then just was like closed off and just very you know
I mean, she's having a hard time opening it back up to anything or understanding closure
There's just the closures not there. You know what I mean?
So then grounding yourself in or both in or did I say or both in order to
Stabilize and recalibrate your equal like your whole your center to figure out. Okay?
This is why this happened and no one can tell you why Jamie you have to at some point
It's up to you to do this
you know what I mean grounds yourself and listen to your own heart and like you can look at it back in memories
But that's all it needs to be and don't think of the bad ones think of the good ones
And you just have to find a nice filing cabinet for them in your heart or in your head and try to find
Some just you know, it's like going through your stuff like get rid of the old and keep some keepsakes just the keepsakes
Don't fill your whole fucking attic or basement just because it's one person stuff and they don't have them anymore. Does that make sense?
Don't let go of the memories. Make sure you use them. They're your rooted base of your, of your tree, of your, you know what I mean. And your heart chakra needs some work. So we'll do that together. I'll just pull you with these ones and then we will move along.
So moral of the story Jamie is you are the only one who's
going to know why when you know why when you start listening
to your heart instead of wanting to instead of listening
to everybody else and don't be so distracted you know don't
forget about yourself you got to worry about what Jamie needs
and what Jamie wants and it's not all about everybody else
all the time you can't save everybody it's like after
my myself that sometimes too right pick and choose Jamie
we need your energy this as much to survive as everybody else does my girl
but we're all here for you because you're always here for us hence why you need time out for some
energy gain okay I would like two I would like two and I got two my thoughts no
Okay. So we have the king of summer. So warm hearted, devoted, loving and faithful. This is a penguin.
A trustworthy person or relationship enters your life. He was right.
See? Just give yourself some patience. Chris, you always prevail.
So you may receive...
Or why is compassionate advice from someone who speaks directly from their heart?
I think that that represents to me, that's like the king of like cups, you know what
I mean?
So it's, it's very much an emotional, well thought out, like not a juvenile offer.
Like it's, it's a, that's a set offer, but we've got the eight of spring, the B.
You have presented or have been presented. I feel like you're her last her last fucking boyfriend was like an asshole and fucking
Just used her and fucking just dipped out like left real quick
But I think I think this this her boyfriend and must be the one
Me he might have I think he's the one that has a fucking kids he has kids like her ex has kids
Did your ex have kids?
I mean hers, yeah hers, oh here I'll read it for you
Yes, she says yes, yes
So that's that motherfucker right there. It's all the kids. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, okay, so that's okay
Yeah, and he got a hold on
Yeah, was it I feel like there's multiple like kids multiple kids
On her ex or whatever, but her ex fuck her over here her act like she fucking uh, it's
Like kicked her out like did you have to do you get kicked out of this hat?
Did he kick you out of her pad or some shit like he had to survive
Type shit. That's what it looks like. It looks like fucking you got thrown out like he's like keep you out of the house
And you're like fucking on the street
Or something like that something like that
Like the guy was an asshole
Or something
But he's got multiple like multiple kids dude with like other other fucking chicks
Yes, you're right she says you're right
Yeah, okay, so yeah, this this the listen
The bumblebee Jamie comes every time for you
Yeah, and it was like a
You fucking you had to like move like fucking survive because of something that happened with this guy
And you thought you thought it was like you thought you thought it was like the main guy at first
But it wasn't you fucking learned about it you've learned you found out fucking how he really was
And he's got a daughter
He's got a daughter and a son
So
If you know
Okay
I'm in the 8th of the 8th of spring, the B. So you've been presented with many wonderful
opportunities all at once. Well, this may feel very stressful. Remember to be grateful for
the blessings that heaven sent to you. I'm gonna do one more just so I don't like that the way it's
Like his girlfriend's have kids
Look at this
Came out twice in two different decks. Sorry. Just this is crazy. It's gonna blow your mind
So we've had this card came up first
With the tree and we're talking about I was planning about your roots your roots
Don't forget about the balancing of yourself because that's where your structure. That's where your trunk is
That's where the strength of your drum, but like this came out, too
So let's double confirmation and then this is the like the reindeer the caribou, but it's the wheel and it's
Expected sudden positive change in your life. You can move or you can now move forward and make a good pro great progress
So letting go of that experience that you had with
You know with the other feminine energy
Jamie I feel like is
It's coming to a close on its own because nobody deserves to feel like that for that long without it, you know
the universe is only gonna
It won't put you through more than you can't handle so
You're almost through it. You're almost through it and it's like now. There's going to be some abundance now
The wheel can and a cycle is it's closing out. Do you know what I mean?
Now you get to start back at the square one you get to start back at zero and the tarot
What's the wheel coming out?
So and just you can make that wheel move and in your favor in any way
You just have power in your mindset and just have to let some things go and if you put it behind you
You're gonna get natural closure from it. It's just as soon as you get yourself past that point, which is
very very hard thing to do and I'm not telling you you have to do it right now I'm just saying once
you do that's when all of this comes in for you all of this abundance it's letting go and making
room for the new clearing out your closet or your attic okay because you haven't in a long time you
hold on to stuff like I do and most other people do when they don't when they lose things they love
because we don't that's the hardest thing for us to go through you know
But she'll be okay, and you're almost through it. Give it like maybe another two weeks max
And you'll probably fucking not even worry about it anymore as much. Yeah, it's like not even that big of a deal
Yeah, I see that too. We're gonna laugh about it in like a bit. You know what I mean?
But I love you, thanks for letting me read for you, baby girl
Good teamwork, Chris. That was fun. I always like doing collabs with people
You come on my channel and do one on time too if you want
For a second
There did that work for you. Hey, listen you ever come to Vegas hit me up
One day maybe if I could afford it ever I gotta come to Vegas with two nickels to rub together
I know you got you got Instagram
I don't have Instagram. I have Facebook, YouTube, Snapchat. That's it. I think maybe I have Instagram. I used to have it. I don't know. I'll check.
Bishop wants the cards from us too. Do you just want the same situation, Vish, or what?
Yeah, you know hit me up in Instagram or whatever you come to Vegas. You look in I'll hang out, you know, chill
I love this I got friends all over the world now. I'll never end up on a sidewalk
Have you ever met Bishop Chris?
Uh, I don't think so. I'm here.
He's like one of my actual best friends in like real life. Like he lives in Canada. He's in Toronto.
I mean, I didn't meet him in Canada. We met on like my lives or whatever doing readings.
But anyways, he's one of my best friends and he's a really good guy.
And anyways, Bishop come up here so you can get your reading if you don't feel too shy to do it.
She'll come up. She probably will.
Hopefully her being...
I think I need a food quick.
I'm gonna have a little puff of the weed.
I
Said she wanted a reading to if you guys could yeah sure would do Bishop quick
Okay, I didn't know Bishop what I'm one sorry. I missed a part. Yeah, bitch is first
I'm just waiting for him to respond. I need it. I need to like talk to the you know
I try my best on the last one, but he's free. I gotta you know, I try you know try but you did really good
You did really good. I'm just
Listen if you want you came up
It's like you still here like look for them to come in the backstage and fucking you know that at least Mike up
It's hard you know
This upset streamer just fucking with him right now. He's gonna come up though
Mine's been weird to actually like it last night. It was being really weird
Okay, I'm ready to go
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, bo
You see yes, I'm from cologne originally, but I've lived back and forth between British Columbia and Alberta my whole life
But I've never left Canada. I've been all over Canada
It's actually more expensive for us to travel
Within Canada from within can't like it's so stupid man for us to go like on a vacation to say
Like hey Bretton or like we were to go to Halifax or something
more expensive than an all-inclusive for Mexico or to go to Vegas
Yeah, are they uh, it's kind of like tripping out on like, uh, you know the tariffs or whatever
Canada is usually always tripping about everything you guys are tripping about because we're sister countries, you know what I mean, right?
I mean, yeah, there's like, you know, I mean trying to think
Okay, they have a like malt liquor in America. It's called strong beer
We have that here too, but we also have twisted teas as malt
Right well, it is like a you know, like all English
It's like strong beer. It's called strong beer. Like I know I know I know about it. But yeah
Yeah
You have to go to the liquor store to get it
you guys
Have it wait like I don't know if we don't have like I bring it up to time beatboxes and for locos and buzz balls
We don't have them in Canada. We just got Tito's in like a couple years ago
Right. Well, like fucking like mall liquor
We call mall liquor like in America. You call a strong beer, which is like a higher up higher al alcohol
Or like a me
Yeah, like before the 40 ounce bottles. Yeah, like a like big big big beer. We call it big beer. Yeah, big beer
brown paper bag shit yeah yeah yeah I want to fucking try some of that shit
like a Canadian you know well if you ever come to Canada we'll get you a
poutine we'll take it check out hot bitches and Calgary and we will take
you to go get some
Fucking Alberta beer, I guess hey, that's just fire dude. Was it a these curds and gravy on fries and fries?
All day. I'll eat that all day long
All the time like it's just the easiest thing. It's just not a main staple on your guys's menu or what I
I've never had it honestly. I've never had it, but I know what it is and I would fucking eat that shit all day type shit
Yeah, we we fucking put poutine and everything. It's like a condiment to us
Like the Kurds, like where do you get the Kurds?
I mean like I thought being a you know, I'll make fries. I'll cook fries and put like cheese like grated cheese
Yeah, most of my stuff you're gonna use if you don't have like the actual like the cheese Kurds
Like the Quebec wall like the the you get it from Quebec mostly all that cheese comes from down like the East Coast side, right? So
Anyways, you got to get shipped in and only certain places it's more expensive to get it
But it has this like texture this fights this like to but mozzarella cheese will work just same if you can do a poutine at home
I mean, I know that there's probably spots out here in Vegas. I could like get that shit
I just hadn't like looked into it. Well, yeah, I know all about a
like Canadian
Like fucking shit like listen, I think I wore the warcraft
With this guy that lives in Nova Scotia
Yeah, and
We got fucking 2300 and threes and fucking who's my homie, bro?
And I know I've met people out here in Vegas like from Canada and like fucking uh, I love I love I love Canada
Have nothing against fucking
Other than Trudeau dude that fills the fucking uh
That motherfuckers not even worth the prayers that's I'm gonna waste talking about him right now
I don't want to say anything because I don't get uh
What's his name in trouble? Oh, yeah
Yeah, I don't want to get psyched trouble like but you know I say
We're not we're not gonna I was just just we're not gonna we don't
I'll get really really heated as well. So anyways, cuz I don't look like wait. Are you are you are you single?
Yeah, I am now
But you have a kid. Yes
I'm only thinking about like a month. I was with him for nine years, and then that's not her dad
But
I was with her dad before him and then Grace was like two or three when she when I met Morgan and then
Then he just left a month ago. So it's a super fresh, but yes, why I
Was I was just wondering you know like, uh, how's your kid? She's 12
She just graduated her sixth today, so we had to go to the big ceremony and get her all dressed up and
The dad the dad you're the dad still like guys there, right? No
No, he's no, he's long gone. We have him and I haven't been together since she was like like two and then
and then he's now married and
Stuff, but the guy I agree to stepdad my partner of nine years that I just had that left like just last month
He just walked out in a month ago. So it's super new. That is her stepdad. It's not her dad dad
What so what happened with him
Why do you leave? We haven't talked about it, which I mean it's I know you don't get you know, I don't want you
It's not
What on here
Right, so it's just a lot of different things other you know, just
Well, pull the cards you'll see I'm not gonna say all my shit out loud on here
So yeah, I mean don't yeah, don't fucking leave your shit. Yeah, but that's what I'm trying to hit you on my Instagram
Cuz I would chill with you. I want to like hang out touch it, you know
We'll teach you how to calm down when you're doing it.
We can't get mad if people you get so fired up.
I try to like be like, I get involved, you know?
I get a, you know, I say, I'll hit you up somehow.
You don't got an X, Twitter?
I don't have Twitter. I've never I don't tweet those for birds. Okay
This are you ready?
Yeah
Okay, the link won't work for Bishop. So it's fine
So are you gonna?
Do you want to do what you just pulled your cards first and then I do mine or what?
I need to like figure out who we're doing now
Bishop so
Is he in chat?
Yeah, he's in chat. His name's hanging with a ship.
Okay.
And then Monica wanted a reading after it, I believe.
I don't want to forget that.
Ooh, I'm already capped in the new fish I can feel that.
Fuck buddy, you had a weird dream.
Weird dreams, hey?
Weird dreams and weird vibes.
You got a lot going on.
I can't wait to talk to you about it later while we're talking about it on Facebook, but this is going to be an exciting reading.
No matter who you've been trying to call me, I'm sorry, it didn't mean to ignore you buddy.
It's been sad.
We're working.
Okay, I'm stoked.
I don't know if I want to use these cards though.
Maybe.
I'll just keep it simple for everybody.
We can go ahead Chris whenever you're ready and just babbling.
Come on baby
Is your head unclear fish like are your heads like head in the clouds like brain fog
I just feel like there's just something like it's like you can't
defog the windshield or something, something's fogging your vision
maybe your third eye, maybe a little bit
something's fogging your energy
is the color of gray and like a mud colored thing, a mud colored thing
weird
growth
Bish, were you at a bar the other night?
Did you go to the bar the other night or something?
Like maybe
Okay, so now I feel bad because I'm the only one up here see my own channel and do this like are you awake?
He's probably not okay, so Bishop we have
Surrender 34
So
Surrendering you're just like are you to do somehow get put in a position where you had to like kind of
I want to say bigger person, but it was almost like white flag like okay fine
Like I just I'll give in I'll I'll be the bigger person
It's like it was like a surrender in that way of sorts because it was just you weren't getting anywhere with the conversation
It was just going in insanity like it just wasn't getting anywhere
It was going in one year out together, and it was like beating your head off a brick wall kind of you know what I mean
and
Pertaining to you there's cups, and there's like a little gremlin and that's like
Reminds me of pool to I just reminds me of a bar like it's just the interaction of it is like
Just backing out from a fight because the other person isn't going to and trying to be the bigger person
I think just surrendering. Just surrendering it's not being like, okay, fuck it. I cut ties with this now because I can't even
There's nothing that I can do to help it anymore
And I've tried and I've tried and I've tried and I've tried but like sometimes you just have to walk away from things
And you have not you and I have talked about that like a million times knowledge. There you go
Perfect. So surrendering because you've learned in those kinds of situations exactly where it can go and with this particular person
I feel like it's a
masculine male energy
We'll like look it okay
These two have different sizes of whatever the fuck is they're holding out
It's like a little like metal pipe or something, but they're both examining it and
Trying to figure out like okay, so mine is a little larger than yours
But like it still has the same structural value. It's still made of the same metal
Does that make sense like it's it doesn't matter, but it's always kind of just that battle of the wits like oh
well you think you know more than me or
Or you're trying to teach and it's just like it's not getting anywhere and it's just a stuck energy
It's just stuck staring at these things now. You're analyzing things from a different point of view
Maybe that person is too, but they never have the ball in the core to the upper hand
You always walk out of that with like knowing that yours was longer. Does that make sense like you're like, I know how to do math
Okay
So then we have peace
so
You know peace will come out of this situation as always because
Divine doesn't really like
There's nothing that this person has done is so horribly bad that it's like not not forgivable
but there's a lot of people that are very upset with this behavior and or choices and actions and
Stubbornness too. It's like there needs to be some movement. So
There will be some peace in this situation once somebody finds gratitude in
Anything and just anything that they're doing I feel like that's just completely lost like it's just completely been been stripped
interesting
Look at how it's trying to timid. She doesn't want that flower. I don't want to want to know like that's sad and
Having to surrender to things
Everybody's just being really pushed to have to do a lot of shit. They don't want to do lately
Or go through things that they would never choose obviously for themselves, but that's why the universe is doing it for us because
It's like a cattle prod if you're gonna sit comfortable and never ever move but still get manifest and manifest
And we're deep down want something with the universe is gonna give it to you for your highest good
Eventually whether you fucking like it or not because we would never move out of it if we didn't right?
We didn't get that fire under our ass
Oh my phone's gonna die like right now
Make that full of it
There
Nothing fancy
It's really quiet up here
Hey
No, sorry page. I'm here. I just was working on a project. I'm so sorry
I didn't know he left
Why did he leave cuz you wouldn't give him your phone number or something I heard something in the background
I don't like I don't really I don't like men right now. Okay. It's not gonna be for a while. I hear you
Not gonna be for a while. I hear you
Yeah, fair enough. Don't take your personal guy. It just is what it is
You could have been Brad Pitt and she would have said no
It was aggressive
Oh my gosh. There we go. I need that.
What is Psyche doing? Is he just like sucking on that DMT pen like it's a nipple?
Oh, somebody needs to see his supervision sometimes. One of us needs to be there all the time.
I know. I'm like an hour away from him.
No, no. Put it down.
Oh yeah.
He needs, he needs us sometimes, but I don't know what he's doing.
Yeah, he does. He does need us.
Oh
I think there might be people that are in backstage, but psyche's not letting them up
Hey, they said you're gonna leave your panel open you better fucking figure this situation out because there's people this sucks
How do we you know how to do that? We're I?
Know how but I told him don't don't give me permission and stream here anymore because no
Okay, because I was just getting trolled too bad for it ago. You're taking people off panel. No, I wasn't but
I'm not gonna deal with there. Anyways, continue with your read
Yeah, I was just bringing in like videos and sound drops and stuff and
Anyways, hi reality Nancy
Sorry, I'll read the chat in a minute. I just have been obviously even visually seeing me not check it
Bish, we can't I can't see you
I don't have any control over stream yard psyche would have to let you up, but I don't know
He's sucking on a nipple. That's called DMT
Because if I call him or she calls them then we have to leave the panel and then you guys want well then panel's done, but
If he doesn't wake up so someone else call him on discord. Yeah. Oh, I could call him because I'm on my computer
So I could call him on my phone you want me to call him? Yes, if you can wake him up
Cuz I don't know what's going on either bitch psyche psyche come back
Okay, I'll call him real quick. Hold on. Hey
Okay one more card for
there it is. interesting. okay so bish you've got the night of spring which is
So you've worked hard and what you've created is impressive and worthy of protecting
Annoying challenges may pop up, but don't worry. You'll get through them just as you have in the past
Okay, so that's clarifying the first two cards that came out in that
Put them away in the angel blessing stack
Then
We have the 10 of summer wait the 10 of summer
Look they're hugging
Kissing.
Okay, so the prairie dog. It's time to express your love and appreciation for family, but it
Be it relatives or a chosen family of close friends
Congratulations, maybe an order on a happy fulfilling marriage as well as raising happy balanced children. Oh, you're gonna
Light's gonna come back finally out from her vacation and you guys are gonna have a bunch of little prairie dogs
Let me cute. So then the two of spring. This is like the two of cups. So I know two of spring. What is that in this deck?
Anyways, it's the Pelican. So your vision your creativity and your dedication to cause have brought you great success
In fact, it may be in your best interest to get a
Partner to assist in your endeavors or oh my gosh, that's useless. Oh
Or endeavors or expand the number of people helping you so
You're already doing that though this drives me nuts when this happens because I want to know something we don't know already, you know
Yeah, you know, let's see
Let's put these back in two more and then if they come out again
But I feel like it's unfinished, and I want to hear something that we don't know.
Also, why does your brain feel so scattered?
What's with this like fog or like this just feels like you have like dementia or something, it's not...
You feel off.
You feel very off or imbalanced somehow.
See my cards don't even want to shuffle.
Okay.
There's definitely some blockages that need to be removed because like there's no way
Or the other one. I just try all the ways that I know how to shuffle. Finally I get one.
Oh, two.
Well, so we have the two of Winter, so it's the Dash Hound.
The Veena Dog.
Procrastination and worrying about others will, what they think, is blocking you.
Shut the fuck up.
Are you kidding me? I can't make this up.
I'm so glad that I say things before I pull cards.
Okay.
So, blocking you from making a decision.
If you are torn between your desires and someone else's, um, oh, someone else's, follow your
inner guidance.
So quit letting the shit that's going on around you get you down and quit letting your own
mind get to you because everyone else is trying to weaken it or poison it because you are
past that.
We can cut your legs off at the knees and you can walk around like these little shits do on nubs
TJ electricity little avatars this is going crazy
They say no don't cut his legs off at the knees, but then Docsons are so cute
But they do have short legs. No, but like seriously like you know, they would um, they're like big dog mentality, right?
But they got these little legs. Yeah, very very very very very
Intelligent they got great noses. They're bred for hunting dog, right? They have a purpose. It's in there with their blood
So don't they hunt like gophers or something they go into little holes
Yeah, they can do that. I think that they also like I might be wrong
but is it dashhounds and
Pigs or that can find truffles
Hmm. Oh, no, and there I think they were a rodent dog too like they were like
Yeah, I thought that's why they were long and skinny so they could go into like go for holes and things
I I could be totally wrong. I'm gonna hurt it somewhere
You know weird how they breed dogs like to have certain traits. I mean what do you think they do that with people?
They do obviously fucking obviously obviously they do basketball players duh
Certain friggin sports players. I'm like, you're you're a test tube human. You have to be a robot. Yeah
Does there like unhuman?
Characteristics that you portray
You are not doing people stuff. Yeah, too perfect too good
Okay, and then so we have life experience Bishop again double clarification and it's
The cuckoo. You know what's funny is I brought that butterfly up. Wait, there we go
But it's one who flew over the cuckoo's nest life experience will make you fucking cuckoo cuckoo and divine timing
I find that that is like in our reality like a cuckoo clock because we're just we have no control over it
When it comes, it's loud. It's crazy. You know what I mean like the whole scenario of it
so anyway
It's good analogy
Yeah important changes are coming into your life that will require you to take action
Don't hesitate to move in in new directions. You know
The ones that you know that are right for you. I should probably turn the light on. I just can't see
Look at this
It's like
Having those legs like you you have so much purpose on the ground, but you can also take flight
You know what I mean, and you just because you can do both
Doesn't mean that you should all the time because it does get tiring. You know what I mean
Just back-to-back transport of this energy to that energy to do in this like we all do it in our own way
Especially when we're gifted it's a lot, but you're always reminding me that like, you know
Did you recharge today?
But you always on my up my like because you love me and you worry about me
So I worry about you too. You should do the same thing like you need to worry about yourself
I know you drink a ton of water in the day like I know you're taking care of yourself like you trip
Maybe you're not right now
Maybe you're not right now. I feel like you're feeling just a little lackluster or something's just a little off the Emperor. Mm-hmm
Okay
It's a little dear mouse
so
Structure and organization are important right now
Don't be afraid to take a leadership role as you have much wisdom to offer
So this could be pertaining to
I would like to say that I don't know that he put his hand drum but he does so it's obviously
related to that he's been doing more lives on his channel with it too but I feel like
you're going to keep doing that and then going to be recognized for it the way that you recognize
or look up to the people who inspired you like that other the person who taught you or that you
Oh, I wish he could come up here, because he would show you.
It's a hand drum, like one of those, like, I can't even make this sound.
Like bonkos, or a Jimby, or a Doombeck.
Like, what kind of drum? He'll answer me.
He will.
It's a spaceship. A spaceship drum.
It does look like a spaceship, yes.
Aw.
I'm gonna try to make the sound that it makes, and then I'll stop myself at me.
It's like, you don't need that ever.
I'm terrible with sound effects.
I make them all bad.
Really bad.
Yeah.
What'd you say is because we have the mentality
of what a six-year-old?
Yeah.
Okay, so the number 16 and the number 4 and the number 13 also is significant and the number 2 so any of those
With this little dear mouse, you know, he's collecting he's harvesting. He's like he's
Organizing his stuff. He's always, you know, you have to organize some things in here. I think that you forgot
Or that are just coming to the surface and or in your general area like rearrange your room or something
Just something small like that so that it feels like a new space or that
It gives you just some sort of sense of a different kind of I
Don't how do I explain that?
Visual comfort or like ambient comfort in your own space like just change it up a little bit
So it feels different without having to leave it does that make sense because I feel like you're getting a little stir crazy
You're getting a little cabin fever
But we also have release the peacock. It's time to release the past and move on to something new this ending
Yeah, this ending is the first step on the way to a happier future interesting
So you decided to cut some ties because I know you're really pissed because I can feel it in your energy right now
for right now it might be the best thing because it could very well have been something that was
taking up too much space at the time for you right now because you're supposed to be moving
in a different direction. I remember I told you people can't come with us sometimes if they're
not ready to ascend they can't come up there yet they can't come to that level with you so you
just meet them again in life where you just kind of drift away and then you can go back together after
Viving together again. Anyways, that's the whole thing cutting ties. They're people just like naturally leaving. It's just not their time anymore
To be in your life because they don't serve the purpose at that time nor do you and theirs
That's good advice. Yeah
Very true. It sucks ripping a band-aid off, but at least it's not duct tape
Don't ever let a wound get so bad and not be prepared that you have to use duct tape
And then rip that shit off your arm because you'll forget that your arm is wounded and your hair will rip off
And that'll be the worst pain you've ever felt
So I just watched a short yesterday where this guy was ripping duct tape off his hand. I mean, that's so random
Get so that gorilla tape just wax your mustache with it. Oh my gosh
I don't care.
Nobody feels that.
It leaves behind residue.
You don't want that.
They have Gooby gone for that.
Oh yeah, they do.
You guys have that?
You guys have that there too?
Yeah.
There you go.
Okay, Bish.
Was that good?
Because I think we should run to Monika.
I forgot we were like not on my live or something.
Just chilling.
Okay.
People are waiting.
And there's Monika.
Yeah, this just call me tomorrow and you and I can totally throw some cards. I'll be at work
But I can still talk to you on my bed my break or whatever
Okay, hi summer. I love when she says hey fuckers. It's my favorite
Monica is here and we can't get you up here
So, yeah psyche. I don't know what happened to psyche. I tried calling him. He didn't answer so
You might have met a verse buddy. He's passed out or yeah, or he's in another whole nother verse
Someone's fucking he's probably like one of the car is on the street
Possible or use this in a little psychorido DMT blanket fucking wrap. Yeah, I'm a burrito
He's a nerd. Oh, I wish I could bring something up. I can't present anything
Cuz I have that short that I made it
That one where it says he's like I'm a burrito. I'm a fish taco
So cute
We need to get some merch made I
Know it's so easy
If he just opened the store I could give him the designs
Well, and I'd be happy to help you with that girl. I'm totally down. It's super easy
We said I want to do it for my channel, too. Actually, we should we'll we'll talk about it. Yeah, I use we use t-public
They it's it's pretty good. And I mean you just put the design in there
You have to make it 4k so it has to be pretty big size image
because it put the picture on it and it just makes the shirts the mugs the
The everything hats and then as they sell they ship them out
Okay, so you don't have to buy it ahead of time you don't have to put any money down nothing like that
Okay, and like they distribute for us as orders. Yeah, they distribute it
Yeah, we don't have to do anything other than make the designs and then pay for the stuff to get made
No, you don't pay for anything to get made only people that buy it pay for it
You just open the store put put your designs as many as you want. We have like over a hundred designs
But they only make it when someone orders it. So it's like made to order
Yeah, perfect. Okay, you're gonna really that's so easy
Just remember t-public or write it down or something and
Do you have a design already in mind I have like a million things I've designed in mind
Can you get them digital though? Oh
I don't know. I'm not very tech savvy. I can draw it with my hands, but then how do I get it on the computer?
Right. Well, you can take a picture with your phone or scan it with your phone, and then if you put it into
digital form, you can send it to me and I can cut it out
on the computer so that there's no background behind it because you don't want like
background like say a white background behind your image because then it when
you print it on a t-shirt or whatever there's gonna be a big white square you
don't want that yeah yeah so you just got to cut it out and then make it 4k
and then boom you're on discord right yeah yeah
Awesome, and they they pay you so whatever you make they just pay you out monthly or whatever
Fucking dope
Yeah, it's not it's not a money
but it's just
It's fun because you know you can like have your own stickers and
Shirts and hats and people can buy your stuff, and it's fun. No, I absolutely love that
Oh Monica says love to be swimming
Monica loves to be swimming
Oh dingles because he said dingles that he's swimming in space with the space turtles right now
Oh, sorry. I'm so weird. I don't know why you guys hang out with me.
Um, you're so fun. That's why you guys are all fun too.
I find the little things I love in all of you, you know, we all have our flaws too.
But I find like some of us are pretty entertaining or scary.
They're either scary entertaining combo or like no, they're all usually that.
Some people are just scary though. Very true. Yeah.
I'm with you on that. Monica, I'm trying to get a
Feel for you. I don't think that I'm gonna use
Can maybe should she ask you a question or something so you can get if you want you
I just like to go in blind though cuz then it makes me look better makes me look better as like if I don't know your name
I don't need your birthday. I don't need your age like I don't need none of that stuff because
Then it's me doing it not yeah, anything right not
There's no way I could know it's not a hoax or some something like that. I'm not feeding you info or anything
Yeah, yeah, it's my way of proving my truancy even to myself
I test my gifts too because I'm all I'm also very much
Logics and science and spirituality, but they all yeah pretty much the same wheelhouse believe it or not. They do actually
They definitely do you still have to have faith
to believe in science because we can't see it gotta have faith there too and and also in
spiritual realms also hi i'm up here by myself don't leave me
hi Miguel good morning it's like still night here it's only 2 12 a.m
i haven't slept yet i'm tired though i'm gonna go to bed pretty soon
But it's always fun hanging out with you guys
My god, it's like caught my Joe
Okay, I don't know why I'm just saying that to you guys. You got more decks. I have so I can't have a couple
Actually, I give a lot of them away
As gifts and like I need new decks, but I don't have money
So I just use the shit out of the ones that I have which is probably a good thing
I feel like you like the color purple. I don't know why I'm also it's my favorite color
But I felt like I didn't mean to grab two purple decks, but I sure the fuck did
This one's a moonology oracle deck and it's manifestations, so this one's really cool, and then we have the self care
then I would like to do I'll do I'll just think these are nice easy I'll
just see I'll pull like two or three of these for you as well just like
everyone else because that's fair so we'll do the moonology you know self-care
first why I feel like it just got really quiet in my house it was quiet the
whole time and all of a sudden I just feel like just
Because you're in the zone you're focused. I know it's like I just came back to reality for a second because the cats made a weird noise over here
So look how pretty my cat just made a weird noise, too. Yeah, they're tripping over something. I
Can usually see everything though. So like I know when there's spooky shit in the house or like ghosts
But I think they're trying to attack a spider or a moth, but I don't see a moth either. I don't know what they're doing
We're not gonna make eye contact. They're gonna do their thing and I'm gonna do my thing
Okay
Okay, so Monica
This deck is a rather fun shuffling deck and likes to shuffle
So what's putting like that hitch in your giddy up? Does that make sense? Like there's something that's affecting your ability to like
Operates as smooth as you normally would or as like, you know, walk a street line like you normally would there's something throwing you off
It's snow. Let's put it down.
concerned about someone's like health in your family? Is there someone that you're close to that's
having health problems right now that's that you're stressing out that maybe you're caring for?
There's something about extra responsibility or extra like just stress like putting yourself
through it mentally first and over and over and over and over again because you know something's
coming. Does that make sense? It's like you're expecting the worst so you're constantly putting
your mind through it when you don't need to and even when I think that because it's been in that
Say you're in survival mode for such a long time that like you only know how to do that like my brain
If I have to go to the grocery store and get something in the city
My I feel like I'm going into a fucking gladiator stadium to fight a lion my nervous system
Just fucking wigs right out with the littlest things over simulation like just your you need
You need some
i want to say you need to find some like a happy place like i feel like you're going through a
lot of stuff it could be at work it could be literally every area of your life i feel like
there's a challenge right now and i feel like it makes it hard sometimes to even just
Like disassociate we disassociate from ourselves when we're in that state
Does it make sense because it's safer than being in and feeling everything and it's like an
Escape, but it's it's not really an escape. It's almost just like like like hiding in a closet
But you're hiding from your own stuff and the things that people have caused you
It's like you're really soft energy like you have very soft energy, but you're not to be fucked with either
But I feel like whomever has been causing you or whatever
Influences or energies were involved in whatever a situation that's just happened to you recently or that you're going through
Which could be family members, you know
Because people get
People get shitty when it comes to you know people passing away or anyone being in the hospital
It's just kind of like it turns people against each other
I don't know if there's like family matters going on in that way
But people are not seeing eye-to-eye with something that a decision that needs to be made
And it's causing turmoil and or you're having a hard time making a decision and or facing judgment
No matter kind of what way you decide to go with that decision or
Someone's judging you and it's unfair and there needs to be some balance
Um, anyway, that's my first spit of this feel, sorry.
Actually, my throat chakra, like, someone doesn't want you to speak or say what you have to say,
or like someone doesn't care for your honesty, I don't know, something like that.
We have movement.
Interesting.
Look at how pretty that is, that should be your background next, DJ.
That is pretty, I like it.
Okay, and then we have make an altar. So just like you're safe space like a happy place, right?
Like that would be I feel like you're very probably very intuitive very empathic or else how in the hell would you be able to?
You know what I mean? Like look at this and meditation. We all need to meditate
Close our fucking eyeballs at the end of the day just for 10 minutes and just find your center
But this is beautiful. Look at here in this card
She's looking at this in here and this this woman here. Oh god, I'm the worst of this
She's the same little thing and that's in this picture
So it's like visualizing what your happy place means to you
What part what things need to be in that space to make you feel like that so that you can get back to your your natural
Vibration of things because you're definitely a healer you're meant to help people and I think that you do a lot
And I think you get taken advantage of there's like a reciprocation or like
Oh fuck you guys, 36 and 16 has come out in every single deck that I pulled tonight.
That's trippy.
Build strength.
So all of your experiences are definitely like, you know, it's hard in you, but it's
opened up your third eye.
So you definitely need a space where you can do these things so you can achieve more greatness
by also helping others.
You can teach others as well.
Like you could seriously just use your third eye like that's how tuned in you are lately
You know what I mean? You're noticing so many different things and feeling them on a higher vibrational level, but
Just remember to keep allowing that that to grow. It's like a goldfish if you put it in a
It's gonna adapt right it builds strength. It's it takes over its environment. It grows to it
all kinds of great size like a goldfish can be huge as long as it has the space to grow but building the strength
It just means like you don't need these these eyes anymore
You can see with them clothes like she can hit knock right out knock anybody right out. I'm just baked. Sorry. I'm tired
Mean with one punch without even looking and I feel like just you've been working on a lot of stuff also
Like working on yourself working on figuring out what's important to you
What makes you happy and figuring out who you need to battle and who you don't because I think for a while
Like your defense was up a lot because it needed to be so you weren't fair reason for that
But try not to make that a habit, you know
People will respect your boundaries without you having to tell them or they should anyways as long as you're
Carrying the right energy, right? You shouldn't have to say anything people should just move out of your way
So we're gonna do this one of these
Is we even people still in here
Watching this that's crazy
Yeah, there is I think
This is like 30 people watching
How's everybody doing?
Yeah, just super focused. I just feel like you've definitely learned a lot in this last I would say a couple of years
especially maybe this last like
year especially there's just been a huge
It's like a energetic
Matureing or like it's an ascension, but it's not quite the same as an ascension. It's a little bit different
Hmm just a minute here. Give me the right word for it
Well, it's just like the manifestations such just like the moon's okay, let's go
Do you think that things are hidden from you because both my decks are clumping up and it's like inner self stuff
These are these aren't like dark. These aren't decks that
They're not tarot decks so
for them to do that and just like what the decks represent and
What I just said so just blockages so tarot the moon. It's like what?
Isn't the dark with what is hidden in the dark? What are you not seeing? What do you try?
What are you not facing when you're not seeing what's hidden in the dark will come to light?
I
Feel like things are starting to come to light the last quarter moon in areas work through your feelings
Interesting I
Want I don't think you're an areas. I don't think you're a fire sign. I think you might be a water sign
Or like it cusp
Well, I could be wrong Monica, maybe
Okay, I'm taking that one
So release your blocks. Oh my god, what did I say? Perfect
That's where I'll end that because as soon as I start getting that clarification for what I said in the beginning with the end cards
Then it's probably almost done. So removing blockages or like releasing blockages because you can hold yourself back
I'm gonna take that one too
It could be an earth sign
So leaving the past behind learning from it, but growing from it and only taking what you needed from it
You don't have to carry the whole bag of garbage
Just takes like you know what I mean like the odd like little souvenir wrapper or something with you and then move along to the next
Place, but don't be carrying all this baggage all the time, especially not other people's because physically you're not meant to and you can't
You'll wear down any
Parish before you're supposed to
You just take care of yourself inside and out, you know, easier said than done, right?
And I'll pull one of these for advice for you, so I don't leave you hanging and then probably done for the night
Readings will be closed
Yeah, they're still clumping you really got to work on them boxes
And I can help you do that anytime if you want to like reach out on my channel or psych can help you like we're all pretty good for that
perfect strength
Look at that shit you cannot make that up
So
The line in the lamp true strength is displayed through kindness forgiveness and compassion you have tremendous personal power and courage
Fuck it the star. Are you kidding me?
You need to just keep doing what you're doing. I'm really proud of you're doing a good job
just remember to tell yourself that every day as well because
We can be our own worst bully or we can be our own like best, you know
true leader in a sense so just boost yourself as much as you can because we're a lot harder on
ourselves and it actually wears us down to you and it actually gets in the way and becomes one of
those blockages right so you're about to take a big leap forward with your life worry will be
replaced with optimism fear with hope and joy is coming home to roast roast roost to roost perfect
It's always interesting to find out.
Where's the rest of the books?
Okay, I can't see this.
Okay, well anyways, I love you guys.
I'm probably gonna go soon.
Yeah, me too.
I'm getting tired, aren't I?
I can barely even, like, function now.
Get some rest, lady.
It was good being up here though and talking to you,
and I'll see you soon.
Yeah, you too.
Alright, good night.
Okay, love you guys.